Hi Vicky madness. Yeah
Hey guys, yeah, I mean it's interesting it was here in the story
It's like, you know, I can see people pull pranks. It's just like not nice when
That's one thing meant basically mentally handicapped. It's like some people find that funny to think people that are retarded are like a
Funny or you know, I think it's like a joke, right? It's not it's not. I mean, it's like some people
Howard Stern had people on you know meant different mental capacities and different IQs, but he's like always taught them or teach
Freedom pretty much the thing. I
Don't get to explain why you would say something like that. I don't want you Alice first of all
I mean, it's already too many times tonight.
I've kicked you off because you're being ridiculous.
Okay.
You're like going too far.
And then you say like that about the,
it's just like, you said everything I don't want to,
on the show, right?
I don't want to hear it.
It's like, I don't want, I don't want to show.
I don't want in my own.
So you're ruining my shows and you keep doing it and it's like you don't have the right to come on
Tell people to shut the fuck up and scream at them
So you can explain to me in the back set or just talk to me in the back set if you want to or it's participating in the regular chat
But no not at this moment Alex
You're special as teacher before your tire is personal. Yes. I understand Amanda. Yeah, and so I really you know
I really like you know, it is like there is some kind of like adorable thing like where they have a show called
And the undatables and it's like, you know, mentally handicapped people and they put they put them on dates and stuff and they just see how they acted as real, real cute and funny.
But it's like, not nicely.
Like, whatever he's doing, screaming at people. Okay, he won't be left.
It's not, it's not cool. I don't know if you understand, I don't want that language, like people saying that.
Like TLC or something you might want to look it up. It's had a few seasons on it. It's like it's really cute and
My eyes are brown as a tree trunk
Are they I
Miss your kids all are those your little students
Yeah
Your eyes are as bright as the tree trunk. Yeah, I guess that was a the live from the show
Yeah, they had this really funny guys, too
That was like he went like some of the guys they just don't get it like they'll start like so let's find this one girl
It's a dance they go to I will I will I told him not to come up up tonight
I just like it. I don't know why he was saying that kind of stuff like it was this thing
There's other stuff being said where it's like don't say that and people were just kept saying stuff. I
Know it's probably doesn't matter. I just want to like
Showed that all in this all in the stream. I'm not gonna like let people just like
Talk all this shit. I mean so ridiculous guys
Yeah, thank you for seeing thank you so much
for always being a
great friend
Your and yeah, you know, you never got mad at me
You always like I think even like when everyone was mad at me
Like you were like one of the one people to come and like talk to me and like be not mad at me
Happy USA to my favorite cousin American cousin if you're a celebrity that kind of thing. Hey
Just dog
What did I eat? I'm having some crackers right now. I haven't drink yet. You don't respect my panel. No, they don't
But it's like that, you know, you heard this you're these stories, right?
Thank you, Christine. You're the stories like he was telling a story about like yeah, who was there just some kind of guy named
Empress
I forgot the guy's name is the Empress, it was not Empress Diana, it was some guy named Empress, Empress something or other, Empress Elephant or something.
And it's a guy with like Down syndrome or autistic or something and then he ended up getting catfished I guess by this woman or man.
I don't know if you got catfished to go to Florida, somehow.
Jade or LD and him were both like in the area like coaching him or
Sending processes to his room. They're kind of like him. I don't know. It seems like it was weird
I don't know his side of the story didn't make too much sense
You guys know like does that make sense to you like oh well? I was just I think we're financially supporting him like helping him out
Like no, no, no, he's no penny. Okay, so what were you doing? He's just like harassing him on the phone
I don't know. If you heard the story, I think Tiffany sells t-shirts or Tiffany wears t-shirts
Shared the story. Yeah, and it's been at least involves you. It's like as far as what I asked about it
You try to turn around me for sure. Oh, what is it? You're right. You're uh, you had an interview with somebody about me
We haven't you know
Wild accusation and then it turned out everything she said was exactly right
But I, you know, Alex, I do love you, but it's like I had enough and you were hurting my ears and you scream, Alex
I don't know if you're still watching, but I love you, Alex
It's like, you know
Actually animal offense criminal offense in some states. Yeah
The one of them populations. Yeah
Yeah, that's just morally they people know it's like it's like here
I had the analogy like someone a blind person will go and they had like money and they and the shopkeeper like you know
Takes a hundred dollar bill and gives them back like you know a dollar bill or something and change and say you know
It's like does anybody really do that like most people don't but it's like you know, it's hard to live in the world of trust people
Because you only know if you're out and like you're blind if you're really that blind
You maybe don't even know you're in the store. I don't know
Yep, so we want to protect vulnerable populations, of course, and and I don't want anybody to feel
harassed. We have people of all different IQ. Like IQ is something really stupid. It's like it seems
like I've heard like great insights from people that you feel people consider like mentally
handicapped or a number of things. I've seen them. I've seen them. Oh, I've seen them come up with
Lot of stuff. Oh my god. Oh, yeah, I got a message from Jamie. I hope you're doing okay, Jamie. I'm gonna hug the cats for you, okay?
Yeah, I hope Jamie's okay. Yeah, sometimes YouTube gets a little crazy and people need to take a break and stuff
But it says how the fuck do they know what they're grabbing off the shelf?
Yeah
Yeah, who knows
Yeah, so anyway
I kind of got distracted. I forgot what I was going to say, but I hope everyone's having a good night. If I pin the link
It's gonna be 4th of July soon. I don't know. It'll be actually 4th of July at midnight
But I don't know if we're gonna do a midnight speedo show, but maybe I will
How the fuck do they know yeah, so let me get back on YouTube. Yeah
So yeah, I love all kinds of interesting people.
Oh yeah, the IQ stuff is like,
people have such different IQs.
They have like, on Howard's turn,
they would like have the staff
and then some of the WACT-TAC take IQ tests.
You know, Eric's midget,
he was not mentally handicapped, really, he did okay,
but even some of the staff, they weren't that high.
There's some people who were,
But it's just like an arbitrary system based on like culture and it's like there's a certain kind of intelligence
It's like as long as you can like, you know go to the bathroom and feed yourself
You're doing okay. That's for people. They're handicapped or not handicapped alike, you know
So
So yeah, I'm gonna my hand might think okay slow tonight. What's up Nick? How are you?
I'm just doing good
What's up guys? Yeah, so also then a good time is trying to show guns. That's ready to do it again like
Why like why
Yeah, it looks pretty cool that it says
My stream is called madness and then I like I'm in the picture. I like all red if you can see it
But I'm not mad. I'm not really mad. I don't get mad. I get like, you know, hired out of stuff sometimes or you're like weary
With myself too, I'm very hard on myself. There we go. It's in my link
That's why oh Alex Alex explain in the back chat
Why you should let me back on promise you just keep saying that stuff the chat doesn't it doesn't want it
I don't want it. It's like every way like I keep like standing up for you
Then you come on you attack me sometimes
really confused Alex, but I'm like
Hello, yeah, you're just you seem like you're too upset right now
You need to make sure you're like in a calm state of mind. You seem like you're on fire
Why are you so mad Alex?
Hold up
Well, it's not yours. It's not your job to do that Alex. Okay, but
Baby, you're gonna hear me roar
I need to scare
The hyena hyena are always around
Well, you're their pack of their pack of flying monkeys or something like that their pack of like
They're not hyenas. They're like, you know, well, you know
And you know hyenas also can like the female hyenas like actually can develop a penis because like the males are so weak in their society that they
Females have to step in to do the even the producing of the baby. It's very crazy. They have a unique society
but I was on so we could have a well, I know it's better one one male line can take on all 30 hyenas and
Okay, that's all I know but yeah, but you know an ostrich can kill a lion with a good kick to the chest
I guess they can you have you know anyone to kill anything with a good kick to the balls
You've been flicked in the balls. Have you I tell people all that all the time like you're in a fight
Forget about like wrestling and punchy each other. Just lick his fucking balls. It is the worst pain
You will ever experience it literally freezes you
Just a little flake like dang if you hit the balls the right way
He's done. He's down for the count. It's the most excruciating pain ever. Oh my god
That's yo, and that's why he's live for people act all tough like yo, I'm fucking ah like flake
Well, they're very vulnerable. We agree. But, you know, they're very they have other powers and stuff
I know I know bro, but just kick him in the balls
You know, if anybody with daughters out there just tell them if a guy will fuck you
Kick him in his balls. He's done. Okay. Oh there. Okay. I was here. I will ask this to lie
I guess we're going to Leo season soon after this cancer season
We're going to Leo and in the you know, this is a studio lion lion
The body is so like strong and fragile at the same time like you men could battle for 12 rounds
Unching and you know, like you know, like you have see like just blood flying killing each other for 12 rounds
But at the same time
One flick in the balls you're done
Well, yeah
Look at the one pull the trigger. I mean thinking how easy this is not bad as well. Yes, but I'm talking about the body
Are you obsessed with balls Alex? I mean, it's like you love your balls, right? Are you just like I love my boys
I love my boys, man, but once and throughout my whole career of living
I don't know I never got kicked in the balls by a girl nothing
But somehow something like things something and men that is paralyzing pain
It is the
Worst thing I'd rather get shot nine times. Okay, Alex. Can we talk about you know the ball torture for a little bit?
I'd rather like talk about some other stuff. Okay, so Alex, okay
how are you doing that are you calm down I'm good have you ever got you know I'm
talking about though no I know I got I know that is it would probably hurt but
I never I've squeezed my legs together too hard
before once you know and you can't walk for a day like oh my god but then you
slam your hand on a door and you know break it and you'll be like lol but you
No, they're both both
They're all the beaters laughing at us by the way. Yeah, they are they're laughing at us at beaters
I don't know about us, but they're laughing at something
There's like 70 people that just and the funny thing is Christine's there all the reasons that are here in the chat
Or now they're sucking dick
Okay, well, it's okay
I
You know, I like to support her show she's just been kind of like she's like it's like too
It's like too often on like it's too. I need to like know somebody's gonna be pretty much the same person like at least
Like if they're like a little bit
I just can't have like them a different person every time because it gets to like one that one that hates me
And it's like the wicked wish one that is like, you know Dorothy and it's like, you know, like
Sweetheart, you know, it's like there's both and then it's like
Okay, well, who is it today that is like then it's like they are
Can't think a joke. Nobody everyone lost a sense of humor. What the hell's going on in this world. It's so mad at me
I don't know. I don't I don't I'm like nice. I don't really do it and people just hate me
It is like oh that mother fuck, you know, like I'm doing something
I think I'm the worst human in the world. Exactly like vacuum you polish shit. Yeah, give me electric chair
Yeah, I don't like that.
Like I felt, yeah.
So anyway, so anyone can go where they want, but it's like, you know, it'll be a different.
It'll be a different pipe. And so I don't know. Hopefully it'll be cool over there
You know beat is charming beautiful, you know, it's good. It's like that. We're not competing even though we are you know
It's the same on at the same time like a lot of streamers stream a lot and are at the same time
There's me days where she's streaming. I'm not so we want everyone to go where they want to go to and sometimes there's stuff going on
Over there. Yeah, God, oh
Yeah, we can all like, you know, sometimes the chill come over here. I'll go over there
We can have fun and like raise your channels and stuff
Back at it again. Yes, it's with a sleigh. Oh, so Joe's in love with uh, so like I like what it's like
What about so Alice is slaying because he like he's like, you know, he's doing my show, you know making me
Delete my stream and then or I'm saying because I like keep keep going and like keep forgetting people. I don't know
And he's the queen. I don't know how much Obama had to be dropped on those assholes
I was trying to hear the story from like JT about how he like scams or it was involved in like this
Taking a bit of the more you let them talk the more they report
Well, the report it was like looking report there, but they're not saying something in report
But the can't report because yeah, I mean
I never got it not how to warning or anything. I mean, I'm totally fine my account
I think the YouTube knows the difference between like authentic reports and if they're and not, you know, it's like
YouTube is not YouTube. YouTube's an AI algorithm
Yeah, but Brian will tell you that AI is there's no way AI is all
Looking at every comment on YouTube. It's just some AI program that is, you know,
programming a certain way in the flags or in things that it picks up on some shit.
Yeah. So people that want to take panels down know what to say to
excite the algorithm to AI to make a trip out. I know, but if they think about that,
if they're trying to do that, which would be like really stupid and what will they do?
But if they're doing it like that, it's like
I mean, they why would they I wouldn't have
But it's too much to look conspiracy like I I know I know I know I'm boy
Well, I'll be fine at least don't get complacent because it could be though, you know
So just you got to keep that on the deck like to be the best
Yeah, I mean, I will this like, you know, it's like there's so much like others like people are just
Where it wasn't anyone talking to check people have been just pretty weird and like, you know
People love to feel like they're part of the in-crowd or like they're part of the
People bring you over every little thing
You're a gay liberal dude. That's awesome
that reason of mind will start to tire it loves this thoughts that it's just a picture of the people out there crazy.
People hate everybody the fucking iranian say the Jews
Hate is a thing and then hate is a part of like the human psyche and there's like, you know, there's love
There's hate. There's has to be does we both that it's like
So a better way to get you know near your enemy than befriend them like it's like I'm God. I'm God
I'm God
Tiki tiki. I'm God. I'm God befriend them before you cause like no
Nope, I don't trust JT. God or Segi. They're here to bring
Bro, I've never been wrong. I told you when it happened with the Allied master computer
Remember that with that electroshit. I was like psych. You're not going nowhere. I've been through this
I can read I have a fucking ox. That's when I become a terror reader
I become page and you like I can feel and
this is
Those are not from the entities. I know the listening
But what are they they're listening they're listening or they have like little flying monkeys here too listen
So that's why I dropped a bomb on them bro
Because it's enough. It's that just milking you like oh
It's so obvious and I can feel it everybody sees it
Everybody tries to tell you buddy, but they're so good at what they do and because it's multiple of them, right?
It's just like four or five of them. So it seems more genuine like now
No way five people could be the enemy like they're also cool. Yes, they're a team of hell
Okay, you know how well my now
Have all the statistics though. I know but it's just I'll let you know unless I'm crazy and you know them before me
Then I'm just being
I don't know but it's like that's not to be like, you know people will say oh, he's I'm so insane with these conspiracy theories and things like that
I mean, I just think well just I know that God's always played them in the panel
Where you get down to the truth, bro. Yeah, but not everything is a conspiracy though
And honestly, I don't know what I'm saying is right
but it's still and every day it proves more and more right.
Like there's more evidence going towards that theory
that they're here to kill.
OK, well, OK, so yeah.
Well, as soon as you went off tonight, by the way,
remember when I just said that and you ended it?
I was in the backstage with them.
I didn't know I was listening.
It was Ziggy.
and the other end so you know what he said he goes the only reason I'm actually here
is because of Paige I was like oh what yeah they're crazy Siggy in the backstage after I just came
up like yo you do this to little kids remember and you like and and it went to the backstage
and it was us three
and I was looking at some talk and they were laughing like oh my god why'd he end it oh and one of them was like was that Alexander bro
Like I said McQueen like they were laughing it up and loving it and ha ha ha and then he goes
Yo, you know why the only reason I'm actually here is because a page
I was like why and then I hit the axe and came here looking for you
Well, you gotta bring it to these motherfuckers. The guys have just been like
Her ass is like I feel bad the cage comes on and it's just like she's like all like it's not her ass
But it's like they're trying to like hit on her and then say they're just like they have no game
It's like really like really a cringy
Awkward like they make a cringe. Yeah, they're like awkward weirdos that make up a range
Yeah, they don't read her the right way. They don't rub her the right way
Yeah, you know, they don't like see her for her. They're just like weirdo. Yeah, I see it
Hey Brian, yeah, and so yeah, and so he's never paid okay, so you know
Yeah
Another person love a page like you came on you said you had a like a erotic dream with about page
Hold those little story and then who else was like, oh, you know, mr.
Big pipes was like trying to like play music for her
We're all in love with her. I think so possibly for some way because he's so cool and awesome
You know everybody every other girl up here has like some trashy like retarded witch shit to her but not page
So that's another thing you have to read into subconsciously like we all want the perfect girl like she's cool
She's pure that she's not everybody up here's another a witch. They're just all witches but page isn't
So I'm gonna go with that theory as well
Well, we don't want that deep down inside. We don't want a page like that good beautiful girl
She's going through the war. She's so cool. She's just she's not like a whore. She doesn't you know, like nothing
Just like a good girl like that's a girl you want to come home to after work
Like I can't wait to work my eight hours and come home to page
Nobody's thinking I want to work eight hours and home to be though
or summer, or any of these, or customary.
You understand?
Nobody, that's a, I will, I'm going to work 20 hours
and go cheat on you, because I don't want to comb
to that shit.
But Paige is the kind of girl you want to come home to.
So.
Well, that's, you know, that's an interesting synopsis of it.
I mean, it's like, but you know,
I think Paige is very,
you know sweet and innocent and she's
Bad ways about her, but there's so innocent bad ways. Yeah
Hey guys guys would love to I think that some guys would love to corrupt her or something
I don't think wishes are like bad or bad. I think of it. She's you know, she's kind of
There's like, but there's like, you know, there'll be
Satanic women that are like kind of like very dedicated to devil in some sort of ways and like artists about like, you know
Corruption stuff. I didn't come up to YouTube to find a
Man. Oh, yeah, so Amanda. Yeah
I mean, I don't come anywhere to find a man, but I like, you know, well, bitches instead of witches. Yeah
You can say bitches, which is you know, it's called bitch craps. There's a whole different kind of craft a man
She'd want to come home to Amanda and she and summer and Christina. Yeah, the man should once are you there, Jay?
No, no, because the words that come out of these women's mouths
Come out of her mouth and just even wouldn't
You know you were like wait, so it's like the way she talks
But that's something with the onima that might remind you a lot
You might remind you and other people of like they're like this inner inner self
And so they're very attracted to this her because she reflects this they kind of inner feminine
They have you might have a similar. Yeah, and I think that she's the one because she's made us like hear her voice
And they see her as she's familiar and and you just get this feeling like she's the one but it's happening to several people
I could see I could see in their eye. Yeah, it definitely is
In this like it's like funny. It's actually my view at least might be flattered in some way by the attention
Tonight because I don't want to weed her out, but I was like you I could die tomorrow and like she needs to hear this
Like everybody needs to hear this I had a dream of page, you know, so I want to share
It's like our YouTube world
The girl right because everybody's great every other girl up here is fucking insane
She just has something different. I don't know that little page like
And you know, trust me behind closed doors. Who knows she might be a freak in the bedroom, but that's neither here or there
Hey, are you okay today, are you are you don't hear you though? Are you just keep saying Alexander the great over
I call him J1 the great by the way, okay
the
I think maybe you're one. Oh, J1 is known for asking questions by the way
I've been here. I mean here and there. I haven't been honest much, but I miss you
Ask you but you you're a you're dating Jay almost gone
Oh, that's my brother from another mother. Oh, okay
Alexander did you ever go out with that Colombian lady at the that was that the I did not J1 you're so funny
Because I just was like fuck that you're so funny you asked that at the check hatching place
Yeah, she still works there by the way
And you know what's so funny about that that the other day she came and she looked hot
Like she'd like arrived at work
She wasn't behind the counter already and I saw her like in her full attire and man
She was looking hot. I was like fuck she looks so good, but I had to just hold it in man
I'm not ready yet. Yeah, you remember the Chinese broad with the inverted nipples
Yeah, you told me that story. Yeah, I'm so trying to get over her man. I'm about to call her up back up
What are inverted nipples? They're backwards or something?
No, they go inside. About six months ago, I started dating this Chinese girl,
hot Chinese girl. And she was like, I have inverted nipples. And I'm like, what the fuck is that?
She was like, they're like, whatever. And bro, you know what they are? They have holes.
the nipples instead of coming out they go in and it looks like a hole like you could put like you
know a little something into it they're like little holes but yo she's the same as horny as a girl
with normal nipples you suck on those holes it got to the point that i would stick my fingers in the
holes while i was fucking her inverted nipples it's a real thing the
the nipples go inside first growing my life that I encountered this with it was so weird and at first
I'm like I am but you know I adapted and because you always love nipples sucking on tits right
nipples no not this one this one had holes as nipples
There was one day I should try to take it. Wow. I was like, you know, I'm gonna pull the nipple out
No, I was trying to like pull them out with my fingers I pull my finger
I'm like, I'm gonna pull this shit out. Like what the fuck inverted I tried to pull them out, but they wouldn't come out
But she was, she was so hot, and it was the weirdest thing I've ever seen in my life.
The first time I would fuck the girl in bird nipples, I dated her for like six months.
And then, because it started as fucking, she was like, I just want sex.
I was like, me too.
And then after six months, she was like, I think I love you.
Like, I was fucking one day in her apartment and she was laying in bed and she was like,
and as soon as she said that, the next day I just called her up like, fuck you bitch die.
later. Like I'm crazy. Christine, hit something on the nose today.
When I see people loving me, I heard Boca Chico Boca Chico.
Yo, yo, yo, Sean P. Yo, yo, what's up, my boy? I just got to
the crib. I've seen you was live, man. I go.
Yo, what's up?
Trump touch boxing.
That's your
What's what the truth song with a little squeegee?
Squeegee boy
Funniest night of my life
Are you being born?
Hello
Remember the grim repo network
Yeah, Jamie keeps talking about that
I
Can't read no chat at all. So I have no idea the party
the party
Kind of exercise
Yeah, bro inverting nipples, I didn't even know about that and it's a thing I looked it up on Google actually
But she was very healthy and um
and she, you know, goes to the doctor every six months to make sure everything's good on the boobs, and it's normal.
Mic check, mic check, mic check.
Oh, yeah, I hear you, I hear you.
Yeah, yeah, I got a phone call.
I was, um...
They cut out.
I'm burning the postman, I think everyone got the picture.
You remember?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, all that shit, all that shit.
I fucked up with her. You know why? Because that's my dream.
Like I'm such an asshole.
I let my emotions get in the way right now.
She'll be here.
Bro, that girl had inverted nipples.
The hottest Chinese girl you'll ever see in your life.
I'm talking the legs, the ass, like kids.
Perfect. Like a model.
But she told me she loved me.
I kicked her a curb on top of it all.
She had a surgery.
She had like her ovaries taken out so she can't get pregnant.
So I basically I come I just come in her come in her like you don't have to worry about getting a pregnant
Imagine having that that's the holy grail
At this age after 40 bro to have a girl because if you come in a girl at 45
Whatever they get pregnant, I think you know your dad at 70, you know, pay child support or whatever. I know that bush
I had this Chinese bitch on the burning nipples that couldn't get pregnant
And my ego kicked into the curb as soon as she said I love you
I'm not to call her she looks three blocks away from me by the way she looks three
Rock away from me. Yo, I'll call a bitch right now. Yo, Alex
I'm about to roll up a split for Zah you're
Roll that shit up man
I just came back from the city
What was it?
Time to run. Nice.
Titanium was packed this fuck out there, bro. Well, you win
Oh, to be honest to how to make a couple plays with my boy
Link him real quick
Then he de-linked he was going back to the crib and then his pops was picking up the out to Jersey
You know match you're going on for for July, so I'm trying to see what's going on for me tomorrow
Got mad invites. I just don't know where I'm gonna be at. You know, so
Don't know I'll play with fireworks man
You know, I got his fucking hope hand blown off because he was a dick
No, no, I'll be humble stay out the way you for me like like chillin, you know if anything gets crazy, you know
It's you know, you know what it is, bro
So why don't you go to the Macy's Deeper, right? I mean fireworks show
Well, what is it the Macy's firework show was a little high Macy's
But where though?
Manan each river the whole fucking manhack is the biggest event of the year for the Macy's firework show
What are you talking about where?
You know
No, no, I know that Coney Island is doing shit tomorrow. Not Coney Island's big Macy
But I don't know about Macy's why you'll guess what I just picked up a strawberry
Apple pie from Papa's
Yeah, wait down strawberry apple pie. Yeah, I was with my man. He's like, yo, try this shit, bro
I'm like, oh my god
I'm McDonald's apple pies. I'd love they're a dollar
McDonald's apple pie these ones were type of
I'm a bad bastard, bro. I bought a fucking thing of um briars ice cream yesterday vanilla
And strawberry. I hate the whole thing the whole thing
yo Alex I got straight pain right now bro I just picked up a half ounce girl
you know 4th of July I got it I gotta get damn it smells like honey I'm like
why does it smell like honey I put honey on the biscuit
You're making me hungry, bro
Let me flip the shout out to Papa's let me flip the camera real quick when I say this is the newest grade a pain right here
Eight jars came out, right? This is the new scary Terry. This is the blue lobster
Oh my god, you gotta send it to Paige. Why not Paige? Where are you?
Yeah, when I tell you this flower is
Stupid pain bro. The lighting is bad right now, but when I tell you this shit is pain bro. That's it looks crazy
Like the lighting is bad. Hold on. Let me try. Oh, thank you
You'll page me 20 me when I say lobster hold on hold on site. Stay tuned. I got you psych. Hold on
Give me one second. Let me I got to stand up for this one
Okay, boom
We in the light now y'all like no cat pain like I would not lie to you bro straight pain
Like pain like this shit is
This shit just came out
I'm trying to get a better nog profile. Hold on. Hold on. Oh
By the way, you gotta show the gear so discuss them it's up here
Yeah, that's a lot of crystals. I would not I would not smoke no dirt for me
Hold on. I'm a show what you mean that yo the gear is mine Alex. I don't sell gear, but that's my clothes game
Oh, that was a joke so that night you showed all that that was all yours
Huh? No, you guys made the assumption that I felt the clothes. Yeah, I did because it was so much
I was like this guy sells here. That was all yours. I mean, I got my Mike Tyson
Oh my god, did you hear what happened to all the Mexican boxer shot out for the woman's basketball League New York City?
We won that heck if a macho um some guy got deported so Mexican boxer
That just for
Bye
This will make that scary Terry
Scares I bought a half of this and what else I got yo shout out to Angel Reese to
My favorite woman's basketball player
she their collab with um
Reese's and last name is recent and they did McDonald's. She did a club
You know I'm saying pretty big for she like my age bro 22 23
So she going up
What else I got you want to see the gear like my boxing gear Alex. I got like the same shit my same setup basically
Nothing great nothing new wrong. Oh Alex. Yo, look what niggas got bro. This is this is weed nigga and
It's the ice cream remember and the in the Bronx
Yeah, I don't remember I don't remember
Who is the last boxer Sean Pete that for Jake Paul the other night
Yes, he got arrested by ISIS is getting deported
When what today?
Chavez junior is
Arrested by ice and it's getting deported. He has a warrant in Mexico and he's affiliated with the Sinaloa cartel
he got picked up tonight
how crazy is that
I mean bro I have nothing to do with that
I'm not sure
I know you don't have nothing to do with it
but you're boxing fanatic
after Jake Paul beat his ass
because I was like what three nights ago
tonight
Ice agent
he's getting deported
that's a funny thing to me
if you see him walking in the ring
or arrogant like I'm a child
and now he's on a plane in Ankos to a Mexican jail
you see that shit Alex?
I mean you can't even write that shit
Alex you see that shit?
yeah Tyson
leather punching bag
You're funny. So after I go through all your shit you on crazy. You're on a rampage now. No. No, I have
Honestly, bro, I found another new John Brad just been good, you know
I've been trying to like just move on and then I found a new bitch on my damn
Oh, you gotta come to me. You're wasting too much money on that shit
My oh my boy cell pounds bro bro Alex don't say that because I'm not gonna say anything
But you discouraged me from last time what happened and you know what those treadmill
No, nigga with the hole. I don't even want to say you remember that last time when niggas brought up your past
Why should have told me is really doing my wife
Bro, I want to hear from some other person and I stick up for you and then I'm like, yo Alex
You know, but is it the truth though? And then you're like, oh, yeah, it is by the way
I'm like, damn, then I look stupid enough is enough my man enough, bro, you know
Pushing people forever enough enough to choose that you're free
What the hell? Why do you need to know that? No, I don't care. I personally don't care
But it's just like how the situation played out, you know
Yeah, no, no, I agree. That was weird. How's that played out? We got three blue lobsters
We got four blue lobsters a half zip right here
Lobsters bro, that reminds you page
I'm upset. I'm yo Alex. You think I type fucked up. I smoke like almost one eighth of my boy, bro
No, I don't think that
An ace. Oh an ace will last me like a I don't know
No
20 it's like I only have an eighth. I'm like, bro. She'll last me a week. This guy's bugging not not cuz it really it really does
Hold on bro, I'm trying to find filters. Yo, thank you Gucci, bro. You may acquire game
Yo, I went crazy. I went crazy chompie and I thought some of the other night, bro. Why what do you mean?
I don't know why
That's that's what I'm trying bro, and I had a dream of page like I don't know what's happening with me
I just been going to go off the deep end
like no
Chara brother
So delete it bro. No, it's already deleted, but it already went it he've already got it
So the job is done. I duck some is real name
Don't know I guess I hate her deep down inside. I don't know. No, I'm just sure she did see
I think that my brain is so crazy that it just registers like attacks
Throughout a timeline and it like holds it in and like a memory bank
And like you're gonna get broken or not attacked. No, this is trust me. This is how it worked
So it could have been a year ago to six months ago
Somewhere to this timeline you did something or said something to me
And you thought it was gonna come back and it's gonna come back baby one day or another
And that's what happened
I don't know bro. I don't cuz I don't yeah
That's crazy because the only people I keep close to me are the people that never attacked me ever
Those are my friends. I can look back a timeline ten years back and not want to tag nothing now
But I would not go good you with me
But I could throw down a timeline and this bitch said ding ding ding
I would say
You think you're not gonna get rich a bruise and baby
We're just taking it all in and one day. I'm gonna drop a fucking atomic bomb on your fucking head
That I fucked up, but you can't do that to people you even if that's how I work bro
And don't judge me that's how God made me. I'm not judging every word you ever said to me
Even if it was 20 years ago, I'm gonna hold it in and I'm planning your demise
You understand I'm telling you right now how my brain works
The moment you fuck me or say something that I don't like, whatever it is, that my soul says enemy red flag, whether it was 30, 5 minutes ago, 10 years ago, I'm gonna take it, and from that moment on, I start planning your fucking demise.
bro that's how I operate brother and you're never gonna know what I'm gonna
let it loose you never know what I'm just gonna be like boom atomic bomb be
two bomber black later but you don't feel fucked up though bro no I don't
because why would I feel fucked up when they're the ones that fucked up they
are the ones that hurt me to initiate the bombing towards them
Bro, they didn't come out of their face in the first place. They would not have an atomic bomb dropped in their fucking head
Bro, nobody understand. So you're not my friend motherfucker. Nobody came out of those first second you beat your Amy
I'm just gonna be like cool
And I'm gonna start planning it the mines and it could be a month two months five months a year two years three years
But trust me sooner or later
Bro, I get it if it's somebody you don't fuck with at all, but bro, somebody who used to be your friend like you can't be doing that, bro
Yeah, but that's not my friend. This is my whole point, dick
I've had friends
That I go back in a timeline and look back like where no no no no
Bro don't be afraid because when niggas docks you then you start bitching bro. What do you mean?
Yeah, well exactly the second you docks me the second you fucking you might as well bury yourself
What do you think's gonna happen to you bro Doc's trying to dox me anyway still to this day. Nobody knows who the fuck I am
Has one picture of me
Nothing. I can walk right by you shrimpy tomorrow smack you in the ass, and you don't know it's me
right first of all Alex
I don't care like who it is because I know you don't but admit it
I can't walk by you tomorrow, and you don't know it's me, right?
The second you close me is the moment I start playing your demise and
When it's gonna happen who the hell knows except me and when I feel like delivering it
What's up, psyche? What's going on Alexander? What's up, man? What's up, you know?
What's up, boom? Yo, good to boom what's going on my boy? What's going on? What's going on?
We're talking about gentlemen. We'll be talking about dropping atomic moms and shit. I heard Alex talking about driving
No, no, seriously, just come up and get it over with, get it over with, because I don't deserve the strip show.
I remember you stripping in the car, bro, and I was like, yo, if I was gay, I'll be jerking off.
Yo, you was there me you we was running the backstage that night. Yeah, bro
But you started stripping your whole clothes. You took off everything. I'm like
And the long hair this guy has long hair like it's it's long
I think I think I think what's the name so don't yeah, thank you. I came up already. I was fucking with the
My
Yeah
I'm a comedian deep down inside bro. I just want to make everyone laugh
No, I'm sitting in my echo. I'm echoing
Nope, you're good. Oh, okay. Okay. Yeah now
Listen, I was fucking with the camera the other night. I was I was fucking around with the buttons and shit
I hit the thing and it's like he like
Oh shit! No, no, no! Who did that? Who killed the boy?
I was like yo, yo, psyche chill, it was me?
Said I hit the camera button relax. Nobody's gonna pawn bomb you nobody's trying to do you like that, bro
He got he got panicky. So then I ended up camming up right quick show. No, you know, man
Like that was that you cammed up for like like like like three seconds, dude
I can't do for like three seconds
I had them with a I had them with a boobop. You know, I'm saying
Sure, bro, I got the whole
Every tattoo
We had the bitches on it at night though, exactly yeah, that's right
I was like, yo, it's the turn game.
Now, come on, we was pimping at night, you're bugging.
We were bugging, but we were pimping.
You didn't room, you didn't room, you were just pimping.
We had all the bitches up there at night,
one degrees, four fucking summer, all of them
up to a second dock.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and you took it down.
I think it was at least something.
We stripped down to the bone in his car.
He was fucking up.
I'll tell you, bro.
Who's that? I don't know who that is choose so please with us. We're living with a sweetie
Yeah, that's funny
No, you can't chose like either the tattoo so fucking die. Oh, he'll fucking supply you went immediately
Now we ain't doing all we ain't doing that
So I saw who I am real quick and let her know I ain't here to
Fuck your channel. I'm not trying to pull on bomb shit
You know because I hit the camera button by mistake
But the shit was just facing my leg or something like some weird shit was facing my leg
I the camera was facing the opposite way, and that's why you gotta you know what you gotta do
You gotta put tape over the lens cuz you never know when you're gonna fuck up
Oh
You know you're on blast just keep up all the cameras and then go on
Probably hit the chat button real quick to look at the chat
No, I don't, but I did one night. I was crazy. I'm like, fuck this.
I did it once. I did it one night. I sort of got out to two years one night.
I was like, this is the time I fuck up tonight.
It was a night that I almost fucked up. I almost fucked up.
And my camera went on and it's only got thumb or something.
And I got old power and all it in the next day. I did it. I just.
The screen shot at your finger print.
They did school last this was crazy. They all went crazy. They was what is that? Oh my god
Why they all like repeat it
And which psyche you think what is that? Well, and then it was just like a Thomas the bullshit thank god
But then the next day will couple like never again will that happen? My whole phone is taped up from now on
Electrical tape around the hairy camera.
Put duct tape on both sides.
He put one in the fray.
He put some duct tape on the face.
Yeah, exactly.
You have to.
Don't tape
Here it's just because the host be moving a little funny so it be making you feel a little weird
You know I'm saying but other so you saying it depends on who the host is
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You know, did you see what happened to K-1 last night?
J-1 left his camera on an accident and we saw his fat leg.
Thank God it was just his fat leg.
What imagine it was more?
I
People do that so what like they put in all that time. Yeah, no
It's so white. Come on dick your TVP, you know, you're coming to the same place we come from so
By the way, I have that video when you trip to the bone I have it I have all of it
But I'm not up there like yes, they turn
Shots galore, I have the whole thing
Let me ask you a question real quick so since you somebody that does that type of shit what like what's the point of that?
The point is for protection, leverage, leverage, so the day you come out of your place, right, for some reason.
and slip on me now I got you by the balls that's why I do it and I'm like it's called the leverage
because I've been up here long enough to know that people will flip on you
so you have to have leverage on them and that's why I do it bro so the day you even think of
coming out of your face to me I have fucking movies so you're jerking off oh boy
Well, you don't got me
All I did was take my shirt off, but I just happen to have two of them bitches on that's why you say they're like
Oh, you stripped down to the bone. No stay turnt and I stripped down to the bone stay turnt
All he did was take his shirt off on cable. Last time I checked a man walk around with a shirt off
You know, I figured it out bro. Alex works for Interpol
Alex where he might he might it's all good though. I fuck with him
Yeah, that's why I like when he's here like I'll try to dock to you with the little stay turn with the hat on
I'm like, bro. I got this nigga bent over in a G string. Yeah
Dinosaur tattoo on his ass
He's just lucky he hasn't flipped on me
What's the other side what do you mean?
Bro that toilet paper shit
So toilet paper, I don't I bro. I'm not
I'm not familiar with this YouTube shit like I don't really go on streams like that like I got a couple places
I go to and but what's toilet paper?
Bro the little leprechaun that be running around the city in shit, bro. He calls it the people's podcast toilet paper
He's in the movie people
Oh, it says it under me. It says it under my name. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I never put that there. They put that there
Is
Yeah, I come from there like that was my first ever panel that I ever been on in my life like like like like what do you know about the
History of that place like like how long you been around I've been there. I've been there for a minute a decent
Like not not not longer. I mean there's people have been in there long. I've been there about I've been about like a year and a half
But I'm saying
Not even drama
Do be seen like the system like how it's like cattle like niggas got cattle going in and out. I
Don't really know what you mean brother like talk to me like what it like like what happens like revolving doors
People get banned new people come in is that what you trying to say? I don't know what you're trying to say
No, no, it's over. It's over, buddy
You're still one of the good ones. Just know that
I mean I listen if you know if you got something to say just say it like yeah, you know
I'm mad at you. Just talk your shit. Just say
I don't I don't give him promo like that. So it's like no you don't gotta promote it
No, no, no listen me and you both know who we're talking about so like, you know, if you got something to say just you know
Just mention it
You know, we don't gotta say his name. You don't gotta say his name. I don't kid say his name. It don't it don't matter
That's I rock with them over there heavy. But like, you know, I
Am at it. I ain't that look look, I know Alex's band or whatever. I don't know why but I don't care
I don't ask questions like it's none of my business. So that that's not gonna stop me from coming over here
It's saying what's up to Alex or anybody else for that matter, you know, and anybody else that got banned over there
They got nothing to do with me
You give what I'm saying like it don't got shit to do with me. I fuck with them. I fuck with um son heavy though
Like I fuck no
Yeah, but it's over now, right? There's no more panels now. It's the studio
It's this is it's more. Yeah, it's mostly the studio every once in a while you cry every once in a while
We you know, you'll get a panel
Since he done the studio, there was already on one or two TPP like regular
The first day was Gina Thomas and Bruno
the second day was so my asshole. And today was some other asshole. That's it. There is
no more panel. So yo, stay turned. I would erase that shit from under your name because
you look like a retard because that shit is over, bro.
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
But what now? I'm about to go over there and do an interview with tattoo. What are you talking about?
You got a people's podcast, man. There is no people's podcast. It's over.
He doesn't give a fuck about you.
There will never be another panel again where you come up with your little Luigi bullshit.
Like, I'm Luigi. I'm Luigi. That shit's over, my friend.
The only problem you'll see, Eli, is we go to his studio and get interviewed by him,
but with your long-faggot hair, you will not.
So you should raise that people talk that shit under your name bro stop hanging on to deal the life
Of some shit that doesn't exist any more
You live in New Jersey
Smacked it out of you if you want me to go to New Jersey and strangle you with your own ponytail just say it
Just say motherfucker, Jersey City. I know your name. I know your address. You live in Jersey City
Brother, erase that shit from under your name because it doesn't exist anymore.
Ha ha, it doesn't exist anymore.
You're delusional.
There is no more TTP.
If anybody who over there is subscribed to the-
Shut up brother before I go to Jersey and choke you out on your own ponytail.
Oh nah, you see, you're one of those.
Stay tuned, you're one of those, bro.
The tune into the- come on, bro.
What's your name? What are those?
You first and Bruno
You and Bruno is on the show
Bruno is the first
Let me hear this
One of you
Espresso 4
You're never going to that fucking studio get into you by Eli like I'm stay turned you heard
I got a fucking tattoo of a dinosaur am I just you heard that shit is over bro go find another panel
which you have
Hopefully Psyche will take you in hopefully Psyche will take you in stay turned
Hopefully yo
Son
The bomb idea. That's a whole lot for me. Um, he was calling you was something something P. Or some Sean
Dead in the water whatever you're embarrassing yourself. We've been having that shit under your name
Diggy slow, baby was gonna
the
JT smoking all right feeling good and fucking team wolf. We got fucking
Bitch we got turn we got boom and we got zig. It's a good little lineup. I like that
Yo, what happened to site with the psyche go he mouse? Oh, he was like
He's doing the wizard of all shit right now in the back
Yo, yo turn the thing that I didn't really like you know when the little crazy bro is
Alex turns you up and then you said yo tune into this podcast come in five o'clock six o'clock
Subscribe
This guy here's a callback party, jump under the fucking truck, he's like yo, shout out to DBB, that shit's dead, homeboy.
What's day, Alex? You sound stupid, you're dead.
You can't hear so, GBP is done, there's no more panels, stay turned.
the panels are over
you understand that
you understand English
there's no more panels
you will never go on TVP panel
with your little Luigi Avatar
and talk shit again
to wrap around your little bushy mind
on that bone
and you're still representing them
bro, thank you
talk about you
this guy represents
something
What is the deal? No, I heard about that. Is he still doing panels or or is
PPP, shut up!
Yes, but not like every night, bro, you'll get one like we'll you'll probably get one like once every week
Once it once every two weeks
What are you talking about he did one since he's been doing all
What do you really what is it because it's not on his it's not there
Stay turn maybe psych you'll take you in relax bro relax. Oh, there's still hope my man
All right, you can still find a home.
Relax.
Alex, it's like he's becoming like a 24-hour shelter
in this bitch, basically, for all the fucking waiters.
Yo, at first, yeah, I was going to go there.
At first, I thought he was rude.
Exactly.
Don't.
I didn't really know he was going to go home.
I was just talking to the monkey.
Just trying to throw him right down.
It's like you're providing a service to the mentally ill the fucking
How many drug dealers did you rob Alex?
Enough enough to make my daily quota today today. How many how many how many rock today?
No, he's the hot dog guy. He makes the hot dogs. No, he's Rob's drug dealers. He's also a NYPD. He's also SWAT team. He's FBI.
Oh, he's a lot of shit. Yeah, but he makes the hot dogs.
He's like John Wick with a badge. Like he's badass too. Like what?
That neighbor's proximity? Boom, boom, bang. You're done.
Broke in that car. Like anything in his hands is a weapon.
Next comes up
He's a savage
Why he's a he's definitely ahead of he's definitely ahead of fact
He's a snitch. He's a bitch. He's the panel Prince
Oh
Fuck fuck I just pulled the spliff and it's hot a lot of grub
He's just come on you wonder we're kicking it the other day
He made the song about you
Yeah
He has a new same career. Oh, you're talking you're talking about that
Takashi six nine songs
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, Luigi, you gotta let it go. There's no more panels at the over. It's only some
Background
The real podcast is now
So far it sucks the first three episodes have sucked. So I hope to step the game up
All right, I got it.
Well, that's too easy, like, with a stupid hat, like,
you heard, like, it's retarded.
Nah, yeah, yeah, nah, well, when I get it.
No, it's retarded.
So boring sucks.
I hope the next podcast will be better,
but it's going to be the most interesting one.
This is what it is.
That's it, I'm making it a week.
Well, why don't you do?
Why don't you do a panel, then?
I'm just going to do the biggest numbers, I promise you.
Or so we are we all like hype men for our favorite streamers and shit is that what we do would go around hype it above like
Alex is sucking dick right now
I
Have a glaze of thought and right now. What's going on? Yeah, he got to he got he got mine
My dick in his mouth and he got um, you know, what I come from
For one reason one reason glit you hear me glit. I'm here to challenge you three months from today. You're going down
You're going down. You understand you're going out three months from today. I'll be in New York
I'm gonna challenge you ten rounds. You're going down
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna see we're gonna see you've been ducking me you've been ducking me for fucking six months
Title from you are you guys going to the movies?
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna see knockout
Pretty for you
Three months motherfucker three months three months you really been dodging it
Yo, we shot weight classes though like y'all got y'all in the same weight class. Oh, right
I don't even know that nigga, bro, but I'm here shit not hard to find
That box you be on summer's panel
I might I might even been on panel with you over there
Well, you'll be using the same name cuz I don't be using the same now. I always you know, I know you you saw me now
I know you want to
And I wonder why they both sounded equally retarded
You don't know what's the debate? Oh the burden by the way
The bait today on the DT
Trial it said the burden of proof is on them
Alex guess what I predicted that shit member we run piano together and I predicted the shit
I
know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know they didn't know
You know
It wasn't another debate that's attacked me as soon as I said that he's
What up what up
Who that would add
Oh, you know, I was just googling kitties and stuff and I found myself in the in-cell underground. What's going on guys?
Anyone in Chad is cool in my book. I'm a fan of Chad's for some reason. So I'm talking about
No, I don't know it. No nobody
I don't I don't fucking notice guy. It's Chad. It's Chad. It's Chad. It's Chad. That's what you need to know
It's a black guy Chad
Why do I feel like Chad's gonna do something fucked up right now
Because you live in the end so under dry
There was a movie with a Chad remember
the more we
that
Feel like he has a child when did you when did you become a when did you become? I just I just had a shoe and I spit it out
Yeah, I know you people
Amazing how long you've been in so just tell us everybody
Fucking guys
Well you got
Give Alex about five more minutes. I'll crash out and then just not get any asked basically. That's what I actually had
I heard that word and I'm like is
Sound like somebody's saying like
You know, you come from like some hillbilly township and your brother, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo,
They killed
Yeah
The FBI watched you ever heard of a stem. So yeah
We miss right
How was your relationship with your mother man, that's crazy
Yeah, that's why how's my relationship with chat mom
that
Oh, he's gonna be
Just like to be helping God he fucking come and meet
Is I have a theory about waiter. I think it's psyche. That's why I keep the soccer counts Lord Vader
100%
Yeah, did you see he a psyche showed one day that some sword he's got some little likes lightsaber shit
His princess laia he's all about
Yeah, you saw the princess laia thing too. Yeah, so he's princess laia
Lord
Hey Alex you've been flipping them fireworks dude you make some profits
Yo, you don't get a real good shit
See at least you got to say it like well comes came up fucking
Take after cake after cake, but you know it's getting harder go to Pennsylvania and bring it back
Yeah
That little
It's not hard to grab the fireworks and come back bro
Like as long as you don't get as long as you don't get spotted there
So what I like to do is I like to grab the fireworks put in the trunk and then if that happens to be a cop in the
Area I stop at the nearest spot get me a on Philly cheese steak
You
He's not like some person that can blend in with society
You can he's like a sore thumb
Like you, you'll see him a mile away.
You should all go on right now.
This is a very cheap thing.
Yeah, Alex.
You know
Dude, you know what man don't give secrets out like that don't fucking say that
You wrote it down. I already wrote it down basic as hell. Oh, that's that's that's like that's that's amateur
That's that should be the first thing you think of come on now like I can mention a million more things
But I'm saying like that most obvious
That's a light, that's a light. Lord Vader's psyche isn't it?
I didn't know it, that's all. Lord Vader, only this little man would call himself Lord Vader.
That's not psyche, that is not psyche.
What's that? Oh, Lord Vader, but we smoking on Jar Wars, Jar Wars, Bulldogs.
Jar Wars, what the fuck? Yeah, Lord Vader was me.
Oh Lord Gator, thank you.
Oh, that's messed up man.
Yeah, it was me.
I'm trying to talk that jaw.
Lord Gator, Lord Gator.
Yeah.
I'm actually Lord Vader to be honest. Well, you know, we're a lot of us are Lord Vader is that you know
Weegee I mean if nobody gets us by now
Because he cares about that guy that killed the CEO
That's
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
He's gonna beat it Alexander. Tell him about your schizophrenia. He's gonna be white
How much you want to bet?
$1,000!
Right in front of everyone!
I bet $1,000 he doesn't beat it!
Listen!
I will bet $1,000
U.S. cash dollars
he doesn't beat it. Do you want to take that bet?
Stay tuned!
We're in front of
Big Baby, we're in front of
Alex Stiggy, we're a party, JT, child angles.
You're listening to me.
So you can't say that ever happened.
I'll put another 500 on top of that.
He ain't going to be doing that.
He's going to be doing that.
$1,500.
He's going to be doing a big fucking one.
He's going to be doing a big fucking cat.
So take the bed.
I'll take the bed.
When he ain't going to get the crazy,
he ain't going to get the crazy plea either.
You know what?
No.
He's going to beat it.
I'll tell you what we need people
We don't think so
No, I will never
Is
You're mistaken I will never
Like a dark side it's not in the middle of the dark side in the light side, right?
Remember when the emperor tried to put correct and Star Wars, but that's a whole and he was like you're wrong
Say work great Jedi brother
I knew that, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it, I knew it
the
that's good but I if you make I here's how you correct me say if you make the claim the burden of proof would be on you
I'm just giving you the short version man
or whatever the one where you know I'm not
Oh crash out right permission to crash out. Oh, check. I always ask Alex check the score, you know
I always yeah, I don't finna crash out score. I'm a
43 to like four
You know, you you know, you don't win against Alex, right? You know Alex is undefeated
On the feet of standing
You want to know how I know I got the burden you want to know go ahead. Let me ask you a question
You were straight you were straight man. You had a girlfriend before right?
Yeah, I'm so gonna you go so I'm talking to you god damn it you you had
A girl yes or no, well, yes, I run the relationship. I mean I run the household. Yes
Big-ass fight with your girl yes or no, man
No, sir, I don't want to fight you, big ass fight.
He is, man.
Let's be honest, baby, when I was like an either.
I don't argue with women like what's what would what would be the point of arguing with them
I only asked you if you had you was in a relationship
So you wouldn't understand argument. My point is you could never want when argument against a female
So basically what I'm trying to tell you is yeah, the bitch would you're never gonna
We win argument with woman
The worst
Hold on, hold on stop the thing
The worst part in a in an argument is when people can't communicate
So he's asking you a question. You're interrupting him and fucking let him finish the question
Well, there's five people talking at once you understand that correct. This is bro. You gotta understand
This is what he does. I've been on plenty of panels with him. This is this is how you move
He dodgy the question he throws some interception in the middle real quick. He tries to throw you won't get game
Right now
Yes or no
And if you have you've been in a serious ass argument once before did you win that argument again?
significant
From the time you was 15 to the how old you are now it don't matter. Have you ever been into a any argument?
If you want to sleep with them context kind of matters if you want to be in relation
You don't even know what I'm talking about, man. You're not gonna get anywhere with it. Turn
Let me try let me try it ghost you are you do you have a woman?
Yeah, you do right you ever been in an argument with her like you've had disagreements with her before right?
Of course you have right everybody does
We've had
The other guys right man. He's fucking sweet. Let him let him let him so I those just ghost men ask
By the way, too, so I think it's like one person fucking
Just just me talking to you. What was your answer to that?
We've had disagreements, but we don't argue. We don't sit there and have a whole fucking debate about it
We don't argue. I don't argue with females
Right, so when you
Rondo rondo you couldn't find a black person like that's kind of like a bad ass relationship. You said they're fucking argue lose
How do you handle disputes about things that you disagree about like how do you handle that with your girl?
If she has a difference of opinion than mine
What girl you don't like say you don't know something she can put her
She can put her two cents her opinion and like y'all listen, but at the end of the day, it's my word
What I say goes I mean, it's simple how long have you two been together?
Um, no, no, never to get like officially, uh, six months
Yeah
This guy's hilarious. Yeah, this ghost man is beta
Oh better in real life then right
Mean can I say the phrase? I mean that means no
Here I'm what did you say I don't know I'm talking to four people once
What's your question
Ghost you better in real life
There's beta real life. Have you met your woman in real life like in person?
She's my girlfriend. She's yeah. I mean, yeah
But you don't like live together, right?
Actually met her in real life, too, because I met her
At a fucking car rally believe it or not. Okay, so you two like live in the same town. Yeah
Okay, um
Yeah, so what he's saying is like when you guys have disagreements about things
Do you compromise or is it just whatever the fuck you you you say it is like?
Yeah, I'm a night. I'm not gonna fucking sit there and believe the relationship
She can have her two cents. She can put her opinion in but what I say goes I mean
I'll see you slap her really that hard to believe you ever try to meet her in the middle
I think I do beat the fuck out of her like no you guys are using something like you guys are using weird as though
What I say goes that's what it is. Obviously. I listen to my woman. I mean, but ultimately I fucking run the relationship
I provide you listen to your woman
Yeah, listen to what she has saying unless she like but she's not a bitch or she's not like that
You debate her do you guys debate?
Does she debate you?
you are the way you know but she has to be a lot of Myron so she's been uh she doesn't list a lot of Myron games
interesting what she looked like if you blonde did she burn that
oh she's looking at her
where's that my friend
let rondo ask you a question ghost so
help me rondo help me rondo
yes is your girlfriend name ghost too cause she sound fake
I mean
She sounds fake okay
You made that shit up in like three minutes on six months. I've met her a couple of times
She might be hey, she might be getting
Just say that's all I'm dealing with abroad. It's not my girl. You you
No gang like you said you met her like four times
Oh, she's getting roped right now. She's getting a whole big full of back right now, right?
Yeah, what's her name? What's her name by the way? I didn't catch that. What did you say the name was?
Yeah, what was the name? Alex. Alex the second Alex.
Alex
Whoa, it's correct, New York
No further questions your honor and she's the best rest she wears white t-shirts
We're dropping we're dropping that we're dropping the gavel
Basically the consensus is you don't know woman. Yeah, her son is what?
This is my fucker's lion
Oh, you're always gonna be fucking health in the tent of court you keep it up
You pay for pussy
I don't know. Don't lie about
Like you could just hit one and move to the next. What the fuck are you paying for one for you make no sense to me game?
So wait you went from having
Robin talks and listen listen listen, but it's
Imagine he's with us. She's pregnant. She has a baby. It's not
I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an eagle, I'm an
It doesn't take much but you guys next time you guys
You went from marriage
To fucking I get prostitutes
At the Robin's Park yo from Mary's
I like to watch
Bullshit, look what I made poppin, so thank you
That would have been fucking amazing
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Who the fuck is gay here?
Oh my god, you could all be gay and I'm the dickhead here.
I am the monkey in the middle.
No, you're gay as fuck, Alex.
I am the straight monkey in the middle.
Holy shit, I'm going around the horn.
Rondo, are you gay?
No, you're aggressively gay, Alex.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
that's two yeses so far
hold on
stay turn i know you're gay
stinky i know you're gay
oh my god i'm surrounded by gay molo gay
i really like myself
i'm thinking
i swear to god this whole time
i'm like god i'm psyching the gay freak
and world man
just having fun up here
But no, I have a wrong, don't I?
I'm in a Russian bathhouse right now, aren't I?
I'm in a Russian bathhouse.
By the way, I just want to let you know.
Is there any gay men on this panel right now?
Sounds like you're all gay.
I want to fit in too.
Super good
It's a lot of sauce activity in the game
Like no, no, no, this is not a way to pay or give out gay favors or some shit to earn some kind of fucking favor in this bitch
No, yeah, that ain't happening. Listen bounce me out of this bitch right now. Kick me
You gave fuckers how many are you or gay?
Well, I'm not gay at all.
The silence speaks volumes. You're okay.
I'm the only straight guy in the world for salad.
That's weird.
No wonder.
You can't get lucky right now.
That was you.
You're gay motherfuckers.
Are you all on my dick too?
Are you all secretly loving me too?
You gay freaks.
That's a whole nother ballgame.
I want 10 million. I got a movie for your ass
Right now dude
I don't know
Because you're always playing gay peek-a-boo with him. You're always doing some weird
Like I'm not playing gay pickleball with anybody.
Yeah, you're playing gay pickleball with anybody.
So that is funny to me, bro.
Yeah.
You're making alternate realities.
And you're saying, like, I'm living and I'm not.
You're making alternate gay pickleball realities.
I'm not playing gay pickleball with anybody.
It might be.
I'm not gay.
I wouldn't touch a dick if you killed me, so nobody's playing gay peekaboo, but I get what you're saying.
It's called gay peek-a-boo, indeed.
JT can open up your gaze, little ass.
No, I'm not opening shit.
Gay peek-a-boo.
You guys play gay peek-a-boo.
What the fuck is that?
Who the fuck said that, by the way?
Who knows that term?
Gay peek-a-boo.
No, I meant mentally.
That should be you, D1, Tyler, Wade, ASAP.
I think the little man is a good one.
I like it.
Gay peek-a-boo.
Yeah, you don't want to talk about me.
He's playing game.
What does that mean, though?
I don't know.
Do you hide when your gay husband comes home
and you just pop a top towel behind the couch?
Like, why do you keep talking about gays?
No.
You jump out of the car and stick it in the desk.
Like, gay people.
Like, what the hell is gay people, though?
I don't know the rules to that game.
But now we have rules, checkers, checks, every game had rules.
I wanted to know the rules to gay peekable.
Well, you already know the rules, man.
You've been for a long time.
What are they?
You have to be gay.
That's rule number one.
What's rule number two?
You hide and take it in the ass all of a sudden.
Like, I wear the rules.
No, no, what are the rules? How do you play this game?
No, what the fuck is game peekable. Oh my god
That's the shit the trooper doing up here. He got busted dude. Yeah
Doing gay peekable with you. I like to play play
Run that shit. Oh, it's a real thing. Yeah, you're okay. Oh my god ghost your day
Because you
And I'm figuring it out now little by little a beautiful woman. I have a beautiful woman
I don't know what you're talking about. Jesus
You're so big you're telling me you put penises in your mouth and take it in the ass
You're gay men, aren't you
That's why you come on me so hard because I'm the only straight one up here
That's why you guys hate me so much because I'm straight and you're okay, aren't you?
Alex wants a race your day your gay man, aren't you?
Holy shit. How many so you're done Jake is gay
Go stick with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the fire with the
that means you're gonna leave right
that was odd that was odd wasn't that strange yeah it was fucking weird that
lasted longer than I thought it was in like five minutes my bad
Not for an attention who are like Alex
Yeah, no, that's it last it for a while. That was
Horror about it as you are and I know you both have attention. So that was that was a fucking meltdown, dude
Second week
Actually gay right there. Yeah, that wasn't a crash out though
He usually crashes
Take everybody else off
like I honestly the way that went I feel like he wants us to be gay correct
Yeah, you know what I mean
That was weird
Now Alex what kind of stuff do you like to debate about man you're always talking about debating
No, that's goes not Ali. Oh shit. That's right. It's like the same
It's the same shit just a slightly different
What happened nothing what what happened here it goes
Yeah, hey yo ghost
Ghosts you there. Yeah
Wolf man said he wants to debate pick a topic
Fuck you doing that smoking back the time
You sniffing crystal
It's in there silent for like a whole minute
Come back to us. We're calling you. It sounds like you're finishing your head or something like what's going on gang
They're okay. You smoke a meth
It's probably all you crack I
Whatever it was hit him right now, but he's not even talking can't even talk right now
The shit must be hard. Yeah. Now. He's peeking right now. Whatever he's on. He's peeking right there
It might be on that matter. You talk too much. Stay trying daddy. I should take your name
It goes look at my name like you a lot right there. Like I'm always
You know, it's better to listen sometimes
Mediocre
where we're talking about Alex
on him that wasn't a real I do it
That's my way into your pockets
I'm kidding with you, but seriously, what kind of stuff do you make money? I mean a real question be how do I even fucking make money?
I don't know. I don't know what you're doing. Yeah, what are you talking about? What kind of stuff do you do?
How does that matter you don't fuck you're talking about
He got
Bro fuck that you want to take it serious now we can take it serious. Yeah, what do you do? What do you do?
Really, what kind of shit do you do?
Don't give a fuck what you do. I didn't ask you. That's I was interested. That's why I didn't
Probably would ask you I don't do shit
You brought it up
You was trying to flex what you do for a living. I was talking Alex. She fucking retard. Are you not smart enough?
I was trolling the troll it's not that hard to understand
No, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we didn't, we
I heard real quick. Give me like 30 seconds. I've ever got stomped out on that podcast JT. I'm not gonna address him
So don't even you have the name you have the name you brought up the name like Alex was saying have I ever got
No, go. He's not engaging you join many of times because you're too fucking stupid to have the guy just me now goes done
What the fuck you're talking about? Yeah, sorry why came here for him? I came here for him, but he's not engaging you anymore
I know
I'm not gonna debate you. I came here for him though. I know what he doesn't want to talk to you. Let's talk
I'm not gonna talk him like
Specific ask questions so like he can make this argument against me. I'm here to debate him
But when I talk to you and I like we hang out like he's gonna like
I mean fucking we do it. What do you want to know? I feel like you never want to debate with me. I don't understand that
What would you like to debate about? No, that's not what he said
He said like it's kind of weird because he's like basically saying I don't want to talk to him
It's kind of weird what are we doing remind me?
Um, oh, I can uh, I don't know the time I can remind you what I cast was on because I know we both join
But the one guy that knows you the longest he's calling you out and you're not saying anything
Alex is actually, Alex has actually known me the longest.
No, no, no, no, no, Alex, this other guy.
Fert, what's the name of him, name it.
Ditching down to him and you're fucking,
All right
You're willing to listen to what you're calling wolf man
Fucking all of a sudden listen to shit. Who's done me the longest what?
Who's done me the longest?
But she didn't know me yet, you know, but I
I
Been observing you for some time now. You didn't know it, but
What was the one thing you want to debate about then since you've been looking at me so for so long we've known each other for so long
What was that one thing that you wanted to talk about no what and that's why I say what is the main thing you like to debate about
You've been absorbed me first. I haven't been absorbed in you. I know he has with me the third time. I'm talking to you
But what I'm saying is I notice you always talking about debating
But I've never seen you debate anybody and all the time. I've seen you I just I'm asking what
Are you the one that wants to debate are you the big dog?
Since I've never why not what the hell why not you want to debate about something what do you want to debate about?
Don't know it's not my thing debate isn't really my thing you pick you're the one that brought it up dum-dum
You pick a topic
We can decide on topic and we can meet back up because I think we're both gonna be like what do you want to talk about?
What do you want to talk about or we could like?
I'm pretty sure I mean
Normally religion politics philosophy what what do you debate about?
Girlfriends all about girlfriends wives. Well, okay. Okay. Let's talk about this. Does your woman think about you spending money on prostitutes?
How does she feel about that?
I don't have a woman and I don't like
I
Please if you have a hay bell on the left and you have a hay bell on the right and you put a donkey in the middle you don't know where to go.
That's not logical. He doesn't know where to go. I mean
It was starving self to death if you have a if you have a retard up here, and we're all clowning him
And then I want to like make him leave so I joined the right side because you know, I'm a human
Doesn't that logically follow? Oh
Did he replace us? Okay
What did you just ask me right now?
didn't ask you shit. Oh, you were talking to that other guy. Yeah, I was, yeah. Well,
he's gone now. I can, I can, well, I can say basically what I was saying. Well, I don't
know about him. He was saying donkey and stuff, but I want to, well, me personally, I want
to Alex to leave and I'm not allowed to like debate on these channels anymore because
psyche and like, you know, the people, they get mad at me when I actually try to. You
It sounds like you lack you lack life experience ghost. Okay ghost. I it sounds like you sound like a fucking retard
So ghost why did you because I got it you in my mouth right now? Sorry? I just want to know
Ghost goes goes one second one second ronda ghost. Why did you lie to me earlier?
I'm not taking it personally, but why did you lie to me earlier by having a woman? I
Thought we were making him leave
But it doesn't matter we weren't having a debate dumb dumb
I thought we all agreed. I thought we all agreed. We were making Alex leave sauce
It's like going and you guys kind of all something not Alex
But you guys all those newer people kind of something, but I thought we were making him leave
But if you'd ask me straight up your boyfriend
Be back up here when you gave free
I
Not like I like you guys
That's what ghost said
Cuz you're a fucking retard and we wanted you to leave
That's the bottom line of it
Alex's Alex's day he's got money
Don't you like
Like so lanky fucking skeleton
Take with a baby like this
Alex I just want an excuse to talk about some gay shit man
into the lake of fire
you're gonna do a triple ending to that bitch
psyche is gonna get pushed into the lake of fire
he's gonna do a swan dive
in his speedos
psyche is gonna do a swan dive
in his america flag speedos
into the lake of fire
you're gonna be the king of money
Ah
We need it
He doesn't want to be appear right now
Don't want to be up here. I don't want to be here right now. Yeah, I don't even want to fucking be I know I I know I I
Shaked the cage and the feathers and you guys get like, you know weed it out
Yep
You are
Alex you should make your own
You guys take dick in your mouth, you know what I'm saying
Oh
Yo, hey yo psyche flicker like a bugger psyche flick them like a bugger
Yeah, I like five seconds curves of my it'd be flipping in like two minutes watch
Hey, he was back he was back
So why didn't you end up debating him? You said you was talking to him
He wasn't there at the time. You thought he was here
He came back on why you how come you didn't tell him you want to debate him
Alexander what are you talking about?
Well, you guys all sound the same man by no Alex, but you know
Stop knock it off man. There are many dicks. I know you quite some time now. You ain't stupid. You're dumb
But you ain't stupid
You guys do something though, and that's I mean it's debatable maybe but now you can tell you can tell you know who's who
You know
Is different
For two years we find you the difference between
Fucking fresh and fucking Chris not myron, but those two I fucking watch it for a year. I don't know who you're talking about sound
Well, that's fine. It was an example, but it's fine, but you guys do some the same you have the same accent
Yeah, don't even bother. It's a different channel access is different
Accents I everybody got their own accent dependent upon where they you know where they live in this and that some people sound southern
Some people are from the city
Nobody here has their face here. So how am I gonna be blamed nobody shows their face. Oh, yeah. Are you saying I sound like?
Me some kind of retard
That's a valid question you do I sound like
Yeah, you guys got the New York accent. Yeah, that's kind of something I have a New York accent
Because I'm not even in New York
No, I'm just trying to be clear what you're saying you think I sound like turn yeah
Well, whenever you don't right now, but when everyone's talking at once. Yeah, you do. Oh, like you have a hard time discerning who's speaking
Yeah, he's trolling right now hard as hell. He's that's it's that it's that autism
Stimulation I was trolling hard core, but I'm not
Look go. They died. Did they ever diagnose you with autism? I'm asking serious question
Like you're feeling you got a do you got a bit of that
Hard to sell like you're overwhelmed like you're overstimulated when too me too many people talking at once
You don't know who's talking well when I don't know them what if I don't know them
Yeah, you know you know me ghosts. You know all these people
Okay, no one person you know these people. I don't even know you when you say no
Buddy not really talk to you. Well, you know about me. Maybe you spoken to me sound the same. I
sound like turn
I sound like Ziggy too when you guys are now when you guys are all talking together. Yeah, you know all blends in
But too many New York people in here, you know, it fucks it up, but why why did you lie about having a woman?
That's a good question
You
Let me run my runs
I've always been very honest with you. I thought we all you're gonna have to shut up and listen though
You know, you know, if you
You know, you can tell us tell us tell us why you lied, okay, please be quiet one pocket and I'll give you the same
Yeah, go on tell us about why you like about having that stare
So I thought we were trying to get rid of Alex and I thought that too was asking so I was just like I'm never gonna debate
The sky I'm just gonna fucking agree with everything. I'm not you were speaking about on your talking to me
Are you like yeah, I thought you guys were acting them on on purpose because you know what he's gonna do he's gonna crash out
They's gonna come back and these are you like
Not at all, I don't try to be nice
Look Alex is a he's an attention whore. There's you don't need it. There's no in-depth explanation for that
He just wants attention
It's kind of like you but like a more amped up version of it
But no, you know God did what you like you I'm kind of like you but more amped up version of the right
Is why are you here? No, you and I are really not the same at all. No, but why are you here? Why are you here?
Kind of with the same thing correct. Why am I here?
Yep, why are you here to talk to you?
Yeah, I'm here to talk to you. Why are you here? I can answer the same stupid ass questions you can why are you here?
I'm here to talk to you
Can answer that question you that's a that's a good
It's just gonna keep doing this I did but I didn't ask him answer my question
I can tell you I'm reason listen. I can tell you
And fucking still talking man was
I was trolling Alex I was trolling Alex. What's your sister's giving number by the way if you don't mind me ask
that was a dumb question
so you asking Ziggy or you asking me
do you fucking see that the conversation
I was talking about
why would you ask that
why are you asking me questions
what does that have to do with anything
stop man was right that's all
that's all
I think rando was maybe on to something we said you lack a life experience rando
I was just thinking that yeah you lack life experience
That's a speculation you don't have to fuck you're talking about
It's an inference actually it's more of an opposite yeah
He's kind of inferring that based on your your behavior and the shit you've said here
That's an observation is that what you just said?
Inference
You're not used to talking to anybody who knows anything are you?
Well, they're used to it now in this family. Oh, you used to talk in a stupid fox. You think everybody's
And are you smart I don't know am I fucking no mask
So you lied about having a woman because you wanted
Well, that's unfortunate
Spice Wi-Fi, he'll be back up
No, that was psyche. Why do you know?
Yes, go
What's up, Rondo, how you doing?
I'm just hanging out
Like run do
What's up the charm so did you ever have a girlfriend or no?
Have you ever had pussy or no?
What's up, ghost
Don't give a fuck what you like I didn't like I was looking at messages and shit. I heard you heard you say something about turn
Yeah, I said what's up turn? How you doing? Oh?
Sure. No, I was just looking at messages. I'm just I'm chilling right now
What did you want to debate me or something? Oh, you just tell him right now, too
You're chilling about what dude about what I could I cold cold cold?
Man
I'm just trying and I'm trying to give you something different to go on you know other than your whole debate topic
Let's just you know, let's just groove out
Because there was no debate
No, but we're like like when the conversation not going your way you just want to write okay sucker, okay fucker
Let's run it. Let's try to make Alex see if there was no official debate. Nobody was trying to make Alex leave
No, he's got that shit in your head. Why nobody was trying to make Alex leave now one person here
you keep talking about it debate debate debate debate then you and you
rondo and you churn and i never said anything about one time
let's you see one one let's fucking run he puts words in your mouth like he
doesn't put it look look back to let's run it you are look look back to let's run it
oh you got it here here here here here here here yeah yeah you're bringing up
You know
Hold on turn I know me too
Do you know what I think is kind of cool is that fucking turn was already fucking calling you out
You guys call him wolf man
JT fucking
Yeah, he pulled he pulled you out there and now fucking we get kicked and then fucking goddamn turn goes ha ha
Yeah
Exactly right exactly like the the Mortal Kombat
He's JT and Ziggy's now and rondo
I can't know
You guys really want to take to the man I mean go ahead. It's not my thing
No, no, no, you're a good deal. You take it to me. Well, let's run it. Are you? No, you're a no
I think we should run it. Can we run it?
What are we running? Run it run it. No a ghost run it run it ghost
Think it's a very good idea. I think it's a healthy situation
Don't do that. Yeah when it's four against one. We got to keep it on topic. So what there is no four against one
Oh, yeah, I think and you know what?
Persecution coming to you right man
No, you're smart
Conversation which I'm not being a victim
No, it's it's everyone's having a conversation
You can you keep talking about this three against one wish shut up purposely so you can talk to me
What do you mean I keep talking about?
Damn, right there.
Don't sound good.
And this guy clearly knows you fucking more than fucking
easy of us do.
I think I know you pretty well, ghost.
I think that you're a fucking retard.
You don't have to fuck you're talking about also.
Yeah, I know who this guy is, but when the boys started
coming to these things.
I'm talking.
You literally keep saying like
Three versus one that's what you keep getting fucked up. We're being quiet
He wanted to have a debate with you. He even told you to pick the topic, but you're so fucking dumb. It's so
Bring a topic up and show your skills. It's just a conversation man
You keep talking about debate, but you never debate
He's even telling you pick any topic you want. He'll have a conversation with you
Right now you're very avoiding
Your favorite Alex, maybe you can help ghost real quick
that
Because we want Alex to leave Alex you're here now, so you can hear this
Nobody care if Alex stayed or he didn't
No, you know that I would say I wanted Alex to leave don't say we
Yes, is there a mouse in your pocket leave. We'll play it back
Well, ain't no playing it back
Let me ask you what is your issue that you got with Alex you have an issue with him or do you like him?
He's a good guy
we always debate I think we have differences we you think you guys debate about things what are you to debate about norm
We debate a lot all kinds of stuff all kinds of stuff
We like literally even the tacos believe or not we debate about a lot of stuff
He's upset because you know what do you care Alex? What do you do debate about man?
You wouldn't go everything under the sun basically you name it we debate about it
that's why he's so sad
So is that true ghost? Do you have some resentment towards him for kind of I think that my friend of
Yeah, I think we might have to team up here. I'm 44 to 3. I think Alex may have to team up the
I'd be pissed if I was lost to base to Alex to
Yeah
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
that's the impression I get from you guys
all right, what impression do you get from me?
what conflicts do I have?
you love attention
oh, you call me an attention whore
that's right
you love attention
for sure, but you're not a mad guy
you just love attention
you love attention
you do, you love that shit
15 minutes of fame
but you know the tension
You got this thing about you
You got a proof
Yeah
Attention or you know like
well you know there's levels right nobody would be here if they didn't want any attention so they're here for something
but it's level I don't I don't necessarily like the guy
so are you an attention whore hold on hold on
ghost
ghost hold on
I'm talking to whore
yeah basically you're the same thing
that you're saying I am
you are more of an attention whore
and you hold your team are nothing but a bunch of attention hookers
Booker prostitutes. Yeah, you come with multiple people wanting attention
Well, listen, that's why people's panels. Who's the attention who?
Shut up exactly and if you have a site he's not here right now. So why you here?
Right? Because you say psych, I'm here to say what's up, but you're here arguing with me and Ghost and stay turned that don't know you, don't want to know you, but we don't want to know you.
Me, Ghost and stay turned, we're not gonna do you, but you're here as an attention pour.
You better settle it down, boy.
Shut the fuck up!
You're a little tension hoarse.
Shut up!
The ghost and Satan want to do with you
near the psych, obviously. He's not here.
So you're giving your attention
more energy to us three.
Let's run it on these motherfuckers
He was giving me a boy
Panels like they own the shit like
Let's say in the quiet you act like I know JT like so well
This is my
But you act you you act like I know JT said well
the
Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex, Alex
You guys got to go back to the drawing board. Why are you why?
Alex, why are you like so confrontational, man? No, you know what it is. He's got this like
I didn't challenge you I didn't challenge you
I
No, do you know who we're talking to?
You sound like you're slumped over.
You sound like you're slumped over, brother.
Are you slumped over?
Are you talking?
Wait, who are you talking to right now?
I'm talking to all of you, Ziggy.
You sound like you're slumped over.
Everybody.
Yeah, Ziggy.
Ziggy.
I'm Ziggy.
Fuck you.
People get
Tony Montana
I'm next
Why do people start getting booted
The the the yo somebody had like a chicken a rooster in the background. Yeah, I heard that shit
That was only one person though
Oh, we're back
Moving people around again, you know we didn't people out by trying to figure out who that was who was that by the way
That was them bro, that was the enemy
You have run white rondo it was wolf. Yeah, what is the enemy?
No, I mean, it wasn't me was a you stay turn wasn't me
Was what me what are you talking about?
the rooster there wasn't you playing the rooster in the background it wasn't me
dude i was saying it the whole time i thought look at this thing
now the little spokesperson they send up the little guinea pig
they send up the little guinea pig up here god the little guinea pig
shut up your little boys ran with the tails behind their asshole and now they send the guinea
You see that they send a little guinea pig up here god
Show but you don't like them look around look at tony
We got a white rondo like super black rondo. Help me rondo. Help me rondo
That's ghost AMC which I think ghost is also him
EY
What you mean? That's not off the table
Ghost is tony
I'm still going with that
They're
Tony's a loser
Fucking fat the crepe loser on YouTube
Cuz he strikes people
It is the epitome of mental issue
He they build these people belong in a fucking rubber room brother in a straight jacket handcuffed from head to toe
That's how crazy you are. That's what Tony is
Stayed shirt. What is it too late to change my partner?
What do you mean change your partner?
I thought it was a TV to you. I don't know Alex
He's retarded. What are you talking about?
I thought we're having a 2v2 debate. That's why I swore up here. I don't want Alex as my partner
favorites
you think he's stupid
or just a glider, what the fuck are you talking about?
thank you for having me background
oh by the way that was me
ay yo come on
That was me with that was me with the turkey chickens and turkey chicken
I'm Rondo. I'm a loser. Oh, I pull them up. I'm a dick. I try to bring channels down and I can't bring nothing down
I raise looking chicken nothing
And look at Wolfie! He's back!
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
it was a
one
Well, what's wrong with the rooster? I understand
Don't make shit though
What do you mean? It's beautiful. It's looks commercial even it's a red island ride man
If it was so if it was so beautiful, why would you get kicked out of the fucking?
If it was beautiful, we'd all try to be listening to it correct. What's going on with you ghost?
You see well because I'm being picked on about having a rooster. Why are you unhappy ghost?
Well, I'm sorry. I don't mean to pick on
You're being kind of a downer
Would you would you like me to be an upper?
Yeah, can you pick up some pick up your energy a little bit I watched a ballerina today
You the John Wick movie was it good? Yep. Oh, it was excellent bad ass by the way, but you got the comebacks of like four-year-old version
I'm not trying to make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a comeback from Stupid Frog, but you make a
Reflect a little more on that but yeah, maybe you're a little extra critical about those things sometimes
it that that you guys were the bullies that got you guys were the whole body listen go
everybody here like she was picking on you fuck all y'all
no it's the victim complex thing stop it
we ain't no victim by and plexi no you're not you're not a victim say it
no we actually want to be friends with you
we want to be first time to be cool with you
wouldn't that be cool
nah
No, no. Oh, I said no, okay. All right, you know, you know me JT
I'm if somebody says no about me then okay, all right
Then you don't want them to be cool with you is what you're saying
But you want them
Yeah, treat me like sure
They can yeah, that's what you want. I want to be cool with people you want people to treat you like shit. I
Don't get along with retards of bullies. Well, who do you get along with?
Somewhere in the middle you're not a retard you're not a bully somewhere in the middle
But you just called him a retard a while ago and a bully. I
Called all you retards and bullies. I know I know that
I know you're not a retard in a bully
Yes, you don't know. I mean, maybe you've heard me talk before maybe you think that I don't know
Maybe maybe we got to run it
before I crash out and
Would you like to actually have like a debate we can actually do it? We probably do on psyche channel
I'm pretty sure you'd agree with it. We can pick a topic. We'd have to agree on it
He's the one that chose. He's the one to ask you to pick a topic
So don't turn it back. Yeah, I'm talking about like a formal debate. We can pick it
Yeah, and we can actually talk about it. I mean we could run on the spot, too
I mean that does happen, but if you want to do that you already did and he already lost
See the white t-shirt shouldn't even be I don't know just want you to be happy. Maybe I should ghost
We just want you to be happy
Is that wrong
No, not at all
Don't you want to be happy to shut them? I just want you to shut the fuck up
Is that what it make you happier? Yeah, everyone just shut up. Don't talk at all. Let fucking ghost talk
All right, Tony the ghost talk aka Tony
Yeah, it's your moment go that's the two ponies talk
I like master computer
Yo, at least I give you contact for your stupid channel
I'm a cock sucker. I'm not what what?
Yeah, you know Tony suck my dick
You understand Tony Bologna the little choo choo dream boy
On your knees and suck Alexander McQueen's dick
this guy's loves talking about gay shit I swear yeah
Something weird man right there
They make a good couple they would make a good couple. Well, I know why psyche keeps you around cuz you're gay shit
When I said flashbang, I didn't mean to surprise being here. It's a clutch being the ghost
I don't know what you're mumbling about man. Honestly
At the time
Oh, the discord Brigade
You guys are freaks
Discord you guys are fucking freaks. Oh, there's you move on discord
I'm Tony JT and God shut the fuck up you guys are the biggest losers on YouTube
What does it make you?
Yeah, why are you talking about gays stuff all the time? That's weird
Shit we're getting dropped fuck you got to respect the gay sometimes. Oh fuck
So how to rain for me that dumb bitch the fuck you talking about
Hey, Tony talking about your mother rain. Hey, Tony. Yo, Tony. Hey, Tony
This corporate gate said a ring
You realize I don't know who the fuck Tony is right
You realize it's you right you threw a buck
You've been saying you're not that smart, bro. You're not that good of a liar
Understand. I am the master liar. You can't live that well, Tony
Shut the fuck up. You're playing yourself. You're making yourself look like an idiot, Tony. Shut the fuck up
It's over
Alex awesome real shit be quiet. Yeah. Hey McWeef
That'd be quiet, bro
You're fucking cute stupid even know who you made the argument against I'm gonna burn your ass up be quiet
You better be quiet, you know what's gonna happen Tony calm the fuck down bro
Yeah, call me Tony one time
Your Tony your name is Tony
You are ghost AMC. You are the guy that tried to strike like his panel 15 times and he was
You're insane. You go around as ghost crucible. Your name is Tony. You're a fat fuck
That is blind and nice to the trains Tony. Shut the fuck up
No Tony, shut up, bro
Chose your tree collection you fat fuck shows your badness you fat freak
You can't even open your eyeballs without talking you close your eyeballs your blind conductor fucking piece of shit
You failed you failed your gum is you failed Tony you didn't bring psyche down
I know how much you hate gay people and taricards, but you failed motherfucker
the fact that you even
No, right? Yeah, shut the fuck up all you motherfuckers
This is
We don't we don't have access to that shit, bro. I like master computer you
Know what I don't want gay privileges
Can you leave those to Alex? No, no, I'm not not gay privileges, but I would like psyche to mute him for a second
This Alex guy man, he keeps putting you down and I don't know why and
Fucking it's weird that fucking we get kicked all of us get kicked over this gay privilege
Strange man for me. That's strange
If I'm not gonna tell anybody who like or how to run this shit, but gay
How's this how's this for an idea you get a life privilege and don't worry about what side you go with this panel
You like a little bitch you like a little girl
Like why did I get good because I like said this
Get a life motherfucker
Yeah, so Alex and psych have something going on obviously in real life, but um, don't don't don't don't take it out on us
right yeah
I mean that's apparent
it's like musical pairs with the piano like
oh punch what pair with the bass
what's happening
I mean oh dude
that was in real life
like
wow yeah wow that lasted so long
you speak
you speak so far
No, I was two seconds. I'm right back. What a dick
You're on a gay guys panel crying about Alex McQueen
That's fucking insane. I'm the king. I am the king that I can actually have men
throughout the country
Crying right now on the panel about me
I'm not I run your mind. I control your mind from where I am privilege. Okay
I'm in your head
If you don't like what you're hearing you can leave
that's what makes me crazy
you keep bitching all night
you don't have to be here and listen to me
you can go to another panel
you can hit the X
but you don't come up until psyche
oh this is lame
I'm not a sick enough sick motherfucker
you listen to me
if you don't like it leave
come back tomorrow when I'm not here
come back when I'm not here
I'm here now
if you don't like it leave
I would fucking boot your fucking neck.
You understand that?
I mean that.
I really mean that.
You better shut up.
No fuck up.
Goofy, goofy.
I just don't know what he's been bitching about all night.
But you say a lot of shit, but nothing's really it's what it's just words. It doesn't really mean anything
So leave it so if you don't like what I'm saying get the fuck out of here
I don't know what I'm not here
Come back when I'm not here stop bitching like a little girl stop bitching like a little bitch ass nigga
You're bitching come back. You can hit the X if you don't like what I'm saying right now
You don't have to listen to it, but you keep you want to be here. Does anybody want to suck my dick?
Rhonda, you know what he's talking about
He's scared of the heat, he's scared of the heat right now.
You can need the axe and come back tomorrow, but I'm here right now, and Saiki's not going to kick me.
so if you don't like what i'm saying come back when i'm not here you understand i'm not here 24
seven bro i'm not here 24 seven but i'm here right now so you're not gonna tell psyche get rid
of him because we don't like what he's saying that's not gonna happen psyche's not gonna kick me
because you say you don't like what i'm saying okay so if you don't like what i'm saying come back
You have the option to leave bro. He didn't kick you. He didn't kick you dumb dumb gay privilege. I'm talking about it
You've got the option to leave motherfucker if you don't like what I have to say
I'm a dick the fuck up
So good dick can get out of here come back tomorrow when I'm not here, bro
Oh my god, the fuck are you talking about always gonna make it 45-3?
Who the fuck was it
He was about to let a firework on his dick do wonder a day Alex. I'm back by the way good for you
This stupid fuck. Hold on. Let me crash out full screen. I'm playing with a flashlight full screen
Put it in reverse Terry
That's weird, okay
Johnson
That's Nick Johnson the fucking freak. Yeah, I couldn't read this. All right. This stuff is getting weird
Yeah
I kind of want to see it too, yeah
This would be good
He's gonna blow himself up
I know, I'm waiting on it
you
You guys are crippled old man
Bunch of crippled old freaks bro talking shit on a gay guys panel. Get the fuck out of here
By that bitch dog you fat fuck you can't even get out of your bed you fat motherfucker shut up with that
Let's run it. Let's run it ghost. Like I didn't see who you are. You're some fat loser
No, you don't have a girl you don't have a life you had nothing and you're fat
You're fat on top of it. You're fucked. You're fucking fat.
What the logic?
which basically means no woman will ever touch you
Alex we need him to shut up
Everybody's getting kicked except Alex. That's what's happening
Yeah
Between the legs, oh now he's about the light the thing oh shit
Oh
That is fucking retarded
Let me crazy
This guy thinks we cool
In New Jersey stay turned cuz I don't have to fucking put you six feet on the moon man
Fuck up you gave fucks crippled men
Yo Tony come down there Tony. Why don't you strike psyche again?
Tell you know how to do
Why don't I strike your mom again? How'd you like that last time I did that?
That was hilarious that was hilarious that was so look look this is Alex right here
And like headbutt it
You stay there straight
He goes back in frame
Look look showing off in the camera
Yeah
Nick Johnson's date
It's like a 1970s one. Yeah. Yeah. I guess. I mean, I know a 70 year old like my uncle.
He likes to smoke through at that same exact pipe right there. Straight. It's like metal.
You could stick it off in like three pieces. The chimney comes on. Yeah. You get the screens
from the sink sometimes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You got a bottom. Yeah. Yeah. But he don't
even use them on boo. He puts a bar right in there and just smokes it just like that
A lot of times he don't need he don't even use a screen. He barely never never use a screen
What's this America did we read we read doing what the fuck is going on here 38 30 for
Okay, I see a marijuana leaf without me. Okay. He's selling weed on side of the street. Is that what he's doing?
And even if he is if that's a a flight dude
You go into the wrong place on terror reading. Oh
Look at that show you oh, so you get weed and it's
And you pay that for a day if you heard that's how they get you
Yo, there's a $38 $38 50 for a terror reading and you got a marijuana sign like what is this and you proud
Yeah, you probably get one eight for that
I couldn't tell if you were selling weed or what what you were doing and it sounds like both
I think he was on something that's a weed in a terror reading 3850 or maybe I smoke
Maybe maybe maybe like they spark you up in here. You smoke with okay. Yeah, maybe just a little hit a couple hits
But I really think it is you get you buy your 8th and you get a terrible reading and it's 3850
So you probably end up leaving $40 and basically they just got paid an 8th for $40 just to sit there in
Pretending with through some cards and talk shit to you real quick for five ten minutes
They win regardless even if it's
For 3850, I better get more than a tower reading
Yeah, I got a free one from my what's her name?
Nobody has a cock up here everyone's gay
That's crazy, man. You guys got to tell me shit like this of rondo
Don't just come up here and be like you Alex. What's up?
Just be like you on my cock sucker for now
Tony you are Tony
What was it your Tony by the way? Oh, two Tony's. Yeah, that's exactly
Yep, there you go
Ghost and Rondo or Tony and whatever they do right now is what they do with the little voice boxes and the little machines
That they buy from Best Buy
You know they go to Best Buy and buy little voice boxes
But this is Tony both of them your site
This is Tony the freak little choo choo train boy that shocked you 15 times
It's both of these people
What you're gonna tell me it's not by your little daddy fucking your little daddy
All right, they told me daddy's gonna make more go Alan master computer
Go make a short of me. Go make a short of me saying I like stocks my dick. How about that?
How about that?
How about Tony sucks
How about that for sure
I'm gonna make a whole channel dedicated to our master computer way out the California from fucking New York
I'm gonna expose our master computer a key Tony both the USOs
I'm gonna battle dedicated to both of you weird relationship you guys got
No, right there Tony
All right
Well right there Tony
What did Tony?
We're
Sir
Shut your bitch. Yes, so I like master your little bitch on the computer you shut nothing up
You can't shut nothing up. You can't even shut sight of you strike the strike and 50 times are you lost?
He's still standing. That's your daddy. I told you you were not taking him down
Standing
24-7
Tony doesn't that hurt motherfucker with simp and so hard dude shut the fuck up quick
quit suckin' his pixel hard
quit tryin' to take him down so hard
uh, you're an NYPD cent, motherfucker
you can't take nothing down
shut up
you- I'm big, I'm a master, I'm big Tony
you can't take nothing down
you could do nothing, bro
you hit a- you hit a button and you're boom-boom
boom-boom, I struck your channel
with lies
you are nothing
you're nothing you remember when you look in the mirror right now bro go and say
I'm nothing I can't do nothing I can't even take psyche down I missed a big
takedown paddle boy and I can't take nothing you can't do shit with your
little computers in front of you you got three screens in front of you and you
can't take with it
fucking retort
You got AI programming you got AI programming three screens and you can't do nothing with it
Nothing, but you're cool
That's it. You just call from the panel. You can't do shit
You got no power at all over nobody
You said it one of ten screens like I'm at like master computer and all you could do is jerk off in your own pants motherfucker
You can't do shit to nobody
The technology or screens or whatever you think you have you two boy you can't do shit for nobody
Yeah, nothing god. That's you got you got me pinned doesn't that kill you bro?
Doesn't that hurt you so bad cuz I know how you think Tony
Tony you you think you're like the god of you to
Anyone I'm pony, but in reality you're nothing your piece of garbage that can't be shit and it's been proven
Sike he proved it. I proved it. That's what means like he proved it. You're nothing
You're nothing. You couldn't shit by another screen by another program keep trying and you're still
You're nothing mother fucker remember that my guy
Shit oh shit
No, you're nothing you're right
There you go, okay
You're nothing
You never were anything in the first place, so you can't be something when you were never anything you understand
You just something crap it old man
It's mine
Thank you
You got power YouTube cuz you got two fucking computer screens and no side of poem bomb
Get a life bro get the fuck out of my face before I kick your door in with a SWAT team shut the fuck up
I'll go to your house right now with a SWAT team
Keep it up keep it up
McQueen you don't even have a gun you probably not a shooter gun you live in fucking New York City
Shut you shut the fuck up so you're you're front and that you're NYPD
Okay, your state doesn't allow you to fucking own firearms
You have no freedoms you have no freedoms at all fucking retarded
Was this
What the fuck is this?
What the fuck is going on?
You turned your camera on, dude.
No, do you want to see that?
Oh, wow.
That hand.
Let me see the inside of your hands.
Yep, no calluses you lack life experience
Little bitch put your little bitch hands, dude dirty
No, you don't do you got dirty pudgy little bitch hands
Oh
You sounded gay when you said that too
I mean fuck man. What are we doing there?
Look my little pudgy fingers made out split
Hey, you got scared
Yeah, hey read his palms psyche what do they say pull those up again
Your hands up again. Let's see what they say
Well everyone left
Wow, hold on. Let me take the comments. You hear me. Hold on German lady. I'm driven to
Goes to the back. Oh, why'd you leave girls? Where were you? Where'd you go?
Hi, so I know some we talk all night tonight. Oh
It is hi, how are you?
I hear you okay good
Did you see my I turned my camera on did you see it?
Yeah, I thought it was that
Why round those God
all of the
Oh, yeah, so was that like so you have lights like do you make a like a light pattern in the shape of a dick or something?
What happened? This is my this is my man cave
What is it?
My bullets are just a man cave not just put my middle finger up. This is my man. Oh, oh, okay your man. Oh cool
It's more lights in there. I need some more lights on my show. How are you this?
Why do if I turn those off I have the black pipes going
Cool. Hey, we're floating to the sky. I'm doing very good. Thank you for your question. But yeah, I have my black lights going
Yeah
How's your how's your month going?
We're gonna summer solstice recently. Let me ask you how are you? What are you doing for tomorrow, brother?
I'm gonna get in my speedo and I'm gonna
Probably take it. No, it gives Ron can take a shower on stream and fall asleep. No fireworks
I don't have me. I have fireworks. Um, the media watch them
I know the company I see them from my window that they can see them in the window because they come
They're on the boats and the pier is like at least go outside and experience. I'm a little bit. I see that
Oh my god, he's so close. I live close to the pier, uh, or
Yeah
Crystal
Hey, you just call me Alex. No, I'm talking with you, but you did discover. No, it's good
But you gotta go outside and experience them brother
I mean I do I mean I go I mean it's like but you might have my windows and you see them perfectly
That's like it's like really close
I mean, I know I like fireworks, but it's like they're yeah, I can see them perfectly now the coward has my chat
Like firework when I shoot them off
Anybody else to shoot them off like fucking like like I get PTSD from that shit
My brother, you know, I'm expecting it, you know, I
Think one of my brothers used to go we used to go to Mexico and he's part of our art
And so that my brother would go like he just like get his own cab and you come back like you know
A few hours later, I think he probably had some cocaine he'd take the guy would take him to we also go to the fireworks
and he got these professional fireworks and
These fireworks
We're like, you know professional quality and they're thinking they have these little cannons
They shot out of like one was like a hundred dollars. I think and it was like this or maybe I think it's been over hundred dollars
They've been a couple hundred dollars. I think they're expensive
But yeah, they gave our family a little show that went down to the beach. So
that off the fireworks and
Yeah, you still have a lot of fun in Mexico. Yeah, I think it'll be I think it'll be good
We usually a lot off a little show, but it's here in like suburbs and shit, but everybody neighbors everybody gathered around
every year
Cool little block party
Yeah, I guess you could say that yeah
cool
Let's see Brian King is no okay
I don't know about that. Let's see Larvae there. Hey, what's that what happens to their panels?
They all left they left in their own court. I didn't kick it over from the studio
I
Joined back
Yeah, I was like I kind of like was experimenting with a different energies or if I like, you know
But it's usually a sub no no no no I'm saying that's why I was like
Why I'm big Leo your big Leo energy
Yeah, you get the sun. I'm not lying
Yeah, yes, sir. That's good. Well, there's a lot of you know
I think the only one that could as the bigger one is like Aries because like that's like the god of war
You know right the areas is the God of war but in ancient Greece areas
Aries is from ancient Greece Aries was kind of like not really liked among the gods
He was kind of like he had a bad temper and he was like, you know, he's all about this
Yeah, but Athena was also a goddess of war and Athena was the goddess of wisdom
Or the hearth no
Oh the hunt that's Artemis Artemis is the goddess of the hunt
What do you say? Oh, you said Athena on my back. Yeah, Athena Athena's a goddess of wisdom
But she's also the goddess of like warfare, but she's like the goddess of like strategy
Wonder Woman like the movies we comics to but
Member in the movies she would end up being the God killer and it wasn't yeah, it was actually her
Right, it was like well the thing is cool, but like wonder what nobody even knew about that
Wonder woman's I could shoot the first of all. She's like, uh, you know
You know Jews have a good thing with like super here. I mean, it's like, you know, a lot of people too, but
Yeah, super man
What a woman she was I think even like whoever played Wonder Woman. I think she was Jewish or you know
Superwoman was his cousin, but wonder wonder woman was just Amazon. You know, yeah, she's an Amazon
Yeah, okay, and so yeah wonder woman. I think she was it's probably a Jewish like you know, Ashkenazi
God goddess or whatever
You know she could but you know more for the women's you've been meant to fantasize about and
It's like I think we should plan it out
I think we should watch out the new Superman that's coming out together. Oh
You don't come come because much on stream. Oh on stream. You don't fly out
You don't fly out see me and spend a couple nights with me
Do I do you think I want to fly out?
Yeah, you do I
Probably brother brother we can
We're gonna know I'm like that because yeah, okay, we can watch it we can watch it we both like comics
We both we both are all that shit. I like I like I mean I like comics and I went but I was like
You know there's people that were more into they more into them or more into the message. I just I just kind of like
Well, I don't know. I'm just saying because you're a tear you're a terror reading scientist. Yeah, I just I mean I like I'm
I like yeah, I like I like like Batman and cat like some of the Batman cartoons
They're like, you know, that's kind of like they're like gonna like spend a little bit of those young but who does
Who talks to or helps whenever I can have a deck that was like
DC your
Marvel and I could do the same shit though
You know I'm saying right well you can make your own comic company or say or create your characters or like what is they?
I mean basically my own card deck my own card deck. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Sure. You can't yeah
Oh, you guys if you want you get anybody can keep their own party. We get along cuz you agree
No, I agree because it's true. I mean, there's oh, Amanda's here. Let's have Amanda. Hello
How are you? Yeah, how are you tonight? Oh good you were talking about
I'm sorry, Leo's so
I'm a Libra. Are you a Leo? I'm a Libra. Libra, okay. And I don't have any gods or goddesses to my knowledge.
Tell me if I do, Scythe. You are Libra. Yeah, Libra is Ma. Yeah, it's a case of scales, and it's like for the Egyptian goddess Ma'at, and she's the goddess of truth.
And like I say, when you die, you go to this room.
And they have a scale there and they put one heart wasn't it a scale they put your heart and
They put a feather and if your heart weighs less than a feather
Then you can go to the afterlife if it doesn't they kind of like the three or just some kind of crocodile being but uh
That's ma ma but I also think I'm balanced and I think you know
You know I think you have femus kind of which is like the Greek goddess of justice be her name is femus
and she's a you know they have
There's archetypes. There's also archetypal justice. They'd be you know people like Athena with the wisdom and balance and things like that
But yeah, Libra. Yeah, Libra. They're very they're always wanting everything to be fair
They're always wanting to measure everything to make it sort of the perfect like the perfect feeling of her that always
Well, you know
An air sign and so they can be sharp with their words, right? They can be and they can be
But they are kind of sharp. Yeah
Yeah, what was that goddess you were saying? Her name is Ma. So it's ma apostrophe at I think that's how you spell it
I'll look it up because yeah, and they have like these like
They have this before you died. It's like you see it. You there's like these like the how many
I don't know if it's 48 or 58 or something
I think but it's the laws of law and the earth's these statements of my and you say instead of saying
Yeah, but there's the laws of my I think there's 48 and it's like the Mott says like, you know, it's like I
instead of saying I
Confessing things you say we do not do so you're supposed to say I did not kill I did not harm I did not hurt anybody
I don't suppose that you're supposed to say all those
In like the net kind of the negative instead of like the affirmative like you're supposed so that's you can read the laws
But there's a lot of different ones, but it's kind of a pretty good moral code to live by it's very it's very positive
I would say they're very expert in the
afterlife like into the Egypt ghosts or not
Why do you just make a horse sound?
Well, I was expecting these boys. I always turn up over here. That's what I was expecting
Hmm. I'm gonna look I'm gonna look up equivalent goddesses. Let's see if there's an equivalent
I mean, they're usually an equivalent goddess. There's you know, she's like from Egypt, which you know, they've spent
You know, they love God things. That's fair. That's like
Prisius. Well, Zeus came down
Like for you
Yeah, well, I mean, it's like most of the Roman gods were just basically the copies of the of the
Because they added then they had the planet's name. I mean, they or they made that the planet's names eventually and
You know, but I was saying about areas the planets are the goddess
Well, I think probably that's well the plans came first but oh so and it says like it says mod or the Greek goddess theme is like I said
I think those are the two
Strongest justice. Yeah, so yeah, so it's also theme is his T. H. E. M. I. S. The mess theme is so Brian's also the ebra
Yeah, so, you know the person air sign air signs are taking different Gemini and the Quares are air signs
So the sword is also there. It's like swords or words. There's also the sword on the sword
The sword if you live by the sword psyche, what do you have to do?
Die by the sword but the swords are double-edged too and they also they also cut through
Right they cut they cut through things that's the thing but also they're kind of like words
Swords is just words with that get S on the front of it, right?
And the words can cut like swords and like, you know, they can speak the truth
They can be like a sword. I think there's people that should be put to death
But that's not murder
Well, what do you know? How do you mean like who should be put to death and what people would be?
Yeah, I got I got yeah, I got yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not trying to break you last but like no, I
Put him to the sword
Alright
No fuck all that well, yeah, that's a good argument though like they should be able to get like because there's no death
Some of these should be like as long as you can live you should be in prison me. I'm like, I'll cut their fucking head off
That's a good argument though. That's a good argument though. I do understand that though because you should suffer in prison
The gipsies believed in a death judgment eternity
So death they believe in sacrificing
Shut up and listen to this life
The life of the last invaders from the journey from the tomb to the underworld.
We open a womb to this tomb.
The car or the life force.
The car or the body.
Yeah, when you guys shut up, I'll read you what it is, alright?
when you puny little minded humans can shut the fuck up and listen to this
i'll talk shut up start reading i guess he says life everlasting begins with a journey
from the tomb through the underworld the car or life force leaves the body first followed
after burial by the bar or soul the falcon headed god Horace leads the bar through doorways of fire
then come judgment. The jackal, headed God Anubis, weighs the deceased's heart,
side of conscious, against a feather of mat, M-A-A-T, or things as they should be,
Osiris king of the underworld, and other gods watch as judges. If the heart is too heavy or too
You're missing three letters to a perpetual coma, it's a
If the hard balance is the winged bob
You'll fat boy shut up
show up because i'm not done if the hard balance is the winged bar you're such a moron bro
he's got the guy that's got his body the hard balance is the winged bar and the car
we unite to form the arc or spirit
Which emerges in the bright room?
Yo, Alex, they could have been your ancestors
They could have been anybody's ancestors any one of us
Well, that was she was the beautiful that picture you showed. Yeah, and there's like a little pictures of like her with the scale
I'll show you because she is like a very Libran like with a just
Also the justice tarot card
Free will
Me and her would have we would definitely have a good one night me and her would definitely have a good one night
I can read all of a sudden like I can't pull it. I mean you're you're taking against my free will
So they have like 42 there's 42 negative confessions. I'll just read a few. There's like I have not committed sin
I have not committed robbery with violence. I have not stolen. I have not slain men or women
I have not stolen food. I have not swindled offerings. I have not stolen from the God or goddess
So there's a few of the deal. There's 42 of them. Yeah, you should read the 42
It's called the 42 ideals of Mott and they're negative there's a confession, but they're in a negative saying you have not done them
Okay
I'll look it up. I'll look it up.
Egyptian is fast. I'm talking to
I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to
I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda. I'm talking to Amanda.
Yeah, well, it's like, you know also Horace, you know Horace as like the son of
Isis on Osiris and the story of Osiris's death is really interesting his half-brother
Like basically at a party was like, oh, you can't fit into this box
He's like, I bet I can and he got into the box and they sealed it up and like, you know threw it into some like
I know
13 bars, are you okay?
I'm talking to you fast or what?
What? No, I'm talking to her. Is she okay? Oh
No, you're good. You're good. Oh, so you okay over him. So yeah
So um, so anyway, like, you know, like I said, this was his wife and she went and she went to like look for his body
He was cut up into like
I think like 13 pieces in like the
She found every piece except for his penis. That was eaten by a croc about it.
Oh, the whole piece is burnt. That's crazy.
She won't find that but she found all the rest of his body.
She found all the rest of his body, put it back together, and then she put her on.
She made kind of a strap on her.
I don't know, she put her fake on his body.
She shoved something on it with out of wood and then she had sex and with the body and then she was able to like make a baby out of that as Horace
And a Horace
You heard
Wow, well, she did she did she was magical when there's those stories about isis that are really interesting isis is like, you know
Isis is like a
Powerful god
Well, you know, you can believe in magic or not, but I think life is magical. I think just even that's talking tonight
I believe in magic and McDonald's too. I love you
I don't know. Hey, let's do some cards. Who wants a reading? I have a few readings for the panel. If you know anyone else in the chat
I don't want to read you from page
Page is not here if you go to page's channel subscribe and then I think she's doing more readings on her panel now
Or just when she's on my loader and get yourself a reading. Yeah. Yeah
It's like who type in prairie page the rest of come on
Very page
Pre-paged spiritual arts or something like that very page and wisdom spiritual arts. Okay, you know the wind beneath my cities or something like that
Winds and spiritual very pretty wins. Okay, so Amanda a ghost or stay turn who wants to
Okay, let's go. Let's go. Let's go first. Okay. What kind of card reading is it?
This is the villains. It's the villains. We shut up and let them do a thing.
The villains.
It's villains from different Disney movies.
Okay, so here's your here's your reading goes.
Okay, what do we got? Okay. Oh, okay. Okay, so we got the seven of coins. Okay, so this is like, you know
coming into you've come into some money and you they can be generous you know you
can afford to be generous but it's like this is really things I've been going
okay well okay I'll read I'll read I mean I'll read the car but that's my
interpretation part of the reading it's like okay well it says from the
seven of coins it says it says you have faced a long or it says you have a
Obviously, okay. Okay. You have an exciting
Long-word ahead of you and are working are working hard
to
With yourself for success the seven of coins advises you to make decisions
With the long term in mind careful planning
We'll be to longer rewards in the future. Okay. Yeah, so it's like, you know, just to find you have something
You have the start of something good you have this like luck on your side
It's me something that makes you happy. I think and so I think go with this
Okay, oh and you want many of the six the coins to and that's I did shuffle the deck pretty well
So it's crazy if he is six of coins. Okay. Also, this is like the six of coins is a generosity card
This is also like, you know, you're gonna it looks like you're gonna
Makes the more money and so it's like but it's saying be generous with it
Like be a gift gives it the people that deserve it like if you give you know find out who do you think deserves it?
You know you way that I'll read you the six of coins the six of coins says
With that what says wall of sharing with others may not be a
At the top of your every villain's priority list and so the coin asked you to be very generous
You've been very successful lately, but you didn't accomplish all of your all of your goals alone
It is time to throw your appreciation or trigger appreciation those have helped you along the way and
And give to those
Less fortunate. Okay. And so that's saying, you know, it looks like
Good stuff having with the money for you. Okay. Now you have the ace of cups and so this is like the start of something
So this is a future card. This ace of cups is saying this is like the start of something that can be really big
There's also there could be love in the future because of this there could be
You know, you want to share that coming your girl were flowing basically with love and you've also had you know
Yeah, it's like a w the blood of W. I think yeah, there's like a there's like a win you've had a win
Here's the advice. Oh, I'll read that for you to ace of cups
Ace of Cups, you know, it's like something handed to you that's gonna make you very can make you very happy
You know, it's just a start of something
Okay, the Ace of Cups says Ace of Cups presents new friendships and love interests someone special will be
It's an entry in the picture soon whether the person ends up being your true love or great new friend
Trust that things are unfolding for you as they should.
Enjoy the moment and go with the flow.
Okay, so here's your advice.
Okay, your advice is the high priestess.
Okay, so this is the high priestess.
I don't think this is the first one.
This is Maleficent, okay?
She's a little bit of an evil intuition,
but you know, I want you to use your intuition
for the best, but the high priestess,
it means you know more than you think you know.
You already have the answers inside, you know, go inside.
So the high priestess is secretive.
Intuitive figure whose power comes from deep within her own self-conscious, like Maleficent,
due to the sophisticated calculating and a magical force to be reckoned with,
the High Priestess is a call to look deeper. You may not be seeing a situation, friendship,
or relationship in your life for what it really is.
What is your intuition telling you? Take inspiration from the serious Maleficent and embrace
solitude to ruminate on the predicament
Consider it carefully for there is more going on the meets the eye. I hope you like that. Okay. I'm sorry
Okay, so so say it goes left goes how rude I was doing the middle reading for you goes
But I hope you heard that okay stay turn Amanda you guys here
Hello, there won't go what happened?
I'm muted
Okay, go see you see that in the chat. Are you right? Hold on. I was the others were have fun in hell
Okay. Anyway, I hope you guys like that region. Let me see how I want to say
All the old odd was sucks. They turned Amanda. Are you there?
Yes
Okay, do you want to do a reading now doing a reading is Alice left and I'm matter of fact
I'm smoking right now. So I'm okay. I'll go on pause and I'll take a reading. Okay. Okay. Good. All right. Thank you
Okay, tell me when good
Yeah, you go for yours. Okay. Okay. I'll do I'll do everything. Okay. I'll do a few cards for you
Okay
Okay, so for state turn, what do I got?
Okay, state turn, okay, state turn, you have this dark card right here, okay, this dark
Wow, it's like, you've got a lot of stuff going on.
You're being told the truth, you're seeing the truth.
You're being given some information.
You're really inspired.
Also, the stars, like I always say, make a wish.
You know, you make a wish on a star.
You are a star.
You're being extra magnetic at this time.
You've been coming through this thing.
Very magnetic.
Okay, I'll read for you too.
Okay, so the star says, the star is number 17.
The star says,
Just as the Queen's magic mirror always responds honestly to any question asked, the star represents
clarity, hope, and the power of truth.
The star indicates you're coming out of a period of confusion and uncertainty.
While this chapter in life may have been difficult, it is the guiding light later to illuminate
So you may not have the magic mirror at your disposal.
The tarot card encourages you to pursue
and then embrace the truth, okay?
Then we have the four of swords, okay?
Four of swords, I would say,
is like, you know, there's been some kind of hurt
you're wanting to avenge.
It says four of swords, you've been through a hard battle.
Here's the scar to it. So it's it's a scar. It's a scar
It says you've been through a hard battle and now is the time for a much needed
Rest and relaxation
put up your feet and preamble yourself you may want to recharge in order to prepare for the
Adventures ahead and for the adventures ahead. I feel okay. I'm gonna pull one more right
Okay, okay
Okay, we have a tower like tower moments are never fun
But this I like this car because this is like it shows the spiritual side to it
So there's that long glowing hair in the tower. There's a way so it's like maybe you feel trapped in some way
And this is like saying there's like a way. There's a way down. It's like this like magical
Unconventional method, maybe okay, I think I see I see the spiritual car and sometimes it translates in the earthly realm to
upheaval and you know things
a big shocking event happening really fast,
but not necessarily bad,
but usually something that clears out the way
for better things.
It says,
the mother Gothel keeps Rapunzel locked in a tall tower
under false pretenses,
helping her telling Rapunzel that it's her own,
for her own good.
The tower represents the sadism
and dramatic distraction of such illusions and façades.
Says when this tower is drawn from his hair reading you're gonna make a big shift in your life because
the
because this card heralds some kind of collapse that you may feel blindsided by a
new revelation
That has you questioning the very foundation of what you thought to be true
Not all is ultimately lost the moment will have you
And then embrace the chaos and then you'll come out unscathed. Okay, so it could be just released
But I also see you may be feeling okay, so the advice is like
It's like the five of corns. This is like device is to I would say
to ask for help ask for help to don't and it's like don't feel discouraged from
Not knowing everything at once or not being you know, it's like you're there's so much time to learn
But yeah, I would say make sure you don't feel left out because I see you moving forward very successfully
Like this is like your full speed ahead. It's like all your foot
So it might be pure stagnation and like the tower might have an effect, but it's like you're gonna come out of it like really fast
I
Can read you the chariot chariot number seven and the chariot says
It says the chair represents determination, unrelenting focus, and the willpower.
much like the formidable, fashion-loving, correlative girl who is who there isn't
anything that will stop her from doing what she wants, not even a car chase in
the snow, says obstacles won't won't space you now, you're in hot pursuit of
your goal and nothing will stand in your way for long. Don't get yourself
distracted, what you want may seem out of reach now, but
Putting your pedal to the metal will give you the last little boost you need to take sleep. So I hope you like that
there's like a
I don't know if we heard it, but you can go rewind if you didn't hear it all but awesome just smoking up some weed
How's everyone in the chat? I know I'm sorry
Was it good was it good you like it or hopefully like yeah, I heard okay good
Yeah, move forward
Don't and and even if you feel left out, I would say like you can do your own thing
You know you all think about being like, you know, you're the CEO instead of like, you know
Just on the team like you want to be the leader or something like that
So don't be afraid
Yeah, so I'll put it back on there we go just just the two of us
You can make if we chat. Okay
tend to put up an error. Let's see. I don't okay in the chat. It's the
Other talk about some interesting things. I have no idea what they're talking about. So anyway
Yeah, we're at the word is happy 4th of July America and the rest of the world
Even if you're not American we can all have a drink together at least
Let some fireworks. Let's unite under the
Now what's he say do an ancient psyche and I'll be up on the panel up guys
You know, it's uh, you know, it's a sponsor school of Athens. I
Do have a cash app you can
Or if you'd like to send super chat or
But that's his request, you know, he's always welcome here, I think that will work
Yeah
Come up here if you got a minute
Yeah, do you have a do you have a channel stay turn or not? Are you like are you? No? No? No? No? No? I just
Oh, hold on
I thought I left it. Um
No, no channel. I just I come up here
Have a conversation. That's it, you know, okay?
Well, yeah
I
So yeah, I've been doing YouTube since like I've probably had my channel for about a year probably been
My last years last October and it panels for in modding for a few months before that
Yeah, I know I know I remember when you used to come over to TPP
Yeah, why don't you tell me you live in your car this guy lives in his car? Oh, yeah, um, oh
Psychic just so you know, I I guess I live in my car now
I don't care. I don't care, but like, you know, that's like, it's
I don't know
This guy has a ponytail
From his head to his the ground. It's the weirdest thing I've ever seen. That's cool. Yeah, it's weird
Bro, he says something about his car
Do you think he has a ponytail? This one, fuck, it makes it easy
It looks like a fucking, uh, like, yo, you
Like you got cancer, like he has cancer, yes, I know
Yeah, I was gonna say like you're like he said something about oh
Whatever, but I mean the last car I pulled that's the chariot the chariot
It's here is her driving in a car
I would say it kind of to me like wherever it is even if you feel like you're done
But where you want to be or if you feel like in a state of lack
It's like it's a it's just driving away from that and driving to your success. I really see that okay
So Alex you better be quiet as you're talking over. I was trying to explain to them real quick. So
Yeah, all right man, I didn't know you were talking. He's been quite
Just come up for him
He was very good looking I hit on him. He said don't hit on me
the
Yo, we was in the back, we was in the back, we was in the back, I can tell you, everyone was trippin'
This motherfucker stripped down to his underwear in his car on a panel for like a half hour
Okay, I was strippin' like what's he doing?
He's lying
Did you guys have to stay turned?
No, there was a lot of people that saw that no matter of fact you said you got the
Stupid dino
On his chest on his arm as a dino from the flinch stones because his name is dino
That's his first name. So he has dino from the flinch stones
So you need doxin right now you are
Yeah, I am toxic, what do you know?
So don't ever call me a liar, motherfucker.
Hey, yo, Saki, he's admitted to it.
That's crazy.
Huh?
Sure.
You want to let him do that, that's great.
No, no, no, not with you.
What do you say?
Because instead of you have a dinosaur tattoo of D,
I mean, that's not dead.
No, he's saying like, oh, I got this such and such tattoo.
And it has a name on it, but that's my real name in real life.
Okay, you're supposed to say real names, but yeah, if you know that that's what he's trying to say
Like he's trying to say what my real name is because of a certain tattoo like yes
Okay, Alex don't say that again. Okay. He doesn't want to be doxxed. Okay. I'll say it again
I mean, you can say whatever. Hey, I won't say it again. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
So I could do the same thing to you, but I would never do it. I know your real name
The psyche don't worry. I'm not gonna do it. I'm not psyche. I'm not gonna do it
Dave I know you won't
I'm Sam
You got family members
No, you're in the car for a reason, but I know you're in that car for a reason. Yeah, I'll let you know
I know everybody in your life, so watch your mouth
I'm not worried about you
There's a I got a I got a decent list, but like you're not on it
you have a list huh
Hey, Alexander if you donate a gift membership to somebody out on the school of Athens will hop on the panel
Wish me
Why him never didn't know what he never he never did no home to nobody
You're more pussy than he is bro. So shut up. Hey
You're crazy. Come on. You're crazy. Well, I never like start a fuck up
He's pussy and you know
How about that?
You're one
Know what hang you with that ponytail in front of your mom. No, you know what listen
I would love for you to come here. I would grab you give you a hug and buy you a beer. I
Promise you Alex
Shit, I went man listen
You ever came over here. I'll give you a hug and buy you a couple of beers. We'll sit down and hang out
Okay, congratulations, HK Memphisheh, HK Memphisheh, one, one, the membership.
Wait, so you get the whole set?
Yeah, I give to the, I just give to the membership.
Oh, okay, oh, okay, guys, you know, yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
HK Memphisheh is like an awesome person in my chat, also a mod.
Congratulations, you got a membership.
Hey, what's up, Easy?
Hello?
who's that he's he's say he's say
I donated so he um
Okay
You want school?
No, I said he's not gonna donate just had a spite so it's like I just did it myself
The fight anything in the first name. I also need I'll donate tomorrow when one Saturday
Yeah, you mean no today's Friday. No Friday
Today's Friday the fall. Yeah, I know
Right, right. Okay got you
So
Yo, um Alex, what are you doing today? You're going to
I just want to make one statement. Can you put you want to see the fireworks?
One second guys, I'll be back. I'll be back. Okay. What's up easy? Yeah, I just want to know. Um, did you buy that deck with the $18 or not?
I will I will today. I will today
Yeah, if you didn't if you didn't block if you didn't buy it yet take that 18 and block stay till right now
And I'm gonna give you more
Okay
Don't worry. Hey 18 19 20 21 2 3 2 4 5 7 more dollars won't hurt
Okay, block that nigga right now. I want him gone for 24 hours. Fuck that piece of shit
Stay turn you've been
Banned for 24 hours
By easy
Okay
Very good. Now go sit back and relax listen to Alex. I'm gonna listen to Alex bitch. They did half bagging
I'm sorry that asshole
No way that just happened
You just banned them for 24
Yeah, I don't want to wake up to hit his asshole then find out he's on all night. Fuck you
man, I
Couldn't even predicted that to happen
He's any got you out he's a got you out mad
school that ends 50 and because then I have to
Refund I'd refund I'd refund allegedly, but it's still like not really I don't
I don't want to greet you at this time. I don't agree to nothing. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, he owes you seven or something because it's 25. I'll put in the rest
Thank you, sir. Thank you, sir. You know, it's it is nothing person. What do you think it's part of that?
No, because he you know, he
I don't want the money back side. He don't don't take nothing. Okay. Oh, I'm bad. Okay. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, I will yeah, he will be for 24 hours until uh tomorrow
Right now, I'm gonna go take a shower and freshen up
Yes
of that was crazy
look at Athens talking shit
if I give 25 to get him on band
go ahead Athens, go ahead dude, I dare you
I don't know if this person wants to come on, if they don't want to come on then just don't say anything
but if you do want to come on
say who you are once again
say hello
hello
here's Johnny, that's Sean P
Yeah, I just missed easy up here, too. You just missed them by a hair. I know I'm tight bra. I'm tight. I just
He banned state turned
I don't know 24 hours
I don't know
a state and the Luigi
member Luigi
talking shit on that
oh bro
honestly I left because
the conversation just got dry bro
I'm like I don't want to hear that bullshit about ghosts
and I'm like it's going back and forth
I don't know man
they're crazy
they're crazy those people
I don't know what to do with them
okay we have again
the more you feed into it
the more they like love it
yo school
I had to come up as soon as you came up Sean
Yo, I love you school shout out to you
Yeah, I think so
Yo school right now my enthusiasm. I'm a little doped up right now. I'm on like spliff number four bro
Well, I want to say the last time I see you you had me in stitches, bro
You were you canned up you had the rocky outfit on I think Alex was here, too
And you were doing the punches and you were working out and shit there ever. Oh, yeah
About the fight so like I listen
I would before I wrote Alex you slipping in the mind chest because when I said I'll give 25 to unblock state turn
Obviously, I'm just trolled it and you believe me, but yeah
But I was thinking
When you were doing that and telling us you will fight and I think everybody on the panel honestly was like is he bullshit
Is he for real? So what's the deal?
Are you? I was just on the live earlier with people already. I think great
I told you I'll pull up
Right now bro just same thing like fully focused working on the fundamentals closing things up on the game plan
Cardio, bro. I've been lifting those big-ass fucking the construction dump truck tires
I've been lifting that shit across the whole
Johnson, you've been the Nick Johnson.
I gotta see that, bro.
I gotta see the construction tires being
that shit.
Nick Johnson.
I hate that shit, because you got to let
and doing it or two different things.
I want to see that shit.
No, no, diddy.
I just hate that shit, because you
know, you got to squat down and lift that shit, bro.
And that should be a pain in the ass, bro.
But bro, just nothing else. There's nothing else to really talk about bro. Just now
Just you know really make sure as they compose and focus and like execute what we have planned and of course the plan
Bees if anything, you know, I'm saying obviously like I'm expecting that there's obviously a high chance that I'm gonna get hurt
Like in between the fight, you know, I'm saying like niggas are gonna get hurt between the rounds and shit
So I really got to make sure I'm composed and don't fold under like the aggression and pressure and
Don't let my emotions got it. Yeah, your boys are gonna be there and we're gonna watch you get fucked up
Right, is that what's gonna happen for hell? No, hell. No, nah, it's just you always have to bro
Obviously, you know think about it
He's throwing hundreds of punches more than me throughout the whole fight most likely and he's coming forward
And like somebody asked me before they're like, oh what are its tendencies and shit and I know he like it's gonna be easy
Like I don't have to look for him, you know, he's going to come to me, you know what I'm saying, he's not going to be
But do you know who he is yet though? Like you're talking about somebody's strategy. Do you know the boxer?
I do but like I
Do you know Argentina? Was that a rumor or is that true? No, it's true. True. The thing is bro
We don't have a name, right? I don't I talk to easy about it
And it's like bro, if I give out the name the galoke I'm doxing myself, you know, because it's just my real name
You know what I'm saying? So like how I'm gonna avoid that is just like, bro
pull up you guys like mystery fighter like arjun yeah but what the hell exactly you gotta say
your name you're in a fight when you listen listen they're gonna obviously say it but i'm not gonna
drop no hair like whoever pulls like school when you pull up i'm just gonna like make sure like
yo you know just don't record that part you know what i'm saying just like go live so wait your
Is it even it's gonna say my whole government full government bro. That's how they know
Oh, when you become a professional boxer because you're gonna be taking a what do they call it a fair, right?
What are they? What are they called a boxing fair?
Like you get your USA boxing official for the amateurs and then for the pros
It's like a whole different paperwork
Regardless, it says your name on the it doesn't matter where you could you gonna be registered as an amateur like you don't get paid for it
No, no, they're paying they're paying for the rounds that shit. It's just right now. The only thing school bro
That's against me is I'm going against like, you know, their guy, you know, I'm saying like they
Though that was a month ago. When is the fight brother? I'm on your side, you know, I know I know I know
No, it's great now. Just couple weeks out right now. It's a shit
Fucking out of you
Imagine he like goes in there with some roundhouse elbow shit like that's
Like me like towards the end of the fight like I wanted to get like a little bit dirty where it's like obviously bro, you know fuck it
I'm talking about I don't fight dirty. I don't fight dirty, but it's a plan
But you're supposed to go down in the fourth or something. No, no, no
I'm planning like bro later on like in the fight. Obviously. I'm gonna be holding on a good punch in him
Oh, if I have to headbutt
I have to headbutt you see cuz yo cuz already the other against me, bro
So I rather just lay everything out on the line like nigga. I don't want to go home like bro getting your ass beat
Whatever you know, but going home and having the back of the things like damn
I could have done what more or cut a one-day fighter. I didn't do enough. That's what would kill me
So when I was saying you know go low and I want to tell you something in sports
And I was an athlete I played soccer in the cross in high school and then when I went to college
I just played club ball, but
You try to get away with anything you can and if you don't get caught it's not cheating
So I played left back right on a soccer field and defenders are faster than
Strikers right the people on offense because we have to mark them
So the defenders are the fastest people on the field now on a corner kick. You know what a corner kick is in
Soccer, yeah
All right, so I'm the guy in the middle
Marking the striker. He's usually the tallest guy because he's gonna try to head but it right
The fad in soccer is to wear your shirt outside your pants, right?
But I'd be wearing this shit inside my pants because when I'm behind the guy,
I'm taking my right hand, I'm turning it back side, and I'm grabbing the bottom of his jersey
and twisting it in a circle, you understand? And my two shoulders are back up against his
two shoulders. So when he tries to jump up and headbutt, I am ripping him down from the back of
So what do you think happens?
Number one, he doesn't score a goal.
We both sit on the floor.
He turns around and what do you think he does to me?
In the same thing something else
How is taking what sure be said the same thing
Every time and then if he tried to do that shit to me
Here we go. My shirt was tucked in you follow
So he's trying to grab it and he pulls the shirt out and they can see him grabbing it you follow
Oh man, I mean school for me. I had a dream a page
Listen school. Oh, I'm like, bro. I'm like fair. I'm not like, you know
I'm not a scumbag like when it comes to the fighting like bro, you know
Yo school, but that's the thing look cuz for this fight particularly like once it gets towards the end
and like you know everything settles down bro i have to do it just because already like nigga
like everything is against me bro like nigga i'm not supposed to win you know so nigga i want to
go in there and win you know so why are you not supposed to win because you're on the dog
He's like some
Alex talk now Alex because one thing that you and I have in common is the mind
You know I mean preparation of your mind when you go into a task exactly it's almost like he's only lost in his mind
Now you go explain to him what he needs to do to prepare himself well imagine you know mentally
just see yourself winning and open as and the worst thing that happens is you don't but you can't go in there already thinking that way
Like I'm gonna lose
Chance should be you gotta go in there like I'm gonna eat the fuck out of this motherfucker
Mind is half of it the body reacts to the mind
you go in there already like yeah, I know I'm supposed to lose your dad
I mean, this is gonna or you can go in there and surprise everybody like yeah, they don't know who the fucking was
chompy
That's all I want to say envision yourself with your hands open the edge open open down, right?
I cried to moments like that where I'm like damn
you know parents front row friends family haters supporters there you walk out you know
like you're in the fight tough moments you get hurt you know you come back
find the way to win like bro it's not the will into reality remember alex that video
yeah that whole i'm not
I'm not
Really willing of her it's a reality
Maybe you don't get her bro cuz you will back
Because because I'm gonna have to take more risks than
No, because because listen, there's gonna be moments in the fight, you know one bro
Somebody's gonna have to take the lead, you know, and obviously I don't want it to be a close fight because what's gonna happen?
Nigga they're gonna give it to him, you know, like duh, that's what happened
You're done. I just see you slow show in his mind about it
Yeah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah
you ever see you talking like an 80 year old like a trainer like yay I'm gonna take the loss and like you know
You're gonna get hurt you're in there like why?
No, you should be excited about what Joey like I'm gonna woof this motherfucker
Right
You rage against the machine album
You ever see the first one, the monk that sets himself on fire.
He puts the gas on me or the stream yard upgrade.
Did you got different bottom pieces now?
Hold up, Ledge.
Hold up.
Sean P.
You ever see that race against the machine album?
Which one is the first one?
It's the monk that set himself on fire and he's got gasoline on him
and then the flames all over him.
That's his mind.
He shut it off.
He didn't move an inch and he was flaming.
That's all.
Go ahead, Ledge.
No way I've never seen that. I don't know what you're talking about. I know
But there's there's Buddhist monks. There's Buddhist monks who can actually build those up. It's called self-immolation
Is this a new
Instinct combustion like just setting yourself
You know, he's got the stuff on fire, but then he's like in a meditative state basically he's meditating
Is you're the minus oh man, it's 90% of the show yo is this a new stream yard cuz he was asking if this was a new stream
I'd like cuz some box
A new setup
You can switch the cameras and the mics. I see i'm touching the waters right now
Look at the background ledge ledge. You see the background. It's
Yeah, these you'd like to made that background. That's fucking that's nice. That's nice. Yeah, easy. I know how to do that
I could do the same thing
This one
He kicks they turned
That was a surprise
No, no, fuck that officially I hate that motherfucker fuck him
Yeah, I know I saw that I saw you wrote yo school Alex. I won't let you guys down, bro
I promise you that's what you need to be saying
I'm gonna put money on the mix man. Well, that was he fighting anyways, no Russian dude. Is he why what is he?
some of the
Yeah, I guess some Argentinian psycho that already beat the shit out of ten people. This is my first like
Well, he's got to get a first motion P, right? Everybody does even Tyson. Yeah
You he shits you piece he feels pain. You just got to catch him bro. Just go for the jaw
Do the Tyson shit liver shot uppercut
Just go for the jaw and knock him out one good shot the jaw rattles the brain his knees buckle
Sean where's the fight gonna be though? What venue here in New York at the garden?
It's good dad. That's what you said last time at the garden Madison Square Garden
You're gonna fight a massive square garden. Like
Setting up something on the roof or you're saying like in the garden
No, they do they do little they do little small shits too. Like it's not a big obviously television like ESPN plus
But it's still in the garden like on the floor
I just like how it sounds because it's like, you know, yeah
It's in the hulu theater in the
garden, which holds lessons.
So now we're going to run sick,
nigga.
You ain't running shit.
They told you run that car car
gas.
Like you're trying to say.
All right.
Now we get more info from you,
Sean.
I heard that the hulu theater
you said, right?
Fuck that.
Son of a bitch.
Ass with man.
Fuck all that bullshit.
I'm going to have to look up
his amateur fights at the garden
in the next two weeks.
And it'll show me everyone fighting.
Alex, you got to look up Hulu theater Argentinian fighter, you know
That's him. I mean, yeah
Your name's gonna get out there in 30 days less than 30
Listen easy if this is my way to stardom where it's like, okay
He got docs this way and I get my name out there then fuck it. You know, this is the opportunity like
You guys put that
It's like I'm reading ducks like that. Don't even say it Sean. He's that he would out of your head, you know, dick
I mean doc you got this baby. You got this you gonna make history. I told you that yesterday
Did I tell you yesterday? I'm talking every time we talk about it. Will you say that?
If this your first is this gun so is it considered a professional bout or an amateur bout can you answer that?
No, this is this is like amateur pedigree. This is a professional amateur
But he's a professional
No, no because
Doesn't turn out to be bullshit because I really want this to be true. I am willing this nigga
This is my one opportunity to make you like my shit. Oh, bro. This is that I asked my chance, you know
Bro, there's still a way to one fuck
I don't think I would you watch would you watch somebody that's always on your panel not always
But since you came like three times ready
And if I could be like there I could be their water boy and like
Free I'll do it for free psyche you would have loved it in the team manager on the socket team, bro
I guess you like to be the water boy you get to squirt some shit in his mouth, right?
Yeah, and give a little massage and like a pep talk between rounds.
Hey, you can do it.
Hey, what's up?
You can do it.
Open your mouth.
I don't have to knock him out to win brahman. I'm coming for
The first round bro, that's what you gotta win but people try
1012 school people already tried to not come out. I've seen like oh, yo, you know, he could fight different
Let's pretend you're Italian you're a greasy Italian tank and you're gonna be wrong
Yo, um, um school. Do you want vacation?
What happened? No
Vacation over time
Vacation that's why you have it came up and you know I be switched from salary to hourly and I be working my ass
So yo Alex, they be having novelists. You can't get overtime like you're salary in New York or changes
Long time
And then they have three rounders and then bro only when you once you go pro you can never go back to the amateurs or the Olympics
You can't do that
No, that's the thing they have novelists and the other ones so there's like one with it and one without it
Because that's the big Olympic thing right let right on show him cuz like when you're the Olympics
You have to be the amateur for years. It was like that, right?
And if I never won I never I never wanted the Olympics
I wasn't talking about you obviously I'm talking about the history of boxing and you know the history of boxing
You know everything the theory the strategy. Yeah, the ones for the love of the Olympics
That's that's like a big achievement. You know you're fighting, but if you turn pro
Or my question or olympic you look at american hero. Yeah, but alex this is my question to the boxing, you know
Historian if you turn pro then you're not allowed to go into the olympics. Is that correct? Yeah. Yeah, you can't go back to the olympic
You can't go back to none of that.
It's either you do that.
Remember, 92, the Dream Team, Alex, that's the same team.
Yeah.
Jordan.
You could probably name 10 players on that team.
Like your school.
You know, the only factor that like the down side is.
The down side.
Like school like yeah, I traveled around
But I never got the chance
Yo school
Hold on. We took a basketball now. We got to get you off the boxing kicker. You'll never stop
You know, I'm back. Can I just say one thing one thing with the one thing turns into fucking 15 hours?
I love you. Now. We took a basketball. Okay
Just say it. Just say it. Just say it. Oh with the Olympics
Oh, we love you. You're a teddy bear. All of you guys from the only thing
With the lamp that was my first time coming back. I told easy. I'm like, yo, I'm not coming back
Bro, I'm off this YouTube stuff. You know me. I'm just you know, I can't even watch what I said cut the cat nigga cut the cat
Yeah, but ledge, you know what? He's just about to say he's just about to say he saw Alex and myself on the panel
And that's why you came up right sure. Yeah, bro. I seen easy Alex
That's why I came up because I've been gone for like two or three weeks with overtime and I seen I was fucking with everybody like
Ah, if you donate if you donate I got like three people
People to donate and then when you came up, then no no no donation
All right, now let's do basketball now dream team. Let's go. Let's start from the beginning Jordan now you go Alex
the
We're going around before I go I say Jordan Alex you go now, so I'm gonna begin in
This is the game, right?
It's game hard way.
Chill for a sec.
The game is, we're going to name the players on the 1992 Dream Team, right?
And we're going to go around in a circle, you know?
And I'll name one name, then it goes to Alex, and he's got a name and name.
Then it goes to Easy, then he's got a name and name.
Then it goes to the next.
And if a person can't think of one, then they're out, you know?
And then it goes down to the next two.
You see what I'm saying?
Larry Bird.
Alright, you go easy which we got Jordan and bird so far. You're up easy
No, see they are out bro. I was in I was in was
All right, so Sean you're up
Hold on one second. I just
When I play basketball, I do it still cookies. Give me that I'm still the ball. We got Alex
I like to dive in down for his ski
You know, easy, easy, I wore an Allen Iverson T-shirt today
I love Iverson
But basically when I think of that team, man, I just think of Jordan Byrd, like the greats back then, Ewing
Chris Mullen and John Stockton, they're the only boys
They're the only boys
Wasn't this a change in his front?
Wait, there was one college student. Can you name this is good trivia? There was one college guy on the 1992 dream team
Do you know who he was?
He's nuts. Oh
No, no, he wasn't till late
If I give you the college he went to he went to Duke
Yeah, I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I IIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII
Do you hear me? He's from Duke right here. He just got number one draft pick 62 million dollars the first
Yo, he's the number one draft pick he went to the Mavs a couple days ago
Is the number one draft bank
Yes, 62 million first two years, 31 guaranteed.
That's because of LeBron James too, you know that?
LeBron James, that's Christopped.
This can't be the same, bro.
Jordan was getting paid 13 million a year.
Cooper, Cooper, his name is Cooper.
That's insane, man.
Imagine what he would have made now.
if he was still if he was still able to play basketball
he would have made the max what uh lebron james makes lebron james just use you do you see the news
right you know some people that boycott sports because of that like i know a business owner
he's a multi multi millionaire owns one of the biggest demolition companies in new york city
right and i did work for him i was with him and i was like yo you watch sports and he's like no i
I don't believe that anybody should get paid that amount of money for that
And I was like what what that is. That's one of the most un-American anti-capitalist
It's not gonna change. Well, that's I I met one of those dudes
I swear to God, I'm like, you know, you saw the Mets game.
He's like, I don't watch sports.
I'm like, he probably owns boxy.
He's a millionaire.
Like he's got a lot of little, but not like that.
But I'm like, why not?
He's like, I don't believe in sports.
Like that's insane to me.
Like nobody's got that amount of money, Alex question.
Does he have more money than some of the players?
Right? No, not at all.
But he's got, you know, he's got money that much money compared to
what that just shows you the mentality of these millionaires.
Some people just because they work hard for their millions.
Baseball in a year, you know, it makes sense to me Alex Alex they born into money. So actually some of the more
Easy easy what about some of the players that come from the inner cities that grow up in schools
Baby work, you know how hard it is to not succumb to peer pressure to stay in the game and practice and knock it
I have I have three almost NBA players
Amount of money bro 62 million for two years
Do you know why he's worth that amount of money? Because another American says he is the owner of the team says he's worth
That's why he's worth it though. You get that right you can pay your employees anything you want anything
I think they gave him like what how many millions like 250 million dollars
11 years 11 year contract 200 a quarter of a billion dollars to play for
But then a cop a cop that has to run around and risk his life
Thank you. I come for you mostly come back
You don't like talking sports job remember that you like sports and I don't like drama too much
WNBA 2024
I had a dream of page last night, bro. I told everybody earlier at a pay of a dream of page, bro
I was making out that bitch
Oh, how is your wife anyway?
Yeah, but why is she missing the easy cameras on that's funny. There's a missus easy out there
Female they could do my shit imagine. Oh, did you see the in you you got a new short out there for my your number one fan
Oh
Yeah, it's just saying it's upon you and it's like awesome devil
It's a picture of a devil like demon and it says this is for easy cameras on the devil is upon you
You didn't see it. No
I would come to that shit. I'm like, I'm like, what is this?
Yeah, but just crazy and this was today
So she's still on it bro, you'll never stop
Yo, that's charisma, that's not charisma Hernandez
Come on, you know who it is
Is it you?
I'm nobody
Yeah, exactly. I have mad sacri-cans, but they're all me
But I don't have different accounts like with all the people Alex question
Is is charisma panthro, I don't know I
Is the same person I think pencil is either
the
Yeah
Harry but then pencil I'm like I think it could be Chris cab because he's also we were talking about the
And the new
Remember that and the no Pantos. Oh, though. Pantos old
I think oh G. Vato is Chris Kev. He doesn't do that. Oh G. Vato the um, um, um
Papa Smurf remember me and I was exposed Papa Smurf and I looked at just like I'm shaving my fucking beard
Isn't oh G. Vato the nigga with the wife
No, I was about to say God would you buy the young boys he say always he says a young
young stuff young stuff
But when he last I heard Chris cab laughs the other day and it was the exact same laugh
from
I'm telling you that's not right. I know that shit. That's they're not the same person.
No way
the
fact that
He's like Alex. He's crazy. He has all these theories that frilly diamond is Birdo and this person is that and and he'll fight you for hours over it
Like he's gonna just say that I'm everybody including him
He's gonna come up with another theory that I'm everybody including him like including me
And we all go the fucking time when we put up birds together, we know who the fuck is
Just say they are all Bruno. I love
Everybody can we get away sharpie can we get away from Bruno?
You know they were coming in here today easy as me some shit. I was doxxing assumption. I wasn't even up here. Christine was like Alex
So I'll stop your crap. It wasn't even me
My city them came the day before yesterday
For them to shut the fuck up leave it alone
I
Went on Sam's page
I went to the casino last night and I was at the slot machine and I put on Sam's page
And it was like I don't know 12 o'clock or that and I see Christina
I see the little dog. Yeah, I said no fucking way. So I read in the chat. I go
This panel so somebody writes your mom
Who's your mom and everyone's trying to figure it out. I said Christine and then Christine was awesome
She went along with it. She's like, yes, I just want to clarify. I am schools mom
Great
You're gonna troll her you're gonna troll my mom if I show you my mom
Christie's the best
Yo, I remember when Sean Pease said he'll hit his titan
Anybody that believed that no no stupid Alex, you know
Would you fuck that thing?
Who fucking a cagaga?
her mother
Now her mother never the million years cagaga, maybe
I
Mean I see like whatever
She's got a channel and she's just something like like chubby like steak bitch with big titties
She's not that ugly. I don't know if it's a way or not. Whatever, you know
I got a mom never know what it is, bro. What do you create?
Before only fans came out. I don't even know
That's an old lady. I think fuck
something looks disgusting
That guy I might give it to but not a mom
Yeah, I'll get it. She was prostituted herself before our oldie fans came out
cool mom
of
Yeah
This is how we found the way she came to her page of 2022 we Google her name. We found we found arm
Just gonna face our YouTube and put in cagaca
And you're gonna see new pictures papa she looks some way and she's a little fat in those videos, but
Whatever and she's obsessed with the Chucky dolls
,
that was another person that just didn't like you
I didn't even like it's ever seen that with them
you gotta go low, you gotta go low fast
once they start talking shit, they go low
I'll drill them out
I know how to do it
Yes, thanks easy for the donation. You always like your seven dollars that cuz he needs that you are
Is that he's in the chat
Like he didn't really know is coming but now he's acting like he's demanding it like he's making that move
He got
Like a football
Fuck!
Yo, get in the bag, get to the back, nigga.
Fuck, go in the corner, put on the dumb hat.
I think you better stay behind, because I was coming at him.
I was coming at him.
Alex, I think that I kind of got that ball rolling though because I said very very way back if somebody donates anything
I'll hop up and I don't know if you read that. Did you read Jonathan saying you just you just go on pan on I said
Well, you just donate. Did you read any of that or no?
But we couldn't see it because it wasn't on so I was waiting for
Two days ago
I said 18 for a book because I see I seen the lowest one is for 18. So I'll send him 18. You know what I'm saying?
So then I can I did my math. Hold on
Yeah, I'm gonna send him that extra money and get this thing you kick. Oh, yeah
Well, then I said to Alex Alex send him a gift membership and I'll come up and then psyche donated a gift membership himself
Did you see that?
Yeah, yeah, I did see that
Exactly and then somebody else donated
I can't. Yeah. Yeah. And I was like, I'll do it tomorrow.
You didn't get it rolling. You didn't get it rolling like that.
And it was the 25 to stay turned. That's who's
had it. You didn't hear me the other day.
And then he came up like, you know, I gave you 18 just use that
to kick his ass.
Oh, so they see how it does. But you're easy. Tell me the truth.
Like, when we were talking about gifts, memberships and getting
the ball rolling and people donating, is that what prompted
you to come up and literally, I just I woke up.
I've seen them up there. I gotta tell you, I said yo, you didn't spend that 18?
When you came up, I wrote that before you were wondering if that's how like momentum happens.
Like, you know, you ever see when people donate on a panel and then all of a sudden that's like
Somebody you know how you call somebody or speak at the devil or speak of something and it happens. Yeah. Yeah, you manifested it
to beat us
he as soon as he got kicked for me he ran to beat us and he's a beat us
and Alex tell me how funny is that
flirty got kicked for the night right or if uh someone's paid
shout out to shout out to took his beam
yo slow down yo bike put me down bro put me down bro
wow oh oh take a more big scream he said
Take a big screen. Don't take him out
I don't know if you're gonna do it today, but since you put on the speedo to go to the beach if so, um, get a nice shave going
Just don't let the balls fall out because then that's the stress in the flag
of the
death of the
death of
know that's why he's been there this whole time bro since you kicked him he's been there
Alex so did you kick them he's been he went there Alex
I'm gonna show him right now I'm like be the how much oh go show that is
yo Alex go kick him from there too bro fuck that Alex of course Alex who is the baseball player you
were talking about before on the match um
I think you're so low Louie so low on total right one solo. Yeah, he got like a 150 million dollar deal of some crazy shit
Yo Alex, that's ridiculous. Oh, yo Alex, of course. What's up? Of course. I'm nervous, bro
I know exactly shit. What do you do? It's an exciting nervous. All right, like it's an exciting
Business, it's like it's like a weird. It's weird. It's a it's a mix of emotions
This is the same shit
There's no there's such an opportunity but nine for this day. Come on. You talk about boxing. I mean
Yo school I've been saying it cuz bro. I'm a nobody and this is the biggest chance
It's all right. I said wasn't nobody too much. I'm gonna kill him bro. Everyone was
You're gonna bury him bro. You're gonna bury him. Let's knock him up ding ding ding
You're gonna bury the relevant ball and still and still from the way of Brooklyn, New York
after a tough fight
Sean
The real big baby
I
Hurricane hurricane P I
Can't use big baby because two other people already have it and they're gonna sam dick rock good baby
He lost maybe it's gotta be something killer like showing the killer P
Something
But that's the thing big baby the reason I always had the name is because my fighting style
Exactly and then it takes his and we have the same style
Obviously, there's different like you know shit in my bag that I could pull out and change it up
But that's if as a heavyweight, that's my fighting style
No, look who's ready look who's ready look who's ready Alex somebody's on somebody's page that they trying to take down
They said I want take this page down. You should go see this the woman's
Right on my page and y'all should troll this shit out of because she said if anybody told her he's coming after them
She's gonna get you she's gonna
Harmony crazy that in this hour at this time six twenty-two
Talking in the morning
Hernandez it could be
We didn't go Alex
and
Easy paid, I swear psyche you have a good heart. Can you provide a receipt that easy actually paid in full mark?
Well, fuck is mark and what are they give a fuck if he's
Mark comes out of nowhere
I love it. I love it. You should come here bro. You'll go in there and tell the page and
Peter and them to come here. Did you come back? I had a dream of page your ownies.
She's mad cuz the other day she came to support him and then he got she got put in the back
And she was like, wow, how did I support him that time like
Yeah, yeah, yeah, she was sick of the support and we're getting along but then she said she's like, oh
Can you give you a tear reading and I was like, well, I know she was gonna do like a really sarcastic like
They can tell people who you really are and she started saying that she started attacking guys
both you guys together and I and we are fighting it like oh look at these guys
Yeah, they're doing this because it's a separation like how these people is manipulating them and like your friends, man
Yeah, really friends like it's like me cast you we have me cast our fight. You think I fast we go
You know thank you
She's really mean as like I never had like a friend like turn on me like that like so it's like I mean
It's like or I
Remember when you pass and I think GTA. Who was it? I went through a garden. Was it
He cast an easy you guys went through a garden to see Sean P
Oh free boxing fight and easy couldn't get it cuz he had a camera. He did get in though. We got
You went and put in the book bag
But first they were like, oh, I think Sean Peer somebody was like you go across the street and leave it with the Hindu
Yo, I'm a crazy crazy situation, bro. I have I had the the pleasure bro of that ass Lincoln
Easy and cast together, you know, I'm saying, you know, I was supposed to go with you guys to that. Yeah
And and I brought and I brought two of my other boys, right?
Easy easy was chilling, you know
I love you Ali
No dude, why didn't you just play Bo Chompi?
I remember, he's like, yo I got an extra ticket
It's gonna be easy, this cast and whatever
And I was like, I'll go, I'll go
And then that should happen
Bo Chompi, believe that
Easy, easy
easy easy Alex for me for me the whole thing is i don't care what what problems you have
between you or don't for me it's like if we link up and we all chill bro i'm not entertaining none
of that bullshit you know it's like we're not doing that we're coming to chill we're coming to chill
everybody's coming to vibe out have a good time you know none of that none of that you too bullshit
Then over and over and over it's not gonna come back alive
Me and easy that has pulled up and cast bro cast was mad sauce
We left that I left that nigga by the by the ticket booth easy couldn't get in because of his
I like the name pass. I like the name pass
Pat
Like
And right away right away easy was like I'm out of here
I'm going home, and I'm like yo yo chill chill. He came back with it in his bag
We went in they got their drinks we chilled said what's up to like, you know boxing people in there easy
That ass was going around around moving around cast, you know, I had to keep my eye on on cast
You know, he gets a little crazy broke cat Casby while and bro and then after that
uh bro my boy won by knockout and easy that I said like yo Sean like that's it you know I came
to support you and your boy I'm out of here my boy dipped and he did the best interview in boxing
I've ever seen he actually asked the fans outside leaving the venue yo school what did you think
yo Alex what did you think oh that's the interview do you remember the one that you guys watched that
I showed between Floyd Mayweather do you remember that yeah yeah how good was that Alex yeah that
Well, he's done
Larry what first Floyd may weather Larry what what's his name? Sean? I know you know that shit. Oh Larry
Come on. I don't know. Oh
Fucks his name Floyd may weather Larry interview. That's like too much too much blue lobster, bro
Yo, how funny was that interview though?
Do you remember what he said to him like you come back?
Can't can't get docks won't docks
Can't docks won't docks can't stop can't pop can't stop can't pop
You want to be a doctor you so too soon jump in on the back on the taxing by wagon
Look at you zone. They're insane
I would never, I would never dox you Sean P.
Your school hours?
Oh wait, you were gonna dox somebody?
Can you dox it in the backtrack?
Don't say it in the person on the screen.
You was gonna dox somebody and that's when I woke up.
Who dox anyone?
Don't do that shit.
Who was that? Who was the...
You was gonna O.T. on Stay Tuned but he got you dropped, right?
That's when I woke up.
Stay Tuned.
That's a good nickname actually.
Did you just make that up or did you like
No frenzy lately man this week I thought summer. I thought everyone fuck it
If you're gonna do it in the next don't fuck it up on the trap don't fuck it up
Remember
I need that real name. Are you? Oh, you know what Alex? I got it
Who summer yeah, you too cool. No, really
I don't think so at the moment
Did you do something wrong? That's a question not an accusation. Yeah, you did see
Everything right
And now there's people coming up at soccer council with her real name and they think it's me and it's not
Apologize to her like like genuine
Something wrong Alex, that's why I'm saying that because I asked you and you said you did
I mean, I mean in their eyes. I did I guess in my eyes
That's not what you just said before I
Do something wrong and you said yes like listen when the wrong you do like the Romans, right?
And this is all taxi bill here. So I
In Rome you do like the Romans do so yeah wrong Romans apologize. You see what I did there
the
and I can't get on chess.com. That's like the
yo yo that's funny Alex I asked my paternal grandfather when I was about six years old I was in
first grade I said can you teach me how to play chess and he said school chess is for rich people
I'll teach you jeho polka which one do you want and I said polka and he taught me how to play polka
I asked my maternal grandfather my mother and I said can you teach me chess and he said sure I'll
Like that was true because he worked for the government. He was a man. I didn't want to learn it
He just forced it on me by the way. I don't want to learn chess
I remember that he sat me down like you're gonna learn chess and I'm like, I don't want this stupid shit
It was so boring at first. I wanted to die
No, was he born in Columbia?
Yeah, he was because they got a lot of grandmasters my great-grandfather was the fucking mayor of Medellin
They I know you told me that you told me that like five times, but
I come from like a high-class family in Colombia like
Everybody does
Grandmasters from Colombia
And a lot of my own my family on our coast I come from a weird family man from now
But oh one night on TPP after hours. I showed you remember I showed you that porn picture of me and then yeah
You told me your life story for about an hour straight. I just muted and listened and you told me
Story of how you got here. So I was down and I was trying to figure out what was
Yeah, and I was trying to figure it out what was bullshit and what wasn't because I was
If you don't want to forget it write that down
None of it was bulletproof.
I write everything now.
When I go into those malls and they tell those stories none of that is bullshit
Oh, I know the whole story about you and your friend when you jumped out of the car when you were tripping remember
I told you the story about
Your room and I was tripping when I went to Times Square for his birthday
He treated us to shoes on his birthday. We went to Times Square. You went to the hotel
Your friend jumped out of the car. Yeah, no, I almost jumped out on the highway on the way back
We had to drive from Manhattan to here. Yeah, he had a bad trip on mushrooms. He had a bad trip and it took eight cops
It took eight cops and like four ambulance dudes to bring them down I literally ran it for diner
Yeah
I had to run into a diner tripping on acid myself because I saw a cop car
Like we just left the car in the middle of the street and he was fighting with himself like walking in circles
You out when you're tripping
I ran three blocks and I saw a diner and there was a cop car in the parking lot
I'm like, oh my god
So I just ran the diner and there was two cops having lunch and I was like my friends on acid
He's going crazy. You gotta come right now like help and they were looking at me like are you in drugs?
I was like, no
the
Best of your story was great, and if that's what mirrored my story because remember I told you you probably can't
Yes, but do you remember it was six period and what we were doing yeah
You guys are nuts, but we did it like not you know getting away from school
You guys did it and like went to school
So we went to school and we dropped it in second period and it kicked in on six period in gym class
And in gym class in New York you do square dancing
I don't know if your school did that in New York, but we had that in the curriculum
So we learned how to square dance in gym and that's when it kicked in and we had the best day of our life
until we got out of school.
I remember my friend, he passed away now,
but he looked at me and I said, what's up?
He said, don't you feel like a million bucks?
And he kicked open the door for the school, you know,
when they had those little things on the front of the door
that you push in, those little,
he kicked out with his foot and like the sunlight being down
and he's like, don't you feel like a million bucks?
Boom!
And we all got into it.
Real got into the Lincoln. Um, what was the link cutlass the cutlass Lincoln, you know that go out of cutlass Lincoln
Call the Sierra
No, no, not that
The cutlass not the LSC because that's the coop but the Lincoln
What is it just that Lincoln s, you know, like the LS like the Lincoln, you know what it's called, right?
All right. Easy. Easy. It's state turn
The one I block the states her
Who did they turn who did oh, yeah, okay. Yeah, he's back in the back chat like you do
Yeah, I'm cool
It turned into the worst day because we all pile into the Lincoln Cutlass and
The five of us are there and my buddy's sitting shotgun and I'm in the middle
Right sitting bitch and two guys are sitting pistol next to me
And you want to know something
we you know that's always the call somebody calls shot on funny
somebody called shotgun two guys call pistol and then whoever's last i was
not getting rich in the middle yeah
i go through
yeah guys guys guys he's really good looking and he just showed me back
he just got back at it i told you you were gonna fall in love with him he's so
Yeah
You gotta you gotta show psyche more than that in the backstage you say you gotta get excited
We found me give it back and you know, then he let him up
They choose your next boot thing hey
If he's gay man, then let him up and pull the guy
But he could be when we were playing
the show and stuff in the back.
He's oh, he showed you his arms.
He'd leave with his tank top up.
No, you forget shit in TPP.
When we had after hours with state term, we played that.
Yeah. No, I was saying that before.
Remember when he's cool, man?
He was cool.
They kids need that eye.
But one day he got some easy shit one day.
I don't know what they said, but he was like you Alex. I know where you live
I'm gonna find you da da da and from that day on I was like fuck this motherfucker
Birdie random of beaters
It's easy if I if I refund you the $7 and then I can I get the tarot cards and then can I look if I bring them back?
If you really want to say yeah, I'll take it back
Yeah, at least we got a free bed for like a half-hour
And I don't want to be a cock blocker, so fuck it, you know
Now he's cool, man. Even even when he said before like it was cool for you gave the money to psyche
You know, he was like good luck. You know what I mean? He said you're welcome and shit
That's the way to look at it. You don't bite on shit
It's like the dick I gotta talk to stay
You remember the last time we seen each other
Yeah
Last time
Was it in half hours?
Yeah, it was in
You remember that guy?
Who? Republicans are better than Democrats. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Last time you were not and you and I were trying to have a conversation and this guy would just like not shut up
You know, yeah, yeah, we we overtook him
We just stayed quiet and he started getting so mad and he's like you're just not gonna respond to me now
He's not gonna. Yeah. Oh a school. You know who I talked about that person with. Oh
You remember, um, the fuck is his name?
No, no, no, no, he's a really good
Very well
Oh, thank you. Thank you. Oh, he's the best. He's the best. All right, boom
I told I ended up telling Hank Hill like yo, this is dude. He goes by the name of boom boom boom
You just said same name. Yeah
Yeah, I'm Republic is the worst than Democrats or whatever and I was like, bro
If you ever see him you need to debate him like yeah, I feel like you got the smarts enough to hang with him
You know they may have but you got to hear them three questions. That's the whole thing. So yeah
Yes, yes
Remember the Jordan question. Yes
And it was a weird and it was a weird one about a younger a girl in high school. Why are you not attracted?
Why are you still not attracted to girls in high school? I didn't like that question
The clothes this shit the point is is I was helping for 20 on his panel. Maybe about three weeks ago
And he comes up on the panel under a different name.
And 420 and I were looking at him in the back
and he was like, school, do you know him?
And I was like, I don't know his name,
but his voice sounds familiar.
And I asked him a question.
I said, did you used to go by the name Republican?
Oh, Ori Matros?
You did, right?
You were there, right?
You seen that?
Yeah, I think it sounds familiar. Well, you weren't that turn. I was asking easy easy. You were in the trolls
Yeah, that's TT. I'm TATT. Yeah, that's who that was I didn't mark wrote that just now. That's my way
the thing is, is I had controls over the mute button because I was helping 420 so I was noticing that he didn't realize that I had the control so I would mute him for about 20 seconds and he would start speaking and then I would unmute him and he was still speaking like he didn't know that he was being muted that whole time
Mark, Mark, if you're, if you're, if you're tied, Mark, chose ordinary chose what I bought off you
Wait, what?
I'm talking talk talk to the chat. Oh, you're talking about something different. Well, anyways, they turn that shit would have that's what happened the other night
He thought he was gonna fool us, but he just ended up getting mad again at himself
Yeah, I mean they good I just bounced over there I bounced from there and it came back
I spent a couple of minutes there if I came back over here. I said fuck it's boring over there
Who's who's a birdie ran you off birdie ran you off?
page
You don't get the joke like who's page who's you do
Whose page
No, he's being silly right now
I said
He's got it now. There it is page page page page. Yep
Watch somebody call him Patrick yo Pat, though, I like the new name
Arthur Arthur made that oh
Arthur close on Pat the guy like a Rony
I think it's a little better.
Thank you. We can start it.
Yep.
They were people that wrote like School of Socrates is like a fake account like towards
me and then when I clicked on it and I went to the YouTube page you know how they have
another name underneath it where it says act something it said act psychorony and I was
so confused I was like did psyche make this account and write that underneath there or
did Alex do it like because why did they write psychorony like
No, I don't have it. I don't have an uncle fan. You know, I am. Uh the San Francisco
the
And they pretend he's like a pro man
You're a pro man
Like him his voice actually
Next to them Alex is the master of like 82 to 90
To what about what about what they get when they talk to Ferrari, but honest when they talk to Ferrari and the guy he's like
Hey, don't worry. I'm a professional. That looks like easy, right?
Oh, no, that doesn't look like a professional. What who does that guy look like you think?
With the state turn with the Mustang stay turn. Did you ever see first?
And what's our feathers view was they all day? Oh, yeah
Do you remember the guy that takes remember with this little Ferrari from the dad and go take it into the city and then park it and
The guy like be careful
No, do you see that to yourself in the character?
You know, we're talking about hi hi J
You guys are breaking up. Hold on
Use the problem is Alex and it's not with turn but like any time you ask like a question online and this type of interaction
Yeah, yeah, it sucks you can't even ask questions, you know, so it's the turn it's it's the movie first view this day off
Stay Tony, it's not perfect. Well
But the new thing is right next to the arrows right next to the mic. So all you got to do is switch it
Information the pop culture between those years, bro, you are you're an encyclopedia, bro
the
Yeah, he loves it. Alex is skiing. Come on, man. Come back.
Alex, come back. Well, back then, it wasn't that strict.
We had nicked it that thing before and he made videos of it.
With that fake slang. Remember he did it on Casus?
Yo, that shit was funny. He came up with it.
I met him on Joker about last year.
Alex, come back. Where's Alex? I was doing cocaine.
Oh, man. It's almost here.
He's summer fuckers 645
Salute him get on the grind. He's no border grind
Yes, he's on the grind. I like that shit. You always be coming up. Stay tuned. He's on the grind
You got the picture. I thought about your picture. That's what I thought about
Yeah, you see me grinding
Alex you really grinding though. I don't regret it
There you go
There you go. That's me. That's me. So the ground ground
There you go, cool, and you could see what you know what I'm doing right there
So I did a 360 on I did a 180 on to the rail
So you see my left hand look how far back it is. Do you see that?
I'm doing the twist like you just jumped up exactly. I got the video to this. I got the video. You should play it one day
I I did actually I played it on on the fourth money's like I played all my videos
Where is money's bitches? I haven't seen money
My school we're gonna meet up again. I gotta give him another computer
Yeah, it should broke down after a week
the
Oh my god
I got my knees done. Oh my god. You should do that. I got my knees up. You look taller
He's gonna come out to me actually
No
Ice cream
Between Windows 10 and Windows 11 or not
I don't know that's you gotta shoot something about windows, bro. I don't know shit, but
Anderson be doing those windows though the sliding crank ones or the open down ones. That's the shit you be talking about
Look you get that bread. That's I can't knock you for it. Who?
A career real career the real career even all on you got to pay 10
I hate them the computer. I'm not I don't charge him. Oh, I'd be charging the people
I don't know I drove out that the fucking Brooklyn it just gave it to him and
So I gave him two computers right and the reason why I asked is because one computer had Microsoft Windows 10 on it and
The other computer had Microsoft Windows 11
And I was trying to tell money to take this other one is better or keep them both
And he's like no, no, I just like the mini one with Windows 11 on it
So with those 11 they all went down the shitter, huh? It's Anderson's fault, bro
Anderson is the biggest window company in America they make the crank ones and then the roll-ups and that's the problem Alex
You know what that was easy that was an alex going
You know you got alex in a chokehold when he says
And he's back
Baby ain't grind won't grind
Is that humans watching this no right nobody
Alex you'd be dipping weight, you know Alex when you when you start on the panel what you when you mute up
It's like they are longer apart, but then as the night goes on
I notice your mutings becomes closer and closer and closer, you know what this is to analyze in my muting time
That's called chasing the dragon Alex. That's wild
So wait you all
inspector
It's very easy to tell human behavior, bro. It's not that hard and like I said easy knows that shit, too
He called it out. So you're mark. You're mark in the check because they said the same thing
He's everyone alley. Got your mark. All right
So your marks out the count you just exposed to school at this
It's Mark. Look at how weak this shit is easy. So we can't even get it out. You just exposed to school at this is
Mark come on Alex. You better
Quick. Are you okay, bro? You just you're getting too slow lately, bro. Did you see me write that before you used to be so fucking sharp quick like
People be smacking you around lately. I hate to see that shit
Free my nigga Alex, you heard exactly free Alex, bro. I like that so
Let's talk about diddy real quick man. You know people were screaming and screaming about those Rico charges
Well, Alex, this might be something you come on a comment. I'm gonna beat the Rico charge
But yeah, but let me ask you a question easy. This is a good question. Do you think the government is using?
Rico too much now and it's starting to not be what it used to be like when that shit like to me
If they don't have evidence of
Like enough if they know they're gonna slam dunk the Rico, they shouldn't use it because he's going to jail for a long time
No, do you think that though?
I think he should but like I just
Eventually they're gonna use the Rico to gather whoever they need to gather
No, by the way, the reason they did not bail is because they're gonna hit him with another indictment
Between here in october they're gonna bring more charges on him
So like who did you hear that from nobody? You just worry about it. What are you buddy? We're out of from
My getting smacked around
You sound like a retard from hell, bro.
Or ego, bro. I'm trying to have a conversation with you about it.
No, seriously, you sound like a demented little, like, retarded kid.
Like, do you think that the repo charged the game?
A million times.
Alex, you were sharp, Alex.
Come on, you sound like a demented retarded kid, bro.
How's that for sure if you retarded it?
So why don't you go to fucking Brooklyn
and give another retard a broken computer?
You sound like a bitch laughing
You know you got him in a chokehold
It's like I'll say no, you know you got out to me. Oh, shut up. You never have out of
Yo, shut up. Shut up. You're hurting so hard right now, bro
You just said show me it's not like a bitch cuz he's laughing at you
Cuz you walk around bro, like I have computers I give a garbage to my boys
Easy do you think that the Rico charge will shut the fuck up?
Look at it with the stupid fucking snowboard picture
Did you break your foot on that snowboarding trip by the way?
That's what I remember that you went into a tree and broke your leg
Right, right you broke your leg, right?
Right computer boy
Where's the report ratio?
Yeah
We're here
As if you're in a little corner crying like a little bitch
As if this plan is trip to home people to get sold for his grandma's fucking plot tomorrow. He's got to go play more plants
So now I'm back psyche. Let's talk psyche. What happened? Okay? No
Everyone's doing
You've been on the other phone just zoning which we're looking up
I've been looking through my books. I like I'm over a thousand books on like Ken's always thinking of things that maybe you could share later
but
Just looking at some stuff and take it out. See you guys
interesting conversation
This is Mark in the chat. That's so funny. Only he would use that generic name as well like Mark
You good
Why don't you do a page in Peter come over here, bro? Oh there? I think Peter's probably doing a show right now. I don't know like
Page competing. He's gonna got harassed. They were here. They feel like almost like sexual harassment like
Again
All the guy like you were there and you're doing it too. You were like telling us that we were kissing and your dream and
That's sexual harassment shit. Shut the fuck up. Don't try to put my words.
I was telling you a dream. I said I had a dream that I kissed Paige.
Now you told me to sexual harassment pool. Shut up you dickhead.
I hate retouch that twist my words. Alex, nothing. You don't get me now, right?
Put me in the back, dickhead.
You just, you just threw me in the sexual harassment pool.
You didn't do it.
All that did was share a dream with you, motherfucker.
Okay, okay, I don't know.
It was everybody else. It was everybody else.
Yeah, exactly.
I didn't hurt sexual harassment nobody tonight.
Especially Peyton.
So watch your mouth, brother.
But it's not what they're saying.
You let us know as you take your sight.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Put this one in the back.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You're...
He said step back, brother.
Anyway, oh does it turn to say Alex was that yeah, it was like well there are a lot of people I'm not sexual rather
No, it's not I mean that that's kind of a strong term, maybe but it was like they're like oh you're show
Beautiful beautiful face. Okay. Yeah, you're about to get back there with them. If you know, I'm I'm doing my thing right now
So anyway
Whatever she was just being told like, you know, I mean she was just really rolling her eyes at everything and then he comes in
Oh, I dream I dream I was kissing you and I was like, I mean she was kind of like this and she was kind of rolling
Her eyes the same kind of thing. It's like I wasn't tell the school of Athens
Oh school of Athens that we made out made love in a dream. He'd be like, oh, that's what's weird and like
I mean, I don't know. It's maybe it's not sexual harassment, but maybe he might think so, but uh, you know, I don't know
But you know you start screaming at me and like oh you too
And you're not as smart as you think you are because you know
But I need to put in the back you right now because you're being difficult. Okay. I like you Alex
But I mean jeez you're such a like a little
Little diva sometimes should I make up some fairy named?
Ike McQueen yes, you should you should so Alex, you know hang out for a few minutes back there
That you're outside that you're outside right now at this or is that a picture?
That's a little I took from the chairlift
Up inside of a main so that's the hot tub and the pool they got a heated pool
So you see all the snow and then I'm up in the air on the chairlift above the pool
So I took a snapshot
This is about 8 0 1 a.m. In the morning
Yeah, hello, it's like that. Oh, he's in the back. Okay. What'd you say? Okay? Oh,
Hold on. Oh, I was in the back. He did that the fake picture, but I know I believe it's real. I
believe it's real
I was in the back. He said that's a fake picture. So that's a fake picture. So I said I said I think it's real
I know it's real. What is he so far? Who gives a shit? Don't I bet you respond to him too much
Did you see before when I just stopped speaking and then show him?
Started laughing and I explained to show him if you look like any shorty stop laughing easy
Just knows that is that his shit is bullshit. So you don't say nothing and it's just crickets, right? You hear nothing
and then Alex just gets deflated and now he won't stop.
Now I bet you, over and under,
if you don't let him back up,
how many times he'll write in the back?
What do you think?
He can't stop himself.
There's a number of hundred comments in the back sometimes.
Well, I don't know if it was him,
but I think it was somebody else.
When when he's speaking and somebody laughs that gives him fuel. So he keeps going and go, you know, and another
When nobody laughs he he starts laughing at himself, you know, and then he'll just stop because he has nothing
Like I remember one time Alex was screaming at me and I just didn't say anything
It was just me and him and after hours
he was like please say something to me now like he was like if I picture them
he was on his hands and knees like please talk to me you know what I mean it
was like the wicked witch melting all right now I'll mute he can go crazy he
just did his bum
Well, it's like I want to go make some food. I got breakfast gone. Oh, yeah
So I can hear Alex why I make
Okay, that's good. Love you
Mental patient
Hey, let's be nice
Yeah, the little boy wishes he was me he's so jealous of me you hear in his voice
When Alex when I don't talk when I talk he does this when I don't talk he does that Alex everyone shut the fuck up
This is motherfuckers crazy
Wishes he was me
Okay
of the
the
You know, I never say that shit when someone jelly the jelly I get lie. I was muted
But I was jelly
What I don't know bro. Why aren't you making food for a cripple boy?
I know I said though when I heard jelly. Yeah, don't worry about it. No, okay. It's the jelly boy. Go make some jelly
I'm gonna go be jelly and eat some jelly and get another garbage piece of garbage computer
to dump on some bull you you might as well give money for 20 nothing that would have been better
then bring his hopes up and crush him like that wait wait wait he better off gave what some money
for 20 give him nothing bro because now he brought this kid's dreams like look two screens look you
I mean like bro, that's fucking torture. You might as well just take them in the balls
You might as well want the money for 20 cells talk them in the back take them in the nuts and have a good day
That would have been better
He's jelly
that's why I would never chill with Athens
because that's a break top breakdown
like on two legs basically
that's why I would never chill with Athens
It's like a walking asylum
Well fuck it doesn't know what he wants who he is what he is
But I do know that he wants to be me and he's jelly
How are you good?
Yeah, good hang out with the bunch of the guys and we have this is you me guys if you don't do you me listen and Indonesia
What are you me?
Okay
That's that's Tony you're thinking what's shown is that she's from Thailand time show us from Thailand
I see I see I see you me on beat his channel. She's really cool
Well, it's you me a singer or not a singer like can't sing I don't think so. I don't think
To the devil double double double double I have a husband
Did you call your your that you're the devil is your husband or what I?
Married oh you're buried in the devil, okay
The devil what the fuck is going on here. I thought she said that I'm married to the devil. I thought she said that
Or does it double nobody elaborate chat anybody, please?
Don't be using that school. That's my word elaborate
Nobody elaborate quick who is pissed got you
If somebody's cooking, what are you like going away to cook or something dick? You like I'm gonna go cook
Now you feel like a library
You just don't realize you're getting cooked right now
I'm getting cooked by you
Bro some good big loser shut the fuck up, bro. You're so laughing scary
Shut the fuck up
Shut the fuck up. Yo Alex you deep-fried don't get cooked
I forgot the first part of it, bro, but I was about to cut your ass house
You see now Alex is gonna steal that line. He's gonna go to another panel below. Yeah, you know everything else is gonna do
You study Alex
Aspen's wakes up and studies me you hear him every word out of his mouth
It's he knows what Alex is gonna do what he's doing when I'm muted. How long I mute in between mutes
No, this is crazy
This is like some psycho bitch from hell
You ever seen that movie with the rabbit gets burned in the pot?
Athens, what if I look at my window, you are
Alex Alex Alex, you know who was in the bushes nigga
Easy
I'm in this whole family him and his uncle and half of us the co-workers were in the bushes like
Motherfuckers and a bunch of Puerto Ricans to do dick
We're gonna swap them on the live the fuck up
From work we are bullshit plans
You can't do shit. Come back at me. Come back at me. Shut up. Alex schools schools on your school. Yeah, shut the fuck up
Come back at me
Easy in the bushes with his uncle Alex. Come on
The fuck oh man shit. Yo, I want to be you never care. No one's talking you home boy
I want to be you. I know it's talking you bro. I can just say like you know shit
Shut up, you know, you can't help it talk. You know, I smack you in your fucking mouth
You know, I'm gonna make you bleed if I will see you bro
I'm gonna take you by your hunchback
Cuz I see in your hunchback and I'm gonna break it. I'm gonna break your hunchback, bro
I'm gonna take a metal back to your hunchback
And cripple you more than you already are mother fucker niggas set a metal back to your back
That's his ego bro like he started talking about easy and that bullshit and we got it
Alex talk to me. No, no, no one's talking to you. I'm talking about it. Free Alex. Help it. I want to be you
No, no, no, we talking about easy the third time was to charge Alex. You're a big
Yo easy I applaud you for staying
Yeah, he good. He good.
You stole what I was doing, though.
You stole what I was doing, though, man.
Bring it, please. Please stop the war.
Yeah, we do.
There's no war.
Being a piece don't like y'all easy. Do you see now like what he's writing Athens is my
Directed him
But you know that I don't like hearing about that shit that when he talks about that shit it needs to be dead in
You know what I mean? That's it like I don't like so it just took three times three times and then I redirected him
I got him on a little leash, you know, and I'm pulling him this way and he told me like twice to the left
But that third told that gave him and he followed me nicely like my little puppy
Look any Alex is Alex is Alex is some days, you know, you get them bad hits and he's just exactly
But you know
Merchawakes, you know
What do I say about Alex like I love him and I hate him. You know what I mean?
I hate to love. You know, is that possible?
Well, it is possible because like I love him.
Yeah, because like you want to know why you meet if this is an honest question
or if it's a troll, it doesn't matter because I'm going to give you a genuine answer.
There'll be nights when I'm with Alex and it's after Alex and nobody's watching and Alex is a totally different person
You know, it's like he's
He's like Alex there and then he's Alexander McQueen when people are watching and you're gonna meet a totally different dude
That is so chill that will like
He'll learn from you you can teach him things
But when nobody's watching that's him when somebody watches then it's different then it's crazy talk, you know
Like he totally just forgot about that whole thing with easy in like what was it psyche 45 seconds
It took me to redirect them. We saw what I was doing. Well, yeah
Yeah
He's threatening people. I keep they don't like the threat really. Yeah, he's looking like a threat mop
And so like like he'll be in the back. Let's see how many we got what are we up to?
for Alex 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29.
That's 30 29 do us and be left one more Alex is 32. You're actually at your one behind you're at 32
And then look what he does like I just told him that he wrote like in seven look at that man
Be good, mr. Alex be good. There's no war. Yeah
But but you me you me you want to know? Oh, he's back. Let him go. I'm gonna mute
Or me what do you think he's gonna do back you think he's gonna talk about me or easy be good mr.
Alex, he's gonna be
I don't know what I talk about him or is he what do you have a coffee dog talk about me go ahead do what I want you to do
No, bro, there's no need to talk about about you. All right talk about easy and it's uncle pulling up
Now you want to talk about me Alex. No, I want to talk about eating his uncle
Oh, that's two times, but you know this game. It's my game. You always lose
Oh, you don't have a mind, bro. You don't come close
I want to talk about easy pulling up with his uncle trying to swat niggas on the live
That's what I want to talk about
I want to talk about his uncle and his friends that he brought out of his construction company his boys
I know all their names got them all on camera
All of them everybody
I always want them on the live right you're gonna swat on the what?
Easy
Who's gonna get swatted on the what I said I always been on camera
Yo, yeah good for you
Yo, I was chill not too much money girls chill out with that. Yo, you me. I know you married
But shit like niggas trying to see some awesome titties to to make this
I'm not mad. I'm not mad. What do you what do you mean? I'm mad at you. I don't even know you
Be good no war no fighting no trolling that's it
that's a five
The fuck you need a thing from avatar. Is that why you have that name is that you me from avatar?
Is that why are you crazy asses? You're crazy, right?
Do you want to ask what pills do you take? What does your old doctor prescribe?
Tell me cuz I know it's a hell of a lot, bro. Get him get him school get him school
I know this motherfuckers got a whole jar full of pills.
Bill bottles, bro. Take two. It's described with depression for this for that amnesia for this fear
Oh, yo, pop on this is scared of his own shadow, bro
Yo, yo school pop on him, bro. Hit him with it. It's scared of his own fucking shadow
He has to take pills to talk the way he's talking tonight. Yo school head him with a jazz
He knows it
Quiet, you know when he stays quiet it means you're right
when absent states quiet you mean he's a little bitch and you got him right i know everything about
happening or he's actually beauted up because he's probably pumping another pill he told you he's
gonna he does not believe you guys you guys will wait all night long and we'll go all night long
on and on and on and on and we'll go all
On and on and on and on and on. Life goes on.
Yeah, we about to bust that ass, you know what's up.
No, no, we're just showing what the guy's couple members you found me. We got easy cameras on
Yo
Yeah, you could take three if you want to take three
Okay
school is easy enough
if you try to
all the weapons are easy
they're all female
you mean
you mean if you try to get gangbang
you phone me with the range that too
gangbang?
yeah
yeah like multiple dicks in your pussy
like we patch you around like a rag doll
I fuck you then he fucks you then he fucks you
you ever heard of a gangbang bitch?
you're from Indonesia that's gangbang city
Yeah
You
That will be your village for a month bitch
I'm not a bit
No, he wasn't
Indonesian broke bit. I have a hundred dollars for you. You mean you can feed your old village if you want
I'll send you 100 hours so you can feed your family for the next two months. I cannot understand you
I'll send you 100 hours so you can feed your family for a month and enough of the game
You me you me. He wants to give you all I want you to shut the fuck up
You need money back you're from Indonesia now you may come by the whole island
I can buy Indonesia money
You me he want to send you a couple of money money money. Are you drunk?
No
Get some water
Don't get some water. I got lobster though. If you want to I got lobster for us, too
I have money. I post it. I have money. I don't need any money from online because I have a job
I'm not a joke. Welcome to the fucking Rhetor hour
Starring
No niggas just wanted to know
I understand the McQueen, allegedly
Yumi
Mr. Marks
Mr. Marks, I am 100% legal
What'd you say Yumi?
Nothing
I'm not talking to you
How much money do you make a month?
How much money do you make a month Yumi?
It's like $400
I made that a f**king hour, b**ch!
Yo, that's crazy!
I made that an hour!
Yo! Yo!
Oh, s**t!
Checkmate, enough!
Enough, shut up!
Talk to me, talk to me, don't peak with Tom with this b**ch!
400 a month!
Huh?
Baby!
Wait!
So do you think do you think every do you think everything in here expensive?
Like in the US. No, it's not everything in here is very very cheap
This is why so many homeless
An hour because they don't have money
You know
That's why we try to
Mr. You guys you guys can check about Bali Island so many Americans so many Germany so many European
Stay and move to Indonesia for
Do you think my salary about
400 is
really
You know, all right. All right. How much money do you make a day a day?
You wake up and by the end of the day, how much money did you make?
For a day I'm a teacher
So how much does that pay daily?
Let me hear this
How much does that pay?
Shut the fuck up, dick.
You sound so broken and weak.
You sound like a crippled asshole in the back of the room.
Like, you weak and shut up.
Someone put this asshole in the fucking closet.
And shut the fuck up, bro.
Yo, someone throw this dick in the closet and shit, yo.
Shut the fuck up, cripple boy.
Yo, cripple boy.
Yo, you me, yo, you me, yo, you me, yo, so we'll put this motherfucker in the closet.
You know what he sound like, he sound like.
Yeah, he has some shit going on here.
It's stable.
What the fuck happened, man?
He sound like.
Yo, yo, get him school.
Fuck done to go.
That's all I need to do.
I hop in.
The university paid me every month.
Not every day.
Calls himself Italian.
No fuck out of here.
so western life and asian life kind of different
kind of, not the same thing
I was that piece of shit BMW by the way
how much
how much more
he's got to speed the shit
three series at the funniest thing
335 yeah it was fucking dirty
headlights and all
man it's hurting
my boy it's hurting bro
my boy it's hurting
yeah you know Sean P
Yeah, you know
She says she came in for a black American
I feel, yeah, hell yeah, what do you do?
So you found them?
Yeah, yeah.
You need to devote for it.
300.
You need to show them the projects.
That's as black as it gets.
Yeah, your voice, your accent.
Easy to get over one black. You got it. Yo, yummy. No, thank you projects
Hell out this bitch shout out to the hill yo
People like you like to call someone like a woman has a bitch
Because you are a bitch, that's why
It's nothing, it's nothing bad
It's just jelly bro, you're jelly that it's smarter than you
It's nothing bad
Oh yeah, it's more than me
It's better English than you
Yo, you just stole my word
You never said jelly in your life
Now you're saying jelly, asses
You're not done with the cool kids bro
You're the nerd
What happens in a fucking locker bro, yo, let's freak out of my face
Don't fucking clean your head like
Yo, you mean what's the cold arm when we say when we say bitch
Coward when we say bitch it means like baby, you know what I'm saying? So we don't mean like nothing bad
It's better. You you say like
Honey love or babe not bitch, you know, bitch is kind of love
That's cool. That's what they do
Like on or something it's more polite
Okay, what happened to Alex you I was just kidding money good damn money good that I slept I
When he acts like a dunce man Shaiki you fucking booted his ass now
What happened you talked to me about my car? I told you was a 335 300 horse 300 talk and he's less
But he got jealous here with this piece of shit BMW
Yo Alex arm now it's because school said some shit after after
You stop talking and I was my friend. Yeah, I told him that he's
Corner with a dunce cap
My salary is in 100 before hundred
every month the university paid me every month 400 not me no no that was
that was somebody else asking about that for I don't give a fuck about that
Jacob mr. Jacob mr. Jacob yeah yeah I'm reading I'm reading from the on the
side chat on the channel so how much how much one menu of KFC in the US KFC how
Oh man, I want to pop out to this shit. They got a okay. Okay. How about make it under $15 and I got
Like maybe five or six pieces big nice chicken hot with two biscuits one gravy and a fries
That was like under 15
You know what I'm saying and then I spent on that frozen lemonade shit that mango shit
I bought one of those and then I bought that strawberry. How much is that? How much is that?
It's like a $20 or something everything. Yeah, it's 2020 but I split it with my man. So you know
20 in here only 10
Yeah, in here only $10 for the KFC a big menu
Well, baby
20 but we was in good we was in good
That shit was hot Tom Square Popeyes
Come to Indonesia, huh?
With the plan
With the airplane. I don't know. What the hell you think this is you better bring your ass over here. What the fuck?
He is you using anger and he were to what the fuck what the fuck
You guys you guys went to school or not
Wait, what you guys like to we're using
Damn
I
Tried no war be a good man. Oh, no war. No, no, no
When you come into America, man
Huh
I said Assalamualaikum
I said I'm gonna be in the shower 15 minutes from now. I'm just gonna put my clothes away in the drawer
Yo school she asking you something bro
It's about 15 minutes
Yo, she asking you something school
Talk to my man's right here. Yeah, oh you mean yo school
Fuck that nigga my school. I mean I mean why you guys like to
I don't know. It's too much you asking mad questions right now. It's
seven o'clock. Um I'm not asking about America. Just come to America. The guys
will treat you right. All that shit. Don't want you're gonna be upheld like a
queen. I doubt it. I doubt it. I totally doubt it. No, no. Trust me. Trust me. Just
you know, come out out your box. Come out. No.
Not for me. Shit. I ain't I'm saying, you know, you can't be living in Indonesia all your life
You guys you guys come to visit Indonesia first and then after you guys came
I go to America
It is great over here
It is great over here. Yo, Sean. Do you know where Bali is?
Oh, I'll go to Bali though. Hell yeah, I'll go to Bali.
Bali is in Indonesia.
Oh, that's Indonesia?
Yeah, you think Bali is a country?
Why are you guys kind of stupid to say that?
Do you see how most Americans are?
You mean, most Americans are closed-minded.
And the thing is, because it's just like any other empire.
You mean, wait, don't talk when other people are.
I stopped talking to you.
other people you mean listen every empire throughout the history it's the same
thing people get content with the roof over their head right we're safe right
we can get a job right and we're not and we can put a place over our head so
those three things you have a house right you have
food right sustenance and
You're safe from harm from the outside world and once that keeps going like decade at the decade
Yo, shut up loser. You don't talk about people talking yo this guy's insane yo
Yo, that was crazy, I thought.
Be good, Mr. Alec.
Have a nice day with my polite friends.
Be good, be good. How old are you?
Don't tell you school year is 15.
Be good
At least you learned about
Man, yo you guys are crazy yo Alex. Yo easy pull back up bro cuz I ain't gonna my bro
It's a man and shit that deserves respect. He's a little freak with a three-series piece of shit with broken
Yo, you also drive a beamer. Yo, you're doing my phone
Alex Alex. That's mad fucked up. You also drive a beamer. You don't know what I drive motherfucker now
That was like 30 years ago. Okay, so you drove a beamer. So what nigga?
Yeah, I drove one and I drove a lot of beamers
so what's wrong with the 3 series?
what's wrong with the 3 series?
what are you protecting him now?
I like to see what happens
I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMWs, I like BMW
I
She said is he okay
You me can you say that you said calm down mr. Alex or whatever? Okay?
She's okay. She said be okay. It's okay. It's so funny
Calm down. Mr. Alex or whatever the fuck she said that I'm calling the Alex go to red. I know you have a serious mental breakdown
I
Shit, she's cooking them
Nah, yo bring my nigga Alex up. I fuck with my boy. Yo, uh, like if you hear it, you know, this is how I was people bring my nigga back
Bro, it's seven
Take a shower, bro. I got it. Don't don't leave me up here with you. She got a hundred questions about him
I know, but you got it. You got it. If you can't can hang tight for like 15 20 minutes
I'm gonna take a shower and I'll be back
Yo Alex, it's just still there pull up bro. Easy if you're still there
Mr. Sean and Mr. Woohoo and
Oh nice to meet you guys. Hi
Yeah, this you don't gotta call me. No, no, don't call me mister. Don't call me mister, bro. Don't call me mister
Well, um, that's, uh, okay. Uh, what should I call you?
It's Sean. No, mister. None of that crazy stuff.
Mr. Sean. Okay. Nice to meet you.
Mr. Sean and Mr. Who, who's the other one?
Do you see, do you see, do you see the avatar on mine underneath you? Do you see that picture?
The painting? Do you see that?
Full of...
Athens.
That's the painting Raphael painted right there.
You can see. School of Athens.
That's the name of the painting.
Oh, I see.
Greek.
Are you?
Yes, Raphael. Italian painter.
But School of Athens.
Oh, Italian.
You see he learned Bali wasn't a country. It's like the UAE people think Dubai is a country, but it's a city
But you mean I'm gonna leave you with my friend Sean
He's good people don't bombard him with a million questions because they'll get nervous down. Just get a shot
Yeah, I'm just kidding I'm just kidding
Hey Selma
The little coward Alex is crying in the back
Yo, free that boy Alex out there. Oh, mr. Cool and mr. Sean. Okay, bro. Don't call me. Nice to meet you guys
I'm going to take a shower. We'll be back in 15
Are you are you from the us of mr. Sean and mr. School you guys from canada or us
I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I'm in New York. I
to be honest I'm just a little shy you know I don't want to I just like it's
tough for me you lied to me you lied to me I'm not in Bali I'm in Sumatra no
way Sumatra yeah that's oh that's my clothes
Bali in Java Bali in the Java land I am in the Sumatra yeah yeah
Yo
I'm in Bali, baby. Yo free money. No, you're not. No, you're not. No, you're not
Yo, sake if you back there let him up man, cuz this shit. It's eight o'clock right now
You me don't know what's going on. She just laughing a laugh. It don't matter what you say you guys so funny
You guys are funny when you guys
Like a screaming to each other
I don't know. That's just a headache
Is that a habit or a hobby?
No, not a headache.
A headache?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Roman Queen, easy.
Oh, you scared it up off the spot.
Yo, last course staying clear the closing doors
Alex pull up my guys are easy allegedly pull up
members members calling all members
whole lot a whole lot of
Calling all members
Speak now forever hold your peace
Pull up and preach
How about
Ain't no way nigga you niggas just skirted on me like that
School that has dipped off
Last call last call
Allegedly McQueen
Oh, yeah, man
Everybody's skirted
Now this shit got dropped
Good morning. You know what he's there?
Hello
Hi, well, I guess oh, I don't know if
Here
What's the name of this Sean or something and then Athens he's taking a shower, I think
So it'll just be us. Maybe when they get back. They'll just wave to me when I'm back
Then I'll bring back up
Going live, okay, Sean good day
Okay
Ladies
So what do I have I don't know my head's really interesting
I was reading like some of the Illuminati book earlier. I have a lot of cool books
See hi
Sean by Sean
They're very distinctive covers. I've downloaded a lot of books already.
Your phone's suddenly ringing. Oh, what's up, Shaw? Okay, I'll find some here.
This one's called
This book is called
It's called Illuminati the cult that hijacked the world. Actually, no, there's a lot when I want
This was good though by Henry man cow cow
Different one
Okay
Professions of Illuminati
My eyes can eat some rest. Yeah. Hi, you're welcome. Thank you for being here. Sorry. They're rude. You'd be good
Oh, yeah, you have a good day. Thank you so much for being on the show
So, what do I got? I mean, it's like this is like a little bit dance. I don't know if you like it. Let me see
People contest
Okay, I found it. Okay, so let's see
Some of it is too controversial
You can read about this world of spies the shadow the Vatican see 250
Ah, you guys are doing piece two, 250, okay.
Okay.
This is about spies or something, let me see.
It says, secret services.
Actually, this is too controversial.
Strangely, encyclopedia of spies.
Choose below another valuable article.
Yeah
I'm not afraid to read it, but I think it was just a little bit too
Advanced right now, let's see something else. Let me see. I'll find something good
Okay, we can read some of these myths. They're good. Oh, there's people in the chat. Okay
These are some myths, but they're like really fun. They really wrote like written in a funny way
This book is called Zeus Grant stupid wishes. I know bullshit and guide to world of mythology to a mythology. Okay
Okay, so there's some good stories in here see so we're gonna read we start with the Greek
Tyresias is twice the man or woman you'll ever be.
Okay, I'll start reading.
It goes, let me introduce you to the baddest prophet around.
His name was Tyresias.
So besides having an awesome name,
Tyresias is a guy who was out hiking one day
and he saw these two snakes doing it.
And he just goes, what?
I don't wanna see those snakes doing it up on this mountain.
And he just runs up and beats them to death
with his trusty walking stick, like a badass.
Now that's all well and good, but apparently Hera was really excited about seeing these snakes do it because
Then she gets really pissed and she says so you like beating a shit out of snakes, huh?
Well, how about I make you into a woman for some reason?
So bam Tiresia has become the woman for seven years
He doesn't treat it as a punishment basically at all and in fact he just shits right into hair's hands
by becoming the best prostitute the world has ever seen.
And he invents, she, he invents so many new sex positions
and they have to revise gravity to accommodate them.
It's just that kind of party.
So after seven years of awesome, loveless sex, Tyrese is wandering into the mountains and he sees his snakes doing it.
And he just says fuck it, and he runs up and beats him to death again, at which point Hera kind of sighs and realizes that she's not going to teach this motherfucker anything about anything.
And turns him back into a man because if you can think of a round...
Being a shit out of reptiles. What are you if not the ultimate man says cut to a few weeks later
Zeus and Hera have some kind of an argument which is not unusual for them
The argument is about who enjoys sex more dudes or chicks
Hera says it's got to be dudes presumably because she has never enjoyed sex with her awful cheating husband and Zeus
Says it's definitely got to be chicks presumably because he's
Hyperinflated sense of his own sexual prowess. So the two of them yell each other
After a lightning for a while until they finally are like wait a second
We totally know a dude who has also been a chick and he's had scabs of sex as both types
Maybe we should try to ask me him so they go hit up Tyrese
He's like yo who has sex to your sex dudes or chicks and Tyrese is like oh man
I thought you would never ask now. I had some sex in my day
I played naked twister and boner bingo and all kinds of yachtsie, but I gotta say
When it comes to chicks and dudes, I actually figured out mathematically, and it turns out
chicks and joy sticks nine times more than dudes.
And Zeus is like, ha, I told you, Hera, just because I put no effort into our sex life did not mean that your experience is the norm.
And Hera is like, god damn it, Tiresia, my husband does not need another excuse to not try in bed.
Let me hear you enjoy sex without your eyes.
And Tiresia said, well, actually the eyes are not so erogenous as bones.
So, oh shit, I'm blind now.
And Zeus is like, Hera, why you gotta be like that?
If so, then there's no reason to take it on Tyreseus.
Yo, T-dog, I'm sorry about my wife, bro.
Let me go ahead and give you the register of prophecy to make up for that.
And Tyreseus is like, okay, that worked out pretty well, actually.
And then after that, he shows up in a whole bunch of stories.
He's always right about everything he says and no one ever fucks with them because he's a psychic
and also probably a sex god.
So the majority of the story is for the fellas.
Fellas, before you complain that pleasing your lady is too difficult.
Try walking a mile in her boobs as long as we're talking about things Tyritius did
No, I'm listening to these stories. I'm telling some cool story. I mean, they're funny though, right?
Okay, okay, so narcissists probably should have just learnt to masturbate as the next shift or it says so the story begins
Like all good stories with a hot nymph. She's blue. I
Literally her skin is blue
That's not really important to the story, I'm just giving you the facts.
Anyway, one day she's out near some river and the local river god Staphiesus,
who no one has ever heard of, is like, oh, maybe if I grape this nymph,
the other gods will take me seriously.
So he drowns Porlyn Fioropi by encircling her with his winding strings, wink, wink.
At this point, she really has nothing to do but get seduced, so they have a kid.
The kid is named Narcissus. Narcissus is gorgeous. Like imagine if someone could look exactly like bacon taste
You have a pretty good picture of Narcissus unless you're a vegetarian and
His mom is like oh snap my son. My skin is blue and I still got
Grape what the hell is gonna happen to my kid?
But he's not even a year old and he already looks like he can suck the red off a fire truck
So she takes Narcissus to see the baddest motherfuckers in the land who's of course
Tyreseus and the Oropius like if my son going to get
Oh my gosh. And Tiresias looks up from his work, which is beating snakes to death,
and a stick whenever they try to get their freak on. And he's like,
bitch, please, he's gonna be fine as long as he doesn't come to know himself.
and the rope is like, what does that mean?
And Tyrese said, quiet woman.
I think it, here's some snakes having sex
and then he runs off brandishing and sick.
So the rope is just like, whatever.
Narcissus grows up to be strapping young lad.
So strapping, in fact, by the time he's 16,
every last person in his town wants to bang
the bejesus out of him.
But Narcissus is like, sorry, ladies, dudes,
centaurs, I have unreasonably high standards.
So basically no one is happy.
Then one day Narcissus goes walking the forest
for bad shit just generally happens, and this nifnum echo sees them, of course, seeing...
As this nymph has eyes, she instantly head over a vagina and love with them.
There's a problem, though, which is that Echo is not some kind of playful nickname.
It refers to the fact that she cannot say anything except for the thing that she just heard other people say.
Because Herup got pissed off about how she used her silver tongue to buy Zeus some precious escape time
during his adultery runs and maybe also use her silver tongue on Zeus in other ways.
Would that feel good even? Silver tongue? Anyway.
So Echo is stalking Narcissus through the woods not able to say anything
But I guess she makes some kind of noise because then Narcissus is like who's there and Echo is like who's there?
Narcissus is like Narcissus and Echo is like Narcissus and Narcissus is like yes
Which Echo mistakes for consent and she jumps out of the woods like yes
And comes running toward and pulling nude and Narcissus is like hey, totally naked hot nymph
Allow me to introduce you to my unreasonably high standards unreasonably high standards meet hot naked nymph
so Echo basically runs to the woods crying, except she probably can't even cry without
hearing someone else do it first. But anyway, she gets pretty butt-hurt about the whole thing,
and not in a good way that she wanted, so she just mopes around the forest until her body
actually disappears. And only her voice remains, and then she uses that voice to pray to Aphrodite,
or actually Venus, because this is the Roman version of the story, and is like,
Dude messed this dude up for me. Okay. I'm not sure how she managed to make the prayer all on her own
But I like to think she probably did it by hanging around the legions of chicks
Well, I wish Narsha's this was dead because he wouldn't have bone them
So Venus here's the prayer it's like done
And Narsha suddenly gets super thirsty and the only water in the woods happens to be deep pool crystal clear spring water
He starts drinking out of it
But then he stops because he realized that what he's drinking is the face of the most beautiful man he's ever seen
He falls in love with this hunk of pubescent glory that he pines after this dude for like days until he realizes the plot twist
The dude is actually a reflection of narcissists himself because apparently for the last 16 hours of his life
He has never seen in 16 years of his life. He's never seen his own reflection
He has never taken a bath or like had a cup of water or you know
Just really
They're really hard of the ball guy until he realizes the plot twist the dude in the pond is actually a reflection of narcissists himself
Hold on
He has he's a pretty sheltered life apparently so in any way
He gets finally really depressed and like riffs off all his clothes
Refuses to eat which is not only makes him more attractive to himself and also dead
And so he basically goes down to the sheaths parts of hell in this time abreast forever steering and reflection the river sticks
Meanwhile Echo's voice shows up in the woods and finds Narcissus body. It's like damn it
Wish I kept it my body can't even fondle his corpse now
She feels kind of pretty bad about the whole thing
She makes it up flowers right out of the corpse and that's the consolation prize for dying
So from now on every time you see a narcissist flower just remember that if you are beautiful
You should never drink water because it's too dangerous
Okay
I'm gonna trip her for Stephanie
More you guys like it or no, I had no one was commenting you're watching and I see you guys in the room
So Persephone is the daughter of this chick Demeter who's the goddess of fertility and crops and whatnot
She's actually incredibly hot and so hot in fact that Hades is down in the underworld
Which is all actually called Hades actually and then he looks up one day. He sees her goes. Yeah
Yum, I gotta get me some of that. So he just pops up like that in the world of the black chariot
Ultimate wretchedness and he says hey little girl. Do you want to come to hell?
And she probably would have said no only he kidnapped her because Hades is the ultimate ladies man
So they're kind of hanging out down hell. It's been kind of pretty depressing in hell
It's actually you've been a little bit better with Persephone there because no one she's not because she's not a little emo bitch
Like Hades is all the time and even though he's a whole fucking badass came into himself
Seriously, why is he always going to be moping anyway? Persephone pulls some exterior decorating like some Spock Spocky feng shui and shit and wham
Spooky feng shui and bram. Hell is pretty okay place to live all of a sudden, but all is not well
Because meanwhile Persephone's mom's meter is up in the regular worlds
Freddie the shit out of herself over her missing daughter and it does not help at all when she finds out that she was kidnapped by the king of hell
Hi
Good morning, psyche
No, I'm listening to you read about the Greek gods
How would you like it? These are pretty funny well rich and yeah
I know the story pretty well like I said
I've been studying religion and even though there's no religious people to follow those gods
It's still used to be a former religion. So I've researched a lot of it. Well, I think there has been a research
Yeah, you know high school. Yeah, I mean in high school
They do teach the Greek myth and a lot of people to capture a lot of imaginations. I actually went to Greece when I was in high school, too
And I love them
They're completely comparable
Yeah, I mean they just basically adapted to God. There's a few differences like you know in Greece Ares is a God of war
And he's like not a very well-liked God. He's like
You know, he's just like he's kind of you know dumb and violent
But then again the Greeks weren't very into war but then when we got into the Romans
They like they were very warlike people and so he was all of a sudden he was Mars and just elevated to this like you know
One of the most powerful gods of Rome
the
What's going on? How you feeling, man? I've been waiting to see you at this
I want to drop that a membership over there summers when you're over there, brother. Oh
You mean pass it on like like
That's really cool that you're about to run up and I gave you my word, brother
That's really cool that you you want to know something exiled. I'll be honest with you. I forgot about that
And I'm usually a memory and that's really cool that you brought that up man. You know one thing about you forgot bro
I'm a man
You're on my wavelength man. You're on my wavelength. You're a positive guy
No, I'm really a truly negative evil entity, bro by birth, but I've strived to be adopted
by the most high and Bre become one of his children, bro.
I like that you said that people by birth, you know, like Omen, what was his name, Damien,
right?
Like, I like that shit.
You ever see the Omen, the first one?
Yeah.
Yeah, man, I mean look at my criminal record it would reflect an evil individual
And my criminal
What there is a murderers or assaults or
My my my biggest case on there will be aggravated arse with explosives. Oh, yeah
That's the only case I got caught
That's what I'm saying. Yeah, it was like how I was
Okay, well because it's like you could have heard a lot of people but it didn't kind of thing right?
It didn't kill people that or didn't but but it could have it was
It didn't but you know, I'd be
So you you didn't get
To us talk is psyche I
I understand you don't think it but I've been always interesting to hear like you did the arson
You know arson's can you know spread or heard a lot people but in this case it did it and I think that it just charged you with like
the arson
Yeah, well how long before you went home after that how long were you away?
Two and a half years. They was trying to give me 18 bruh, but I'm a little bit crazy
And then they tried to go ahead and pass me through without no psychiatric plea till my lawyer brought that to the table
Mm-hmm. Okay, and I see
Psychiatric doctor they was like yep this man's certifiably crazy
So let me ask you a question because I'll try to divert it away from you if that's alright
Do you guys know who Eric Rudolph is?
Yeah, I've heard of the name. Is this uh, Greg tell me tell us so so there is a great show man
Like I always use solar movies so I can like get anything from anywhere, but
It's called manhunt and in the first season they did the
the unabomber and
Worthington Sam Worthington the guy that you know was in avatar
He played the profiler that caught the guy in the woods dead kizinski. I think his name was
and then manhunt season two they did the Olympic bomber and that story is so crazy like I didn't
realize the extent of what happened and like with the government and with the North Carolina
regulators that's the oldest militia you know that was formed in like before the revolutionary
This guy
Futs a bomb in the Olympic right the Olympic Center during the Atlanta 96 Olympics. Do you guys remember that?
Yes, okay
All right
Hear things like it this it makes me question things because when I bought a house
I had found some records from an ex-military individual that actually retired becoming CIA
and there was a certain bombing that happened in California at a postal department and a man
was framed for it and it was actually a CIA operation. I'm glad you said that word, sprained,
exiled, so to finish the story.
Pat why did you say Richard Jewel? It's just a question
I thought he said the Atlanta bombing wasn't that Atlanta or over taking it was different
Oh, no, you see this though
And this there's nothing wrong with you saying this but were you under the impression that Richard Jewel was the bomber, right?
Is that what you're saying? No, I know but I think he said he was someone that framed and then I thought the Richard
I was confused. I was kind of like, you know, just listening, I was
They had taken this part. This is my point, psyche. There's nothing wrong with you saying that it's almost good that you said this because this is what happens
With the government and what they did. So there was a bomb place there and Richard Joule was a security guard that always wanted to be a cop
And he was known for like maybe saying things at a place that
wasn't going to happen, you know, but the point is, is what did the government tell us? If you see
something, say something, right? So that's what he was doing in a lot of places. And they're like,
stop it, you know, you're not a cop back up. And he went and said, this bag looks suspicious. Can
you look at it? And they're like, stop, stop, stop. And he went there and actually found it, you know,
in the bomb, right? Found the bomb and saved a lot of people or whatever. A lot of more people
the CIA, no, the FBI comes in, right?
Cause that's on our government.
And what do you think they do?
They're trying to figure out, you know,
someone who did this and they're stumped.
They can't figure out anything.
So what do they do?
They go under the pretense in 1984.
If you remember the Olympics in 1984,
there was a bomb placed and the guy that went
and found the bomb was actually the guy that placed it.
and the FBI were like, oh, we're so great.
We figured it out.
So they did that to this guy, Richard Jewel.
They said, this is just like 84,
but it took like a couple of weeks.
He went on like, you know, 60 minutes at CNN
and was held as a hero.
And then all of a sudden, two weeks later,
cause they can't figure out anything.
They just put the blame on him.
And still today, like you're now Richard Jewel,
people think today even, all these years later,
just cause his name was associated it.
Do you know how they figured out in the long run who did it and like what happened with that story?
I don't remember exactly, but it might tell us
Check this out, right? He planted the bomb in July 27th of 1996, right?
111 so this will happen it killed one person
Allison Hawthorne and caused a fatal heart attack to Matt something
111 people were injured, but so many more people would have died because he pushed everybody away
Now, June 16th, 1987,
we're talking like 11 months later,
a bomb gets planted at the Northside family planning services.
That's an abortion clinic, right?
Four were injured, but none were killed. Okay.
February 21st,
1997, which is about a month later,
There's a bomb at the other side lounge. I'll try to make this quick too. That's a lesbian bar in Atlanta. Four were injured. None were killed
January 29th a year later
Obama was placed at the new women all women health care clinic
It was an abortion clinic and what happened was and I killed an off-duty police officer, right?
a witness noticed a gray pickup and a license plate that was tied to Rudolph's NC trailer, right?
So now they have a name, right? And they figure out, like, the guy, right?
He figures out that they're going after him because they, like, post his name.
You know what I mean? Like, idiots, you know?
And he flees into the woods, right?
These woods in North Carolina, I don't know if you know them. They're called like Smoky Mountains
It's I wish I knew the the
What are they called the square footage exiled right, but it's one of the largest like in America, right?
This guy now for us. Yeah, it's also were a lot of drug traffickers hiding them
Definitely, definitely he planned for this. So they found all these years later
Do you know what he had? He had gigantic food dumps and ammunition supplies in these
big cat uh not catapults uh like things that he tied up into the trees that were protected so
animals couldn't get it all over the place he had places where he could live in various reasons
so what happened was is while
They got his name. Check this out. They couldn't tie it to the Olympic bomber because
You know, it was all those years later and it had like that was different. So check this out
He came on and with a self-proclaimed
pro-life advocate do you see what I mean at the abortion clinics and
The militia in those woods in North Carolina. They backed him
So the FBI tried to go in and find him and they were like head-to-head with the North Carolina regulators
And they were overmatched the story is unbelievable. You should watch the the manhunt show and
What happened was is to bomb experts
found one thing in the in the Olympic bombing that was similar to the other ones because he was a
explosive expert and that's when they tied it and the way that they got the
Regulators on their side. I'm talking about the FBI is that they showed the regulators that he tricked them that he's not actually a pro-choice
Advocate he bombed the Olympics and once they saw that they were like fuck this and the two actually
came together, went arm to arms, and they walked through the woods together.
The regulators, with the FBI, to try to hunt him.
And they couldn't find him.
He got away for five years.
Do you know how he was found?
This is the end of the story.
How?
He was found dumpster diving at a Taco Bell because he ran out of food.
Because it was five years and he couldn't get food and he didn't, you know what I mean?
He didn't have the supplies to hunt.
So he dosed or dived and some rookie cops stumbled upon them, thought he was homeless,
and you know, ripped him into the car, threw him into the, you know, police, because he
wouldn't identify.
And they identified him with his fingerprints and found out that it was Eric Rudolph, the
You know top of the top 10 fugitive list like this rookie cap, and that's the end of the story
Crazy
Collected the reward or if he didn't get the reward cuz he was on duty
And everybody on the top 10 had a reward on their head
He didn't found him. Oh, yeah, so you're talking about the old for finding the guy. Yeah, I don't think I don't think
a little bit right now. Yeah, he's right in here. We get to collect it. That sucks. Okay. So, uh, the highest reward, this was one of the highest rewards ever offered by the FBI at the time for a domestic terrorist, one million dollars. He was on the, yep, he was on the list. The reward was announced after the 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, which killed an off duty police officer. And then he was connected to the other bombings, the four bombings. Now,
Root off remained on the FBI 10 most wanted list until there's a rest in May of 2003
And he was ultimately caught like I said
I remember this not via a public tip meaning no one claimed the one million dollar reward because that's what I figured
And you're absolutely right. You're absolutely right. Action of duty. Damn. That sucks
Yeah, and he wasn't off-duty or anything, but he was on duty, right?
So he you know like that or anything because that's for like the the I think society that gives a tip
That's what I would say because then you're absolutely
In the dormeration of his duties and shit
And you know what something I never knew that you just told me something because I never thought of that like in an on-duty police officer
Collect a you know, I can't you're absolutely right
It sucks. That's a crazy story though, right? It's called manhunt
Season two like Olympic bomber. It's so where I swear that day that cop hated his job
He's like what what couldn't I just been a guy fucking going to order Taco Bell today?
Well, he was it wasn't he was a senior. Oh, oh, oh the cop or yeah the cop that found yeah
Yeah, cuz that was a million dollars. I just slipped through his hand, right? Yeah
You know what he got famed the cop way though, you know, he brought in the number one domestic terrorist
So like he got held and shit, you know for all that he got lucky he stumbled upon the guy
It was like
I think if you're a reward you have to like actually like give the oh this this person's here
This person's here to give the information
Exactly what you just said psyche if somebody called in and said my name is Patrick psyche
I know of a domestic terrorist whereabouts right now. I am looking at him
He is actually in the back of this Taco Bell in this town
In the dumpster looking for food and then the cops go and get him then that guy would be rewarded a million dollars
when they put those tip lines up exiled, what happens?
Man.
They get a radio all stiffs.
Yeah, everybody.
I mean, you got a whole task force just answering calls.
Oh, I know where the guy is.
He's here.
I know where the guy is.
You know, and they gotta like read through the shit, so.
Yeah.
My, my thing is like this, dude, like back then.
They usually actually put real domestic terrorist on those lists. You know I'm saying nowadays shit you got just anybody that opposes the government's current fucking policy and ideals on the government watch list is ridiculous.
Oh, yeah, but it's like I don't know. I never thought of that like or I gotta look at that but I believe you I mean you never usually
Right at all. I have no ill intents. I have no plans and future harm of any humans or anything
But for some reason I'm on the government terror watch list
No, yeah, all right. Yeah, he's he is but that's maybe because of your arson. I don't know
Maybe I think it's that but I mean what I first got out for years
I wasn't on it. The thing is I think it's just my opposing ideals
I don't believe in their laws and their ways
I mean, I believe I believe some of their laws serve purposes
I believe the bulk majority of those laws are just to keep the people a slave
Did you show, were you the one that showed me a website to go look at? And it said all those things. Somebody showed me on a website. They presented it or they asked me to present it on a panel. I feel like it was on Northwoods because you're always on Northwoods with me.
And did you show me that? Well, maybe it was him. Maybe it was Northwoods. Maybe it was Press.
I don't know. What was the content about?
Man, it was pretty mind-blowing. I gotta ask Press again then for the details.
But he showed me this site that was a .gov site.
So that's a site that is put on by our government.
It's not a dot com, meaning commercial,
where anybody can write anything like Alex Jones
as a commercial, you know,
I think it was me.
I think I shared it in the backstage first.
I think you did.
Do you have that again?
And then I look, and then I, oh, maybe that's what you did.
Maybe you shared it to me and then I clicked on it.
And then you, and then I was reading it to you.
Is that what it was?
I just don't remember the contents of what it's all good. It's all good. It's all good.
All right.
What but it was mind-blowing and I think I have because I was arguing with somebody at the time about the information
I was like dumbass. It's a dot gov site. Yeah. It's not a calm
It's not a dot org. It's not a dot net. It's dot gov
Yeah, and that's when you debate with somebody you both allow to state opinions
But you have to back that opinion up with that
opinion that is government
Government site like
that dude. Exactly. You know, people ask, what are facts? And you say, if it's from a
dot gov website, you know, the government is saying that this is to be a fact. This is
yeah, right. Yeah, or they're debunking it to not be a fact. But regardless, the information
was there for that individual that night. You're right. Stay ignorant. See, that's my
problem with the enslavement of my people.
I agree people are very fucking ignorant because of the enslavement
They don't look at things from an objective mindset or or from open eyes
Yeah, here they walk around blind and they don't have their own belief
They are part of a beast system well said well said
Well said, I agree here here on it man. That's on it because you know what?
I think it like coming from like a history major's viewpoint like I think every Empire
mirrors empires in the past and then to the future so whether it be
like the Roman, whether it be the Greeks,
whether it be the Romans, whether it be the Ottomans,
whether it be the Danes, whether it be the British,
and now us, we all, as decades and centuries go on,
like each generation gets more content, right?
And rights slowly get stripped away,
and technology does that to us too, would you agree?
It has the capabilities. Yes, but because
All right, if the four the technology is being forced upon you. Yes, but if you are choosing to partake in the
Technology, I can't agree with that. See, unfortunately, I participate on this black mirror called the phone
because that's exactly what this is is a scrying mirror and
I chose probably about 14 years ago though to stop watching the Black Mirror called the TV
and it's predicting programming. Yeah, I would say that you are you are ahead of me on that.
I would say that COVID is when I decided that you know what
uh, whether I watch MSNBC or whether I watch Fox news or whether I watch CNN, uh, it's
just parallels of each other that are programming whoever is watching it.
And that's when I snapped, you know, into it and I started watching first amendment
audits when we were locked because I don't, I was a marriage, you know, I had a girlfriend
that like I couldn't see because the families were so, oh, you can't be around your boyfriend
You know and it caused a big riff like with her family. You know what I mean? Like
They were crazy, you know and like that kind of added to it
We ended up breaking up, you know over it because it was tough, you know
She like was like I want to be with you and like so she like broke away from her family exile
Then I was like yo, this is
crazy. I don't, I don't want this. You're so upset all the time.
It's obvious that you miss your family. And I was like, but I respect you.
Like if we're going to do this, we got to do this all the way.
And then not to get too deep into it, but you know what she said next,
then why don't we get married? And I was like, nah, I don't want to do that.
So then she kind of called my bluff and I was like, yo,
I don't want to get married. She's like, then I got it, right? You know?
And that's how we broke up. But my point is, is me being alone now, right?
Single, no kids.
That's when I was like fuck this and I started watching 1A. That's when I got into it.
I didn't find my woman until I was by myself and I focused on self for real.
Honestly until I found my own identity. Yeah, I like that
I like that because I was a guy that kind of went from girlfriend to girlfriend
And then I was like but but not for quick like I was there between 24 and 36 months
And then once they wanted the commitment, I was out, you know, like I was like no
I don't want that like so I could say I you know, I I get fear commitment, you know, like
Look back to the predictive programming. It was 2012 for me, bro. I wasn't I was in LA and there was
I can't even remember what the news story was, but it was going on and they was talking about it was national headlines
So I pretty much googled what done it wasn't Google, but I internet searched whatever browser. I was using
Wait, what did you do then? What did you use to search if it wasn't Google?
I think it was the AOL browser back in 2012.
Nah, it was Google, bro.
In 2012, Google was in full swing, bro.
I feel you, bro.
But I think I was using my AOL browser at the time
because I was still using AOL and shit.
But anyway, I was in LA, and there was some kind of news story going on, and I was like
thinking the news story was on some bullshit, you know, because I'm like, this can't be
national news.
So pretty much I browse searched my local news, and then I was looking up a clip of
that segment of the news and bruh.
they were saying verbatim exact word for word like awful script the same thing this mother
fucking person that now hiring right hiring in LA yeah the same thing that the the press person
announced in the same way they announced it word for word and I was like bro this is scripted
That's one of the fuck I woke up with it later that year
I'm sitting here watching television shows and I'm watching the similarity and how they're trying to build your culture mindset
And I was like fuck this shit
I'm going to do so for me. It was the you remember the election you remember the election and
January 6th and everything, yeah.
So once that happened, that was like, you know,
during the time during COVID, because you know,
do you know the months that had the most deaths in COVID
was actually January of 2021?
Because people think it was like in the middle of 2020,
but it actually was January of 2021.
That's what was so wild that the January 6th,
Yeah, yeah, I I took the like fact-checked it everything like deep like I really they really wasn't reporting on it like
exactly exactly so I have like a
Close close acquaintance that was on the front lines in the hospital and she took a video and she sent me a video
of them throwing body bags into the back of this fucking truck like i mean one two three
four because they're heavy you know you got a couple people here and i mean it was just 12 13
kind of images it was coming out of china that first year in 2019 yeah and that wasn't on the news
so she sent me that because she's in nurse filming and then this is what happened
I turned on Fox News and the correspondent looked at the screen, like right at the screen,
and they were like, you need to reelect Trump because this other side, the Democrat,
you need to fear the Democrats. And then I switched to Rachel Maddow. And what do you think?
She said, she looked right at the screen and said, you need to elect Joe Biden because you need to
thing on both sides you know what I mean just like you said like and the same way they presented it
you know like and they're instilling fear that's what they were doing both sides you know yeah
But I mean
2016 I got confirmation to stop watching these television shows and movies because I
Was looking over at the TV wife was watching one of them Avenger movies
By this time I had learned how to read ancient symbology and sigils and things of that nature
Can you read how the hieroglyphics and shit?
Believe it or not. Yeah, and which way the characters are facing on which way you read
I respect that cuz like I said was through the philosophy and connection, you know
Psychology about 2012 earlier, and uh, that was the year that you know
Everybody was talking about the Mayan calendar and shit and everything else
That year I was learning uh hardware glyphics. What was the date? What was the date of the Mayan calendar?
John Cusack movie remember the juice John Cusack movie 2012
Yeah, what was the date? Was it like February 12th or something or what was the date?
I don't even look it up real quick. Hey, siri. What's the end of the world mayan calendar date?
I mean, at the end of the day, their calendar was the end of an age, they had several ages
and several calendars for several ages, and I had already knew that and studied that back
then, and then you studied the mines, you realized the mines just basically disappeared
off the face of earth, well of course they're going to have a calendar just the last calendar,
I know I don't listen you're an intelligent you're an intelligent guy more calendars. I
Mean I know what you're saying you're an intelligent guy, so it's funny cuz like to you. It's like common knowledge, you know
You just laughing at it like I
You know, I'll tell you I enjoyed my conversations with you every time I run into you I always have a good conversation, man
Well, where you study Aztecs you you understand they was a culture of astrata, you know, they they studied the stars
Struggle they don't have the minds he was their thing. Yeah, so I mean even that game with the ball that they play
It's it's all about astrology. So
You know, you look at their calendar all it was is an astrology calendar of going into one
Celestial body of stars and seeing another celestial body of stars. What is it astrology or is it astronomy?
What's the astronomy?
Astrology to me, it's all the same. Well, no
They all connected all them people in the ancient times connected the stars to some kind of
Deity or something of that nature
Yeah
Well, are you saying because I mean, I have to disagree with you that
Astrology and astronomy aren't the same
But are you saying that it was the same then at that time?
They had to understand they had to understand, you know, the stars first which is astronomy
But as it was basically about astrology, which is you know after study of
because
and you know the game with the ball and all of that is it was a form of worship to a god bro
I never really know
You gotta assume even though we don't know where
Those calendars that they had written it mark going into different celestial bodies had to
Represent some kind of god to those people
Does it make sense?
Yeah, that totally does. I never really thought of it that way because I mean if we're talking today
If I totally disagree astrology and astronomy of two different things, but yeah, yeah
Hold on if I look at it the way you're presenting it to me back then
I can totally see what you're saying that
They mirror they they mesh with each other right for lack of a better word because they have to understand the stars like you said
because I don't
but
I think somebody had already taught them astrology.
I think they knew astronomy.
You know, all the things they were doing,
I don't think, I think it is, how can I say it?
They equipped it into their astrology.
Let me ask you a quick question.
Everything they were doing was some kind of worship
of a God down to even the sacrifices they were doing.
But let me ask you one question
When you say someone taught them like are we going the aliens route? Is that what you're saying or no?
That's not what you're saying
Believe these things to be dimensional beings
Believe them to be dimensional beings and just modern man is too stupid to understand these are dimensional beings
And they don't come from outer space itself
Yeah, all right, cuz I like that of you because when somebody like says to me
It's aliens man. It's a fact and I'm like listen
I can't agree with you, but I can't disagree with you because I don't have any proof
You know and then someone's like oh if you go to this website
I go to the website that they're trying I go this is somebody's opinion man like it's he's not backing it with any facts
Yeah, are you just fucking bullshit? You try okay? No problem because I'm trying to throw a line to the guy telling him you realize
I'm not disagreeing with you. I'm not saying you're wrong
But you have to respect that I can't agree with you right because I just don't have any facts, you know, that's
And then most people nowadays they they have a problem with agreeing to disagree
Yeah, and this yeah. Oh, that's good man. That's good. I like that because it's it's okay to agree to disagree
You're right. That's what you mean man. Yeah
Totally
You ever go to that website solar movies or not if you use that
That's a pretty good one. They haven't shut it down in a while
usually they they shut it down and you just got to get a new
like domain name, you know like
The end, you know they change it
I'm here. I'm more curious about what they've done with
Cause I can't discredit that there might be some kind of life out there also. Oh, definitely. I can't I mean
So I'm kind of questioning what they're doing with this new thing
They're doing like I don't know if you remember the satellite back in the day where it shot out in the space
It had like a radio signal and then it was she's talking about we talked about this already
We talked about this remember from the Jody Foster movie remember
Yeah, yeah, well they sent that to you know, basically give them instructions back to her
You're talking about the hitlers the Hitler speech right? Isn't that what you're talking about? No, no
No, I'm talking about the satellite that the Americans shot up there that uh gave
directions to
Our DNA sequence on that. I believe it was in the 80s. It might have been the set
But uh, we've been using Gemini because I you ever use Gemini that you get a month free if on their premium thing
Because I cost $15 a month
They're shooting
Another satellite up there that you know has our technology now that they can like
It it's got actual sample of our DNA in there and all kinds of shit like
Deep these motherfuckers is reaching out boy. I don't understand that shit
So so this doesn't disprove what you said
But it says while the US government hasn't shot out a satellite with DNA inside of it and directions to earth in the way
You might imagine a direct DNA sample. They did launch
spacecraft with detailed information about earth and humanity
including representations of DNA and they know they haven't shot no samples of DNA out yet
and this is their plan they're planning on doing this and they're planning on using the technology
we have now to show them like
build footage and all kinds of crazy shit bro. That's what you said you said all that so to answer
your the thing when we were talking about the year it says Voyager golden record the NASA Voyager
1 and Voyager 2 spacecraft launched in 1977
Okay, they each carry in quotations a golden record.
These records are essentially time capsules
intended for any intelligent extraterrestrial life forms
who might find them.
So they went out in 1977
and then I have a detailed list.
Um, and this is from NASA. Okay. This what I'm reading right now. I clicked on the source
It's from NASA, you know from the from NASA. So this is from their
Website, I don't know what their website is. So let me click on this thing. I think it's NASA.gov. That's probably what it is
No, wait up. Wait up anything's because we're going somewhere with this now
I clicked on it this what I'm reading is from
WW dot NASA dot gov. So this is what they they put on their website
The contents I have the whole thing here
115 images. I'm not going to read the whole thing and get boring on people, but 115 images including diagrams of mathematical and physical quantities, the solar system and its planets, DNA structure, and the human anatomy and reproduction.
all types of sounds and what's interesting is
I'd love to know this.
You know the movie Close Encounters
that Steven Spielberg put out right after Jaws?
Yeah, go look at CIA.gov.
Yeah, that movie came out like right after this sounds thing.
And I'm wondering,
Like look at CIA.gov some shit really happened on Devil's Peak
But like think about this though. It's a good day to everybody. Salute
Who's that? I don't know. There's the panel. It sounds like is that true?
Hey, I only have a question one brother. I don't know if you guys knew
You know what that day the 9-11 hit
The Pentagon is missing 2.3 trillion dollar that day
I don't want to be I don't want to be rude, but will you listen to our conversation? No. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I do have anything to say about what we were talking about seriously
Yeah, well, I have friend that you know what I mean
Really interested when it comes to this about me when it comes to it. I feel like
But what exiled said before he brought that information to the panel
He was saying that they shot a spacecraft out back in the 70s. Did you know that or no?
Satellite, but yeah, you know
What I'll tell you to look up though is they got plans on shoot the motherfucking upgraded version of that shit out there
Have you guys seen those speedrun before those tiny speedrun that they do racing have you guys seen those?
Hmm
You guys have seen those those little tiny drum
No, I sure have it. You haven't seen a speed drone the racing speed drone. I
Haven't I've seen those military drones though
How big is the one that you see?
The military drones they come in all kinds of sizes
Huh? No, they're big like maybe those speedrun that you see they have a 10,000 times faster and then 10,000 10,000 times bigger
No, we both haven't ever heard of them
So I feel like I feel like if we if we talk about alien and extra terrestrial and they bringing only drone
They not really out from out there
Because they have it like we already in 2025 a year telling me we should we just shooting drone
So this alien or whatever we're talking about or the extraterrestrial group
They haven't gotten nothing no new technology whatsoever. What do you think about that?
I wasn't talking about current days. I was talking about ancient man and what they were doing
No, no, I was just saying even during that time like for example, right?
And let me give you a best example how they steal money from us, right?
for example i feel like the moon landing right do you think in we 2025 now do you think this
group of people back in the days they have enough infrastructure from the moon
to to
That's what the fuck you're on it down me says sound like do you know how to speak on me fucking English on me correctly?
Do you have like a
Is that what the fuck you want to tell me guys?
No, stop, stop fucking, I mean, be honest with me.
Like, you make your own, you make your own stuff look fucking cool, I mean, to be honest.
You're definitely not...
Berto, Berto, Berto, be fair.
I'm assuming fucking English is his second language.
English is my third language, my brother.
Oh, it's third language, so he's doing pretty good, man.
It's the third language, my brother, my bad, my bad.
Yeah, okay, it's your third language.
You're doing pretty good, man.
I think you speak pretty good English. I understand everything you're saying.
Hello. Hi, Crystal. Hi, Crystal. That's the only thing is mine is like I feel like if we talk
about alien and all of this thing and they only have a drone they nap from really out there they
actually lower than us because our military already have a drone capability where
The whole entire city of Chicago can get eliminated within 30 minutes.
We're talking about just our drone capability, so if an alien are coming in this place and
they only have a drone and we haven't seen anything.
They don't I agree with you anything that's ever came to earth in any history has a I don't think it's came to earth from out
I do believe in this technology for something else and I gained I believe it was
Interdimensional beings. I don't believe they're from outer space
Yeah, you're backstage
I was a guy years ago. They depicted these things that look like drones and writings drawlings
Hey, I mean, so I mean at the end of the day
They were dealing with some kind of technology and that that was outside of earth
But it was outside outside of earth not from outer space. It was from dimensional
Exiles, you know crystal because she was that I think
Like she flew she was she's like into aliens. Do you like do you know anything about spacecraft crystal? I
Really don't there was this guy Krakadona. He was like really into
aliens, but
Yeah
No, you know, you've never been abducted. Okay. No, no, not that I know of I don't wouldn't remember. I didn't remember it
so
Same with me
I seen something one time that was like really strange in the air.
But I don't what I was like a little kid. So you know
You guys mess with a cultic arts and it's often known that a cultic arts
People that mess with that's cultic arts have these type of experiences
Good
Okay, I'm sorry
Yeah
A couple days brother. I'm saying they took down my channel boom. I mean channel get taken down
What Alex and them did that? I just got it back. Just like a two hours ago cuz I
Bought me the other night bro
And I didn't take the live down and they took my whole channel bruh, I just got it back I would go
Nice in him in like two or three days, bro. Yeah, bro. He's too nice ago. He hit my panel boy
I didn't let him up. I know that was in the pool
He missed it he let he left before just before you came on he was on you
I deep fried I deep fried his ass you talk about cooking I deep fried that motherfucker. That's what I call
I'm a boy when I'm able to post again, bro
I'm about to cook your ass bro. You you sabotaged my channel
I know that's I know that's that was you they did that bro. That's some gay
Watch me fucking deep fries ass about what was it psyche two hours ago? Yeah
that
I'll make a whole live stream about you bitch, but I ain't gonna come up here. Fuck. I'm psyche's up a lot
But I wanted to tell you that exile one boy. They took my whole channel down brother. I was I was I was sick my stomach, bro
It's all y'all promise out there man
I gotta stop going around doing that weird shit man
People put a lot of time and effort into these shut until these channels man and y'all give people channels taking down man
That's some weird shit, man
Yeah, I know. It's like it's kind of scary
Yeah, it's weird about truth. They take down channels. They like to participate in that's the weirdest thing of it all
Well, yeah, I mean as big maybe that's a really good point. That's a weird psychological
Yeah, no, it's it's also like a lot of these people like it's like, you know in my situation
We as you know, I'm willing to mention this name, but
He's like he's like yeah, he's like he's asked why do you hate sake his channel? Why are you trying to he he's like
I didn't even have an answer. He's like, I don't know. I just don't like him
It is it is like that's all there's like and so sometimes there'll be people like that and unfortunately some
Are like more, you know
Yeah, we'll try harder than others and you know, you know before I go I want to say something about what you just said
That was really good what you just said. I just want to ask you a question
I ain't trying to put that jacket on Alice, but is he known for falling by the people channel?
You know
But that's it's not a coincidence that I didn't let him I didn't let him up on my panel and then ten minutes later
Somebody come up there showing pussy
Yeah, that's Christine or summer date. They take the most time around
She said you got a strike or you got your shower down
My whole channel down it took the whole channel down bro. Did you leave it?
We tolerate did you get it back to still yeah, they took it down yesterday, and I just got it back like a hardware go
I was talking to one of my
text but I was trying to
I got it. Did you get it? Did
you hear? Did you hear me fucking
knock him out for you and he's
trying to fucking fuck you up
before
well
I had the big YouTube to give my channel back I had I told him I say you got people running around YouTube sabotaging people's channels
And I told him mind you I didn't have any strikes on my channel
So I said that's unfair for you to take my channel down and I didn't have any goddamn strikes
Christine is Alex known to porn bomb by any chance
Yeah
Yeah, he's not but he's not but you know, we don't
I want to put that jacket on him, bro
I'm just saying I was I was alive. I never go live three four in the morning
I just happen to go live that night
Alice tried to come up and I didn't let him up. I should have let him up, but I was being a jerk
I didn't let him up and then like 20 minutes later somebody somebody pulls up showing pussy and dicks and stuff like that. So
I don't think it's I don't think he's going for the three letter d word right like that's what he's known for
Three letter d word
Don't know what that is
I texted someone and told her to share my new I texted
She ain't text me back, but it's all good
She was like getting ready for an event this morning. I think I think she has an event today
And I'll share it
Yeah
Yeah, so put do it right now put three little letters and I gave away the d-word so you put d in the front and then
Somebody gets another letter
We'll see it. You ever play D. D. I. K. No, sorry. No, so you get so now you got the head and you got the body
You got to put on now. Let's play hangman. This is fun. Oh
Um, put your new channel in the back and I'll share it so we don't
I got you
I got my main channel back, so it's all great
But you still need to build up your second channel, hun
Remember, go back
Let me go get it, let me go get it and I'll put it in the back, give me a second
Thank you, because I'll share it to other channels too
I'm good at sharing
Maybe I'm spelling it wrong Christine. So D. A. No, no now you got an arm. Now you got a head a body and an arm
Yeah, now you got it you got to do
Hey, do
Look at that Jacob. Look at Jacob. I like that Jacob dog. They dog do gee. Maybe I'm spelling it wrong
Don't think I am though. What'd you say dough dough dog? Oh now you got listen. You're gonna die soon
You got an arm and then a leg. Oh, well the last word the last ready. I got it truth soon. You got it
Hard to get the next year. The last letter is one of the panelists first letter. Okay, see doc
Docks. Oh, yeah. Docs. I'm not sure.
So now, so now, did I spell that right or no? Yes.
Oh, you get that and you guys just made it by one leg. You guys
one leg. Yeah. I just like you could do a hangman as like a
game one time on here. You could put it up on the screen, you
know and play hangman. Yeah.
I don't know if that's like you know trademarked or something but no I mean it's not I mean it's like I know that games
I find are you know, it's something to be fun upstairs like I have an idea
Please I got an idea for you. There is a a Christine probably knows it. Oh, you're talking about Jack box Jack box
There's another one too that I told you about. There's Jackbox. So Jackbox you need two
Devices, but the other one let me find it the other one. You don't need two devices
Wait, I don't even know what we're talking about. I was gonna say
Jackbox is a website somewhere told me about it's like, you know, you really you don't know jack because it's trivia games and you can
Yeah, but you need two devices though. Yeah, you had these two devices
So if everyone on panel what has to have an extra device and then it's able to like, you know, they just put a code in
There's another one just to fun that you only need one device. I'll find I'll find it
Cool. Yeah, I don't know what do you what were you referring to?
Athens
Well, anyways, thank you what I wanted to talk to you about was trivial pursuit because you read like online and
Pogo is the game site and you can play trivial pursuit online free with friends. That's what I was trying to
Okay. Oh, yeah, I was I didn't even interrupt. Yeah, but that's a good idea
And and you know, I do like to should be a night or trivia stuff, but it's like, you know
It's a little bit
I do like to be in stuff. It's like a little I mean, I do I don't know. I'm just kind of I'm tearing down the
Content I think I'm peering on the content a little bit
You know me with you I always like to make sure you're on point and you really have been on point. I'm watching you so
I mean, it's like there's like a little and there's people on the panel want to play and stuff
You know people rag on me and I'm like psyche water psyche water and I shut the fuck up you as dad
You know, I'm like fuck you, you know what I mean? Like I'm just trying to fuck it
Okay, I found the other one is called proud spur. I'm gonna put the link in the back
Okay, is that the one device thing that you guys are talking about? Yeah, it's a one divisor
Yeah, what scum wrote, you see what scum wrote, that's where I came from, like I came from
the debate community from Twitch.
So you're saying twitch Dreamy uses it. Hey, I was the winner
Yesterday on page on trivia. I was I was
I was I was tonight, but they're the same questions. I think she has he like had the same cars
It's a but I never saw this but I thought I got most of them right. I think I got I was trivia queen
I was a winner last night
So all you wear those out there, man
Stop going around keep going back to the bro
You mentioned the truth the more they're gonna do it
Let me land all in these 10 seconds, bro, you won't cut me off
To all you
Go ahead
Before I get on your ass next
You want me to rewind the truth go ahead take it ten seconds stop bitching
Bo
Just for you guys, you know what you got? I'm playing this amount
Now you know you my dog school that doesn't know even though we had that bump in the road you still you still
That's not cool man y'all going around seven times seven times and people's panels like that, bro
Seven times the people's channels like that, bro
That's not cool man, cuz I don't I let everybody up on my panel
Bro, just for me to meet somebody take my kindness of weaknesses and the time I let them up
They pull them by me, but it's my fault
I kind of blame myself for letting this person up and then they're doing that
I have my channel removed people channel channels have been removed
Do y'all know anybody's channels that get removed because of this? Yeah. Yeah, good times
Yeah
Yeah, also have your make sure to cash that this that I've been like, you know, and their alternative
methods, you know
Well, what's what were people talking what were people saying this morning about me? No, so I was trying he was talking shit
I mean you can watch it just the color and I was like I cut them off quick
You know and I was just like yo Christine was so cool because I was at the casino last night
That's why I said I want to just about 150 bucks because you know my system, you know walking out of money
I always bet the max on slots if I lose a certain amount
You know I leave and I am sitting there at the slots and I'm bored. So what do I do?
I hop on Sam is and I see
The body I see the puppy dog, you know, the beautiful and I'm like no way my mom's here. So I wrote like oh
Someone wrote
Christie this is the best part like when people ask oh my god, is that really your mom you are like you just said what do you like?
Yes, I am school of Athens Bob and that was it and I was like yes
So like all these dumb people actually believed it, but like
So many other people would have been like, I'm not his mom.
I'm like, you know what I mean?
It just starts with the fish, and you were perfect.
And then Alex, you know, he couldn't really say anything.
So he kind of.
Well, this community has a problem with a person.
And I will make sure this person, in any way, shape,
or form, stays off panels.
OK.
I don't even want to get into it because psyche, you know, I'll get upset with you know, you know
Psyche was probably very upset last night at this pursuit for what?
You want to know so I
Was trying to elude him if we're talking about the same person why he was upset with but I saw like I think you
Didn't you remove somebody for I did?
Yeah, and I think it's the same person. We're talking about that. I am so upset with just because of my buddy Miguel
You know, right? That's the same person we're talking about. Yeah. Well, he went after psych on
His panel the other night for no reason and he said some nasty things about psych it's bad
The psych has done nothing but support him. Yeah, and I was trying to tell psyche and I don't want psyche to get upset right now because
This is no way you heard me before I said you've been doing great
You can tell me anything you don't like about me. I'm not gonna get upset. So just please don't get upset quick that day
when I let when I was gone for a little while from your panel, I was trying to explain to you
what she was doing and you know you are so they about they what what they I don't know like
and uh like you just were kind of lying to it because you're not stupid you're just supportive
you know what I mean and I saw it in your eyes that you would be in genuine and she wasn't she
They were trying to get content out of it, you know, but I'll leave it at that and just never take an accountability for what I've said.
Psy has always supported them and I understand and it's like, I support gay and trans. I truly do, but this person, I can't support.
Yeah, and you know what she'll do, right or he'll do they'll they'll try to turn it around and
Say that you're a basher of it because that's what they
I don't care. I know I know that but my point is is that's the game
We don't care because of our actions. No one will believe it, but that's what they do
She goes around he goes around you know what I mean and just says those things
But you've seen the other day on beatus. It was about a month ago. That's what she
I was like, you know, I have a problem with you and like, I don't even know how you are. And I was like, I don't expect you to because I remember that day and what you did. And then I brought up the scenario and walked through it. And she was like, all I know is, is that you're a basher of LGBT. And I was like, that's what you're going to give me from it. And that's all they had, you know.
You know the stuff they're putting in society because I think they're a lot of the trend stuff is being pushed on to the society in order to like
Cause like a negative reaction. I think it can roll back, right?
I think it's I'm gonna already be happy cuz like so
But this is the end the same time. It's like I do support, you know
And I know that they have difficult lives and it goes a lot of stuff and look at a lot of hate and I kind of like
Good friend
that is the trans. And I love her dearly. And it pisses me off that its behavior could
affect my friend's life.
Yeah, I'd say to answer you on that. I'm trying to think right now. I have met many trans people
I am friends with a ton of homosexuals
I wouldn't say very close transgender people just because it's just the way it's worked out
But I've met tons and I support them especially adults like when you have that choice
I want hundred percent support any choice that they want to make when it comes to the children
I don't really have an answer for it because
that's a gray area right so like with the parents or guardians I don't know like I don't know my opinion on that yet and what like I can even have an opinion on you know
I have I have a friend and she she got married
and
the two of them
The other one got artificially inseminated and have has a beautiful
Baby girl and they're both great moms
They are beautiful moms. They have got such a well-rounded
beautiful child
One second. I'll be right back. Yep
You know so it's just I I won't I won't do him I won't
Well, and piranha, we we shouldn't be ducking anybody and like I have said over and over
We shouldn't be talking about families either
We shouldn't I mean I'm gonna say something to you pirama and don't take this as an insult because it's not but I just think that your statements naive
I agree with you
But I do see the lol at the end of it
So actually I probably should eat my words because maybe you are just joking about it like that is the simple answer, right?
So it's just funny how like
People get mad and then they dox right, but firama check this out
Isn't it funny psyche said this just before a lot of times the people that dox are
The people that like being on the channel, right? Isn't that weird?
Because I didn't see his lol, you know is
Bobby greeting everybody. Good morning
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I respect that scum. I respect that a lot scum. Oh
No, you just said that scum because Christine will tell you when she comes back
That's exactly what I did. That's the three weeks ago about three weeks ago
I was
magnetizing bad energy your absolute like the same exact thing
So this is actually the believe it or not psyche. This is the first panel that I've been on in
I'd say 21 days about three weeks. Did you know that?
No, I haven't seen you for a while, you know, I just know but I mean any panel this was the first
Yeah been on and I just I've chatted really quick and said hello, but uh
Yeah, I never went up. That's why I wasn't even planning on coming up. Did you notice how I was trying to drum up donations for you?
Did you notice that? Yeah, yeah, I appreciate that because it's so funny. It's so funny like
J1 was in the in there and J1 was like I
Said to J1. Hey J1 if you donate a one gift membership to psyche, I'll go up on panel. Did you see that or no?
Yeah, I did
And then J1 was like, why don't you just go on the panel?
And I was like, why don't you just donate one gift membership?
And he was like, well, I lost my wallet.
And then Amanda went into him.
You know, Amanda was like, I had to lose your wallet.
And then he's like, um, I lost it in my house and then I was like, so do you have any money
to live on?
And he goes, well, I spent all my money on 4th of July food.
And I was like, and then Amanda goes, how did you spend all that money if you'd lost
your wallet?
And then he was like, um, I did with cash and it was like, I don't know about this narrative
school.
You know, I'm like, yeah, there's too many gaps in it.
You donated one gift membership, right?
So I was thinking I was going to come up, but then I'm like, Alex,
you have to match psyches.
You know what I mean?
And I'm just getting and then somebody paid for stay terms.
Was that easy?
Uh for a state turn. Yes. Oh, but that was you know, because he donated a few days ago for so to buy a deck of cards
And then he was like so but then it was then he made it 25, but then I've unbanned
Let me get let me ask you a question before you tell me he donated $18 and then he added seven to it
Is that what it was? Yeah, it was what it was 18 so I could buy a deck of cards and then
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And it was so funny because I was on Kate's
and donated a membership.
And guess who got the membership gift at tour?
You know what happened to me on site wasn't it on your panel psyche. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was so weird. I donate and I got it. I'm like this at the point of this. I beat you. I did that on psyche's final about a month ago. I donated one gift membership and I got it.
To like receive a free membership like I've noticed I've got I've got my my like I've gotten actually on emas
I bought a membership once there
Gifted one and then it was gifted to my other like one of my other accounts that I
I don't think they know to opt in
Yeah, you have to you have to click on the little gift box what someone does donate
There's a gift box on the top and then you have to click on that and say opt-ins to receive like
Possibilities of the gift to the membership you have to opt-in and then be a member
I never opted in to anything and I've gotten gift memberships
We're along the line you did home
Yes, you know, I can really lucky. Do you know how many gift memberships? Oh, I get them all the time, too
I get a lot too. How many do you have?
Oh
If you go to subscriptions on your phone and you hit all the purchase things on there
And I got a gift membership to a Long Island audit psyche
Awakens which actually ends in like a day. So I have to pay that forward in like the next 24 hours
Hot mess summer
Or maybe it was on hot messes them. I don't know and then oh no actually I bought that one
Speak easy. I got a gift membership and Harvey free birds like I didn't know where like I get because I'm
well, if you if you go to your
Your your channels and click all all the ones that you have a membership to are at the top
At least mine aren't there at the top
Yeah, that's what I just told you. Oh, I thought you I thought you said you had to go into your thing
Never I'm just hit subscriptions and then on the top is purchased
Yeah, but they don't tell you which is gift and which is purchased yourself
That's why I was trying to think hot mess summers
I purchased and then the thing was is something really cool happened tonight right before you came on
Exiled came up and he's like oh school. I haven't seen you in a while
He goes the last time I saw you you were on hot mess when remember when she was doing the walk on
Yeah, and I gifted a membership and exiled got it and he came on the panel and was like yo school
I promised you that I would pay it forward and I was like what are you talking about he goes on that hot mess summer
You donated it like almost a month ago. So next time him and I are on the hot mess channel together
He's waiting for us. He's gonna pay it forward and do a gift membership for somebody else, which I thought was really cool
Well, and that's the whole point of I mean I I always gift a membership because a
It'll get other viewers in
be hopefully the person who gets it pays it forward. But not everybody can't say
okay like that. Of course of course but that's why you use the word hopefully and
then if anybody attacks you fuck you people can't do it you say that's why I
said and I'm and I'm totally okay and that's why I like doing it because some
people can't.
And that's their opportunity to possibly get one
I have I have no problem with people who can't and and I don't have a problem people don't want you either
I get it. It's okay
Hey psyche, can you can you highlight a comment at 902 by piranha?
Christine tell everyone if I had a dime
for
To the one that says you sound like if I had a dime Christine. I'll tell you for how many times
This this has been said to me
Is it 902 you sound like?
Times
Wait till they me and I run out you ought to hear when the two of them go at it. They it's like oh my god
You know
Like he or she I don't I just I've never met my run. I love that name though
Because it's like piranha piranha. Do you know is a girl or a guy I have no clue
But do they come?
Piranha is a girl and piranha was like my co-host like the first co-host
Yeah, she doesn't the panel sometimes
Yeah, I like
And scum is real cool too because did you see the one underneath by ronnie click on that one?
This is an important comment because I asked scum to come up and he wrote school of happens
I dig your game in and like it's cool
You know like I like you want to come up and he says but I've been
Magnetizing bad energy you see that one's like put that up there
And I don't want to bring that to psyche's panel and I wanted to say Christine
You remember you and I had that conversation about three weeks ago
and this is the first panel that I've been on in about 21 days that was that and so
Hey, Braun, very good morning. Oh, nice, Braun. So sometimes you see that one?
What's this thing to scum put that up. Okay. Okay. Yeah, okay. Yeah, okay
Yeah, this is important because this is good advice any time
You magnetizing that bad energy and if you listen to yourself and you don't like what you hear take a break, you know
Go away, you know focus on something else work
Or you know what I mean family and stuff like that because that's what I did in
Realized I hung out with my nieces and I said, you know what I was talking to my brother. It's like I feel like I haven't been around
He's like oh my gosh that play was so cute. You like that, right?
Yeah, and I asked him I was like I feel like I haven't been around he's like you kind of haven't but you know
Everybody's busy and I was like no no no no. This is what's important. He goes. Yeah. Yeah, you know and
You know, you don't fall off for months and months, but I got kind of a gig, I got sucked
into the, you know, to the screen, man, and so that's really cool, Scum, really cool.
Sorry, I'm just saying like right now. I'm going through my mentions on my account and I have all these mentions like oh
I'm like, you know Nick was mentioning and then there's all these videos chip cake made of me and then there's others
There's other videos, but I'm just oh
You psyche you're gonna love this I'm gonna play it actually so somebody must have been listening to your panel before when I asked
Yumi
Yeah
I said are you the person that sang karaoke and you were like no, that's somebody else that person was listening and
She said me this is so funny
Listen she goes I found you I got a heart from her. Where is it?
What
That's that's Jonah, right is it Jonah or yeah
They did the song they did the song. Do you remember the song or no? Yeah, I never
Listen to this. This is great. I think Christine was it
Yeah
Is it that that person was listening right? Yeah, she was she's like a great friend
Like she's one of the first people to help me start this channel. Like I like she really
She's a very very sweet suit is her name her
Her channel is Chona adventures blog and she's Thailand and she's like the sweetest the sweetest person
So she's not sometimes she's in the quieter in chat, but I think she does uh, she does watch the school of Athens. Yeah, absolutely
Yeah, uh, it's respect bronze. What's up dingle? Who else is here boom on shoe?
So let's see when she says we'll pay money
to be
This isn't gonna be out. I'm just here to stack alex to save you all
Pat is a kid dude. I'm not even gay or anything, but he's good cool. Oh, thank you. Oh, yeah
Well, I don't know. I'm getting a lot of uh
Meaning I don't think they're kind of going it's a quiet quieter, but it's like it's still it's like it's doing better
Just quality people here sometimes for the conversation and
Having more fun so
They're going good lately. Yeah, Christine's away. Let's see who's chad right here
Hey, we got people finally come in in the chat this morning. You're chilling like a villain good morning Dingle
Uh, yeah, I'm bronze verbose of guys. Yeah, you know, there's other channels, you know, I know there's
Over right now. There's some other people you guys are familiar. There's I can't she doesn't have to say her name
So I won't but there's the content creator that's like mad at me
And I think she's maybe told people like just like stay away from me and I'm just a bad person
That's okay, you know, it's but
I just asked, you know, judge, judge me on our relationship not on based on what somebody else says, but
Like it's your choice. Hi. What's up? What's what are you doing?
Uh-oh, what was that? What was that? Did you hear something bad with those penis?
Did you just show us penis? Hello
Give me more entangle
Well, I don't know so I've been watching but it looks like some of these are funny
Funny clips one of them. I'm willy Wonka and like a and three diamonds like
Where is she?
Three diamonds like
Put your diamonds like like violent Beauregard. I think
No, she's the person's like pull she's like
Oh that will be does the from pulp fiction. They're a beta is like the John Travolta and then who's that?
She's like looking at
He's looking at like
I don't know who they made me raise you demon or something. It's pretty funny
I would make a great way wonky. Yeah, I'll see the picture when I come up in a second. Let me see
Okay, shout out you're like pretty awesome. Thank you for tagging me on these on these videos
I'll try to get the picture. I think we wonk for halloween. Yeah, I need a purple
A purple suit and uh, oh my gosh your picture is beautiful. You look pretty cool
I don't know if they'll show me. Let's see. I wonder.
Never's Avalovine. Okay. Here's the full fiction.
Dream lines of cocaine.
I don't know. I guess they use Sandman space for like the...
I don't see where they, I don't see any Willy Wonka
about you in the picture.
I can't, let's see.
Well.
Oh yeah, so, Nick, he's posting, he's like, let's see.
He sent me a drawing, or he didn't see,
he sent me a picture of a drawing.
Thinking Nick for the mentions
Yeah, he drew this he drew a drawing of me. I think it's me in my speedo. I this it kind of
Kind of hard to see you might see
There's like there's a like feet. There's like the nor I think it looks like I love my right
My skin's a dream, but yeah, I don't know. I put the blanket. What's that? What is that?
We're wearing oh my pants are down and there I am in the and then does me
Oh, and they can see you see the whole thing. It's me in a speedo
Make what a talented artist. I would love to own that someday some Wonka bars. Yeah, do you know like the Wonka bars?
They're like every word they're made of wood
They think the props the professor made of wood because I saw the guy on the
What's that I don't like the pond pond pond or to the ponch up so
And he goes and buys some Wonka stuff. I think he buys like a golden ticket
I think he buys like an everlasting golf stopper and then he asked him to throw in a couple of this of the Wonka bar
Props for free because they're like they're like the least expensive ones
I think the everlasting golf stopper was quite expensive. I think it was like
Hey, I
Don't know I'm thinking 250 that's $250,000 but that might be high, but I don't know I think it
Maybe it was maybe it was less than that, but I think it was pretty high. You can send a good deal of some money there
I
Gotta go to take it. I love Willy Wonka because it's like
That's a good like story, but you know, I'll be all represent like the
Some of the sin if you just was wonky you should run some water in the yard to put chocolate in it
And your own little chocolate. I should I cared
You guys do you want to donate through this? I wish I put a Willy Wonka costume in a like a large fondue fountain
We could do a diddy fondue. I was chilling over on summer because she's
She was playing fucking Kendrick Lamar shit that I love because I fucking love Kendrick Lamar
You know he graduated sixth in his class psyche 4.1 weighted GPA Wow
You know, I don't know
Well, I am at my GPA in high school. It was just terrible. I was like, I had like a 2.6
You know that Kendrick Lamar graduated sixth in this class at Compton High School with a 4.1
I'm not surprised. I'm not surprised. You know, there's so many talented intelligent people
It's like we're your player intelligence, but he goes above and beyond intelligence. We're talking like
Philosophy like because you've heard me talk about fear based ideologies a lot because I believe you know
There's been you know psych of the psychological psychology papers, you know written to me
Fear is what drives humans more than any other emotion, right?
And a lot of people will counter with, I think, anger, but everyone has agreed that anger in the scientific, you know, community is a secondary emotion, every single psychologist is a unanimous.
So it can't be anger, like it can be other stuff, sadness, loneliness.
Well, I mean, it's like, I think emotions are like, you know, the moon because they shift and everything with like, you know, it changed your time.
What is that you said?
Not it was an anger, but it was like
It's a scientific fear
that
Anger is a secondary emotion. So what I'm trying is yeah, I'm trying to say
Okay, if you had a graph of other emotions loneliness, right sadness
Fear right there would be percentages, right?
Then what is first before anger and my belief is that fear has the highest percentage right?
Right, okay, because there's something called the reptilian brain. It's like the oldest part of our of our brain
It's our you know the first part of it and it
Is the charge of like reflexes and also something called the fight or flight syndrome and so fight or flight
That'll be basically regulated by a fear and that's like one of the most important survival parts of it
And so it makes sense that we'll have the strongest emotional reactions maybe to fears maybe why also, you know
So much fear is used to manipulate people and
by people that know know about you know that kind of thing and so
Yeah, that makes sense. I'm just saying yeah, maybe surely fear is what one of the most
of mobilizing or immobilizing can also paralyze
rather than make people move more.
So maybe it works both ways.
Hey, was that Bronzberg?
You're talking about the brain stem.
Hey, Bronz, what are you doing?
You're talking about the brain stem, right?
The reptilian brain, like there's like a little thing,
it's like the first part of the brain,
it's like the stem and like-
Yeah, so it says exactly what you just said.
I always admit like I never try to act smart. I always like if I look something up
I tell you, you know, like people will try to say he's trying to act smart like
Stupid but a stupid person can't play smart. Yeah, like that. You always got them quotes. That's just a t-shirt, bro
The most basic ever let evolutionary oldest structures of the brain primarily the brain stem and I don't know how to pronounce this
But the base are you basil ganglia basil ganglia?
How do you pronounce that anybody know? Yeah, you said he said he said it pretty much, right? Yes al and I know gang
Yeah, the basal ganglia. Yeah. Yeah, it's associated with the instinctive grid survival based behaviors
So everything you just said is fucking on like 100% true
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, the brain is called like the triune brain like we have and what differentiates us from other
I guess even mammals as the neocortex the human beings develop this third part of the neocortex and so
That's like the more is that later. Is that like later in the evolution?
Yeah, I think I'm gonna be doing research on this, you know for the next like I'd say 48 hours when I'm on the toilet and stuff because
I'm serious. Yeah thinking and
I don't know enough about the brain
because you know when people say I majored in this
and then I minored in this like bronze will tell you
when people say they minored in stuff
it just means you took like right bronze like electives
and then you know what I mean they use
you took a few classes
but that was a big thing when you were minor
to your degree
yeah
but what I mean is you have a major right
and then
you just take a couple of classes like bronze said and people use the term minor very loosely. Oh,
I majored in history and I'm minored in philosophy and psychology and you know what I mean like
when I was in school and my history courses like I took a course in just the battle of Hastings
you know 1066 the like the syllabus like he was like
week two to week three, you know?
And I took like a psychology course here,
the one, right, Bronze,
where you take 101, 102, right?
Like what do you take in psychology that you have to
in the early years?
Yeah, I mean I remember when it was like when I first started college you don't the most annoying thing is that they gave us the
Refreshers course and I was pissed cuz I was oh
You had to take that. Oh, I was like, why do we need to do that? I didn't have to take that
Yeah, I didn't have to take that but I know what you're talking about
Yeah, I can't say yeah, well, I
Isn't right bronze. Why do you have to I'm totally with you cuz I got my friends
Why do you have to take that?
It's such a waste of money because it because you come in there and they be like, okay
Well, welcome to college, but you know, we're gonna refresh you off of the shit that you learn when you was a house
I didn't have to take refreshers. No, I didn't either but he's right bronze is right about that because I
I did and here's the other thing though you got to remember at least when I had to go into college, I had to take a college entrance exam and depending upon what number you got was depending if you had to take any reference
You know what I mean? We can like speak more like if I had this or you had that
You know, I mean Christine because it's different well, and it could have been the degree type too
You think so yeah
Well, I
Like if you go to a four-year school like what do you mean what kind of degree type?
Well, you gotta remember my first degree that I started on was chemical engineering
That was my first degree when I switched it
Yeah, okay. So go ahead expand. So I didn't have to take any but I think because my entrance exam was so high I
Didn't have to take any refreshers
I don't know I want to I remember because we're going back now
20 like 20 years in change. So I
Remember even taking and like did you remember taking bronze which he's talking about that?
Entrance course thing. I don't remember how to take a college insurance exam. Oh, I did or you didn't because I didn't
Know I didn't yeah, I didn't either. I mean, maybe but maybe it's because I went to a private
College, I did too
Yeah, the first school I went to was in the SUNY or CUNY now because you talk about the next colleges I went to yeah
They were you know how much you cost a semester for a SUNY school if you were a resident
Now it was seven grand semester
It's nothing now if you go to a SUNY school now if you graduated high school you get two years free
Look at this real quick
Shit
What oh who did that?
There's one of me in summer too
We
You know, there's one of me a summer. Oh, yeah
That's a video on fd's
And clip talk, I don't know which one
And I think it's a he he is so talented
Seriously, so talented the way he can put clips together and put it to music and it
flows.
I've never seen somebody that talented ever.
I don't know if it's the I'm not I'm not I don't I don't think Joe's mind. I don't either. I like I like
I think it's I think it's all fun. I don't I don't and I hope nobody ever tries to
You know, yeah, yeah
Yeah, oh, yeah, we have fun. We have laughs
Yeah, he was like a little bit drunk last night. I had to put him backstage if you sorry
I put Alex backstage for like 10 15 times the night, you know
It was crazy
Yo, I had to smack him up a little bit again. I tried to stay quiet
But then when he goes too far just for Alex. Yeah, I got it, you know
Nothing you under the sun sometimes you just got to get his ass beat, but then he's got a comment
He learns it afterwards. You throw it
That's right. You throw a throw punch. You throw a throw punch. I gave him a new nickname Alex the dunce McQueen
You know what I mean because he was trying to say you want to be a cool kid. I said Alex
I still did I still don't understand. I was like Alex. You're so far in the corner in the classroom
You got a dunce cap. You're so far away from the cool kids and shorty came up and started laughing so hard
And he got so past Alex. I
Still couldn't find where y'all were talking about me and I don't know who was talking
Okay, so who's talking? So what happened? No, who's talking?
He's like Candy Man
Wait, what happened?
Oh, he's here, he's here.
Oh my god!
has crystal marita this morning what wait wait wait why don't tell us about the time he raped that